<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile on Crypt0 News</title>
    <link>//crypt0.net/categories/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile on Crypt0 News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Dataence. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crypt0.net/categories/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Qualcomm chips to be used for Microsoft Windows 10 Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s Snapdragon processor offers some of the most advanced features of mobile computing, including Gigabit LTE connectivity, advanced &amp;hellip; Windows 10 Devices will run on Qualcomm Snapdragon Processor This announcement at the WinHEC 2016 came as a surprise and is expected to take on the mobile computing segment by storm. With the support for &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Out of date websites cost Kiwi businesses dearly &amp;ldquo;These mobile apps, by their very nature, are designed to be responsive and their popularity only goes to prove just how popular mobile computing &amp;hellip; Canberra reseller MIT Services prepares for school BYOD surge Being the end of financial year for most independent schools in Canberra, it&amp;rsquo;s when they start updating their laptop fleets and bring-your-own-device &amp;hellip; The BYOD revolution has added the traditional desk phone to the endangered CIOReview It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that ditching the desk phone is not always analogous with canceling your phone service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Detailed examination of the North American that is expected to contribute WhaTech The Mobile Device Management (MDM) market is estimated to grow from USD 1.69 Billion in 2016 to USD 5.32 Billion by 2021, at a Compound &amp;hellip; Qualcomm Collaborates with Microsoft to Support Windows 10 Computing Yahoo Finance &amp;ldquo;Qualcomm Snapdragon processors offer one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced mobile computing features, including Gigabit LTE connectivity, advanced &amp;hellip; Microsoft Unveils Windows 10 for Qualcomm Chips, a Blow to Intel s dominance in PCs and help the software maker gain a bigger foothold in mobile computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
More than one in three Singapore CIOs believe their employees are their MIS Asia &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) practices pose a major cybersecurity threat which requires protecting corporate networks and data, mobile device &amp;hellip; More than one in three Singapore CIOs believe their employees are their MIS Asia Technical applications are also implemented - 53 percent say they are deploying mobile device management technology, and 52 percent are using &amp;hellip; Global LiDAR Market to Grow at a CAGR of 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
When to Choose Hybrid Platforms for Your App Development Its advent initiated with the growing trend of Bring your own device also, known as BYOD. The simple implication is that now, the rather than &amp;hellip; High Capacity (Exceeding 20000 mAh) Power Banks Market Steady Rise In The Mobile Computing Today According to a new market report published by Credence Research, Inc., High Capacity Power Banks Market (Exceeding 20,000 mAh) (By End-use &amp;hellip; iOS is still an amazing achievement that redefined the world of mobile Quartz Last week&amp;rsquo;s Monday Note on the Macintosh endgame generated more comments and email than usual, which prompts me to pursue the topic, this &amp;hellip; What Analysts say about Marvell Technology Group Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Cybersecurity threats loom larger from within: survey They are stepping up against the security risks posed by the widespread use of Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) practices, where employees use their &amp;hellip; Discover the project portfolio management (ppm) market overview, size, WhaTech The demand is further projected to be driven by factors like the increasing trend of bring your own device (BYOD) or workforce mobility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
INTI, IBM partner to develop highly employable students It also addresses the rising centrality of mobile computing, security, and social computing. Tim Bulow, CEO of INTI International University &amp;amp; Colleges &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Achieving True Productivity with Unified Communications The BYOD revolution has added the traditional desk phone to the endangered species list, but is this the end? It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that ditching the &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Two Effective and Reliable Ways to Restore Bricked iPhone Data After the release of iOS 10, some iPhone users report that a few issues happen to their device after updating to the newest iOS version. iOS 10 &amp;hellip; COPE, CORE, BYOD? Deciphering Mobility for SMBs Mobility management is big with small companies a big headache, a big expense and a big area of possible conflict with mobile-savvy employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Clevest Extends Cityworks Interface Under Their Development Partner Program &amp;hellip; to transform their field operations by harnessing the power of our software and deep domain knowledge of mobile computing and utility operations. Jargon Breakdown: 11 Cybersecurity Terms Every Businessperson Should Know Bring Your Own Device policies are being quickly adopted by workplaces everywhere and for good reason! BYOD is generally more affordable for &amp;hellip; Samsung Galaxy C7 Pro Spotted with 16MP Primary Camera Samsung Galaxy C7 Pro is grabbing the eyeballs again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
The Strategy That Made Apple Computers a Leader in Mobile Computing For Steve Jobs, having the cheapest computer on the market wasn&amp;rsquo;t the goal. Instead, he wanted to produce a machine that would be better for users. Bringing security to the BYOD phenomenon Mobile device management systems (MDM) have been met with raised eyebrows, and in some cases have even stalled BYOD attempts in its tracks &amp;hellip; Wireless Gigabit (WiGig) Market Analysis By Type (802.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
New report examines the Mobile Security Software market by identifying WhaTech To calculate the market size, the report considers the sales of mobile security applications and mobile device management (MDM) software for &amp;hellip; Cyber Monday deals: mobile computing and audio Greetings again, gerbils. In the previous installment of Cyber Monday deals, we covered components and peripherals. Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time to get your mobile &amp;hellip; Energy Efficiency of Computing: What&amp;rsquo;s Next?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
The Digital Turbine Inc. (APPS) Rating Lowered to Sell at Zacks Investment DailyQuint The company&amp;rsquo;s product include DT Ignite&amp;trade;, a mobile device management solution with targeted app distribution capabilities, DT IQ&amp;trade;, &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
[ November 25, 2016 ] Microsoft Releases Surface Phone Specs to Run on About Cruise Ships &amp;hellip; as the first processor to be produced in 10-nanometer process that promises more mobile computing power with increased efficiency of energy use. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
BYOD Policies At Law Firms: Tips For Securing Devices smartphones for work are primarily technological, but a much larger piece of &amp;hellip; Desktop Central lets you manage Server, Mobile &amp;amp; Desktops Desktop Central is integrated desktop and mobile device management software for Windows, Mac &amp;amp; Linux that helps you in managing servers, laptops &amp;hellip; Samsung to Launch Jet Black Galaxy S7 Samsung always prefer giving different options to their customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Strategies to Protect Networks as Personal Devices Connect Another way IT departments can tackle the challenges associated with BYOD is through mobile-device-management (MDM) software designed &amp;hellip; Alternative Networks (LON:AN) Analyst Target Prices Recently stock market analysts have updated their consensus ratings on shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN). The newest analyst ratings which &amp;hellip; BYOD Security : Global Industry Size, Share, Segments Analysis and Forecast Satellite PR News (press release) BYOD i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Acronis Expands Service Providers&amp;rsquo; Portfolio with File Sync &amp;amp; Share and a CSO Australia &amp;hellip; companies and organisations faced with a challenge to open access to their data, for example, through a Bring-Your-Own Device (BYOD) program, &amp;hellip; Edimax Launches Powerful 11AC Dual-Band Enterprise Wireless Solution DATAQUEST It is ideal for crowded environments and BYOD workplaces by providing adjustable RF output power and high receiver sensitivity for wide coverage &amp;hellip; Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) Market Analysis by (Device, Industry), Global U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
BYOD paperless crane inspection app launched Techs4Biz has introduced a new paperless crane inspection application that eliminates the hassles of paperwork during crane maintenance while &amp;hellip; Learn details of the Worldwide cyber security market technology, analysis, WhaTech With the proliferation of cloud, mobility, and bring your own device (BYOD), endpoint protection is crucial for all security departments. Cyber security &amp;hellip; OnePlus 3T Has Better Hardware and Camera than its Predecessor A lot of rumours were going on about the upcoming model of OnePlus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
NEC Concludes Third Multi-Vendor Wireless Transport SDN Proof of Concept ACN Newswire (press release) Furthermore, the available computing power in the EX Advanced allows it to perform additional Mobile Computing functions, such as the one &amp;hellip; BYOD &amp;amp; enterprise mobility market growing worth 73.30 billion USD by 2021 WhaTech Increased productivity and employee satisfaction, reduced hardware cost for enterprises, increase smartphone penetration, demand for enterprise &amp;hellip; BYOD &amp;amp; enterprise mobility market growing worth 73.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Teaching Hong Kong students to embrace computational thinking MIT App Inventor is an intuitive introduction to programming and mobile computing. Hal Abelson, the Class of 1922 Professor of Computer Science &amp;hellip; Mobile Device Management Market by Solution, Service, Deployment Type, Military Technologies LONDON, Nov. 14, 2016 /PRNewswire/ Increasing smartphone and tablet penetration, strong adoption of BYOD policies, and growing security &amp;hellip; 3 considerations for securing your mobile devices Generally, EMM solutions include mobile device management (MDM), mobile application management (MAM) and mobile information management &amp;hellip; Research details developments in the Global bring your own device market WhaTech Solutions such as mobile device management (MDM) and mobile application and content management have been employed by organizations in &amp;hellip; Research details developments in the Global bring your own device market WhaTech The global BYOD market is expected to reach USD 238.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Android Operating System is the Future of Mobile Computing and Smartphones The new Android phones are phones that operate on the Linux Kernal mobile operating System. It was developed by Android Inc, and later purchased &amp;hellip; Zebra launches mobile computers for retail tasks But you need mobile computing to unlock that potential value.&amp;rdquo; The TC5 line is intended to be a general retail computer, not a specialized tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
BYOD: With greater device choice comes greater responsibility, Australian IT Brief Australia Gone are the days of being locked into using a specific device or operating system in a workplace, as now 60% of Australian organisations now allow &amp;hellip; Brocade announces Ruckus Cloudpath ES 5.0 Brocade has announced the availability of Ruckus Cloudpath ES 5.0 software. The new release builds on previous BYOD onboarding capabilities to &amp;hellip; Google Denies EU Complaint About Android Bundling Charges In a blog post, Google Senior Vice President and General Counsel Kent Walker characterized the EU complaints against the company as unfounded &amp;hellip; Research delivers insight into the mobile cloud market: global industry WhaTech Mobile Cloud Computing is the amalgamation of cloud computing, wireless networks and mobile computing to fetch enhanced computational &amp;hellip; Whatsapp Offers Two-Step Verification Process for Beta Users We have seen that Whatsapp aggressively brought many new features this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
What is mobile device specific co should criteria for specific business uses (e. Jul 30, 2016 To register a &amp;hellip; Momentum Stocks in Focus: Extreme Networks Inc. (EXTR), The Bank of Nova iStreetWire &amp;hellip; other third party network management tools for mobile device management integration, threat response next generation firewall, security information &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
FG grants petrovice patent on solution for last mile connectivity &amp;amp; Guardian &amp;hellip; which has been the major obstacle to mobile-computing penetration and cloud computing for rural areas and developing countries with last-mile &amp;hellip; NVIDIA Corp. Earnings: A Home Run in the Data Center Thursday evening, NVIDIA (NASDAQ: NVDA) reported results for the third quarter of fiscal year 2017. The graphics and mobile computing specialist&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; How to maintain data and document security with a mobile workforce Managed via mobile device management (MDM) or policy, you can employ a variation of controls depending on your specific requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Toshiba Forms New Company, Confirms Commitment to Mobile Computing in Digital Signage Connection This new Toshiba subsidiary will focus on delivering business-to-business mobile computing solutions and services to Enterprise, Government, &amp;hellip; Time For a Mobile Security Assessment A Comprehensive Mobile Security HIT Consultant 20% of BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) programs will fail because IT departments are trying to implement MDM solutions that are too restrictive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Toshiba Forms New Company, Confirms Commitment to Mobile Computing in Business Wire (press release) SYDNEY&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Toshiba America Information Systems, Inc., today announced the creation of a wholly owned Australian subsidiary, &amp;hellip; DaaS and BYOD: a Partnership Made in the Cloud One way to deal with this issue is mobile device management a number of technologies that guard proprietary data while maintaining the privacy of &amp;hellip; How should companies deal with data security when they have a BYOD policy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
HTC Bolt May Arrive in Black Colour HTC may soon launch a new gadget for their customers and it may be named as HTC 10 Evo or HTC Bolt. The names will be different for different &amp;hellip; Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s Yoga Book Review: A Keyless Laptop With A Real Pen, More Details TravelersToday Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s Yoga Book is meant to usher PCs into the next wave of mobile computing, but does it succeed?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
BYOD and enterprise mobility market to hit $73 bn in 2021 According to the research firm, mobile device management software will play a key role in the BYOD and Enterprise Mobility Market by 2021. BYOD and enterprise mobility market to hit $73 bn in 2021 plan-enterprise-mobility BYOD and enterprise mobility market is projected to grow from $35.10 billion in 2016 to $73.30 billion by 2021, latest report &amp;hellip; Alternative Networks (LON:AN) Broker Price Targets Recently stock market research analysts have changed their consensus ratings and price targets on shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
A Brief History of Mobile Computing The fascinating world of mobile computing has only been around since the 1990s. Since then, devices that have been developed for mobile &amp;hellip; Desktop Replacement Laptop Reviews, Analysis and Advices &amp;hellip; the digital freedom that is available with Wi-Fi hot spots and go-anywhere internet, there has been an increasing trend toward mobile computing. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Huawei Mate 9: Do You Really Want a 5.9-Inch Phablet? Huawei&amp;rsquo;s new smartphone has a massive 5.9in screen. But just how big do you really want your smartphone to be? Phablets &amp;ndash; smartphones with &amp;hellip; Enterprise Mobility is the Buzz for 2017 Mobile Device Management (MDM), mobile application management (MAM) and mobile information management (MIM) are combined to create a &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Commoditised MDM failing to address companies&amp;rsquo; actual mobility challenges, CSO Australia Many businesses are investing heavily in increasingly-commoditised mobile device management (MDM) tools that are failing to address the real &amp;hellip; BYOD &amp;amp; Enterprise Mobility Market Worth 73.30 Billion USD by 2021 According to a new market research report &amp;ldquo;BYOD &amp;amp; Enterprise Mobility Market by Software (MDM, Mobile Content Management), Security (Device &amp;hellip; BYOD &amp;amp; Enterprise Mobility Market Worth 73.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
New report examines the cloud-based ITSM market that will be worth 8.78 WhaTech The cloud-based ITSM solutions are witnessing the rising demand due to widespread adoption of BYOD policies and increasing mobile workforce, &amp;hellip; Hong Kong - Privacy Commissioner Issues New Guidance On BYOD. In August 2016 the Hong Kong Privacy Commissioner for Personal Data issued guidance for employers who operate a Bring Your Own Device &amp;hellip; Earnings Action: Earnings Per Share for Novatel Wireless Inc (MIFI) MoneyMakingArticles It operates in the wireless communications industry in two product categories: M2M Products and Solutions, and Mobile Computing Solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
How to implement mobility management for your workplace When selecting a mobility management solution that best suits your company&amp;rsquo;s individual needs, it should have mobile device management, app &amp;hellip; Uber partners SabRentKaro to offer rental smartphones to its driver ETtech.com &amp;hellip; its driver partners with smartphones on rent or a rent2own (R2O) basis, as part of the cab-hailing platform&amp;rsquo;s bring your own device (BYOD) scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Nov 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-11-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Are Drones Destined to Be Just Another Survey Tool? The BYOD Mapping Kit is a new offering from the GeoCue Group, which provides geospatial solutions to help accelerate, automate and better &amp;hellip; Jamf Wraps Up Successful Seventh Annual User Conference With deep roots and experience in education, Jamf highlighted its progress in education, noting it is the mobile device management (MDM) solution for &amp;hellip; Two Fire Departments Find Xplore Rugged Tablets Best Suited to Improve Yahoo Finance Community Volunteer Fire Department (CVFD) in Texas has also chosen to standardize part of its mobile computing technology solution on Xplore &amp;hellip; Into the cloud: The rise of the flexible workplace Companies using mobile and in particular BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) strategies are still putting in place effective mobile working practices to &amp;hellip; BitTitan Appoints New Vice President of Product During his tenure in the mobile computing division at Motorola Solutions, acquired by Zebra Technologies in 2014, Kirstein focused on overall &amp;hellip; IGEL Named a Rising Star by Experton Group &amp;hellip; management in which the previously separate functionalities of mobile device management (MDM) and desktop management merge together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Griffith Uni to outsource end user computing Application virtualisation is only available for students, not staff, and there is no mobile device management for the 1650 iOS and Android devices in &amp;hellip; VAI Pours Business Intelligence Into Midmarket ERP Cloud and mobile computing initiatives&amp;ndash;along with analytics&amp;ndash;are tools that are transforming business overall, including the ERP software business &amp;hellip; Managed Print Services Cloud, Virtualization and Mobile Computing: Why they CIOReview At its core, mobile computing requires an infrastructure that is adaptable, flexible, and ubiquitous while traditional implementations are rigid, inflexible &amp;hellip; Mobile Mentor undertakes BYOD deployment to 33000 ABS Census field officers Mobile systems provider Mobile Mentor is claiming one of the largest bring-your-own-device (BYOD) deployments in Austrlian history with the rollout of &amp;hellip; Wearable Electronics Market : North America is the largest market, followed openPR (press release) Wearable Electronics are minute electronics devices worn by the consumer which enable wireless networking and mobile computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Episode 2 Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) - Free Podcasts help your organization save money and increase employee satisfaction &amp;hellip; BYOD sign icon. Bring your own device symbol. symbol.&amp;rdquo; designed by blankstock at the lowest price on Fotolia.com. Browse &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Analysts Update Their Price Target On MobileIron, Inc. (NASDAQ:MOBL) Its platform enables areas of functionality, including Mobile Device Management, Mobile Application Management, Mobile Content Management and &amp;hellip; Uppgroup Inc Announces New Mobile Friendly Website for Showcasing Pro Desks Digital Journal Pro Desks, a mobile computing division of Uppgroup Inc., have been providing vehicle and office laptop computer mounting solutions for years. Managing enterprise mobility within your organisation The increase of bring your own devices (BYOD) in organisations, effective strategies should be put in place to ensure that employees understand &amp;hellip; The Barcode Warehouse goes live on ServiceNow asset lifecycle management&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; and together with mobile device management tools enhances visibility over mobile assets enabling their customers to lower the cost of operating a &amp;hellip; Outstanding Analyst Ratings For Alternative Networks (LON:AN) Numerous investment brokers have in recent days changed their price targets on shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
IBM - Top ten reasons you don&amp;rsquo;t need Mobile Device Management (MDM) IT companies make it easier to centralize the management and security of mobile devices of various shapes and sizes, that is no excuse for &amp;hellip; Short Interest Alert: Could DECISIONPOINT SYSTEMS INCORPORATED Post News The Firm sells and installs mobile computing and wireless systems that are used both within a company&amp;rsquo;s facilities in conjunction with wireless &amp;hellip; Survey: Firms Struggle With BYOD Overspending New research from Syntonic and Information Solutions Group finds that use of bring-your-own-device strategies are common, but that organizations &amp;hellip; Mobile Application Market 2014-2020 Shares, Trend and Growth Report &amp;hellip; such as Bring-Your-Own-Device (BYOD) and deployment of MDM (mobile device management) solutions, rapid development of gaming industry, &amp;hellip; Global Military Mobile Computing Systems Market To Exhibit 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Broker Price Targets: Mandalay Digital Group, Inc (APPS) The O&amp;amp;O business is an advertiser solution for carrier and OEM inventory consisting of services, such as Ignite, a mobile device management platform &amp;hellip; CIO Jury: 10 out of 12 tech leaders trust Samsung despite Galaxy Note7 TechRepublic &amp;ldquo;The key driver for enterprise acceptance should be focused on control through mobile device management (MDM) tools on the market,&amp;rdquo; Spears said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
CEO Satya Nadella Seeks to Change Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Image &amp;hellip; Inc. GOOGL 1.42 % on emerging technologies, including mobile computing and web search. When Mr. Nadella took over as CEO in February 2014, &amp;hellip; CEO Satya Nadella Seeks to Change Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Image&amp;ndash;Update &amp;hellip; on a strategic path that trailed rivals such as Apple Inc. and Alphabet Inc. on emerging technologies, including mobile computing and web search.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Microsoft: What&amp;rsquo;s The Mobile Device Strategy? I believe that Microsoft is emphasizing HoloLens because it&amp;rsquo;s a form of mobile computing device that is differentiated from its competitors. Nadella&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; Alternative Networks (LON:AN) Analyst Target Prices Recently stock market analysts have updated their consensus ratings on shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN). The newest analyst ratings which &amp;hellip; Biometrics Becoming The Future For Smartphone Industry &amp;hellip; transactions on their mobile handsets, and also that the BYOD (bring your own device) culture seems to be spreading on the enterprise side as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
New Microsoft patent suggests connecting two Surfaces via the keyboard MSPoweruser For example, mobile computing devices such as tablets and phones may employ a slate form factor. A connection device may be used to provide a &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
To BYOD or not to BYOD: factors affecting academic acceptance of student To BYOD or not to BYOD: factors affecting academic acceptance of student &amp;hellip; Stavert, B. (2013) Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) in Schools: 2013 &amp;hellip; Enterprise Mobility Management: Mobile Device Management&amp;rsquo;s Expansion to This white paper uncovers key considerations for a unified mobile enterprise policy. Discover how to gain visibility into every device entering your &amp;hellip; iBusiness Magazine Features SyncDog SentinelSecure Mobile Container Consumer Electronics Net &amp;hellip; and details how IT administrators can leverage SentinelSecure to secure enterprise data from vulnerabilities originating in mobile computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
TechTarget: Citrix XenDesktop features make it a fit for BYOD, graphics TechTarget: Citrix XenDesktop Features Make It a Fit for BYOD, Graphics &amp;hellip; Tagged: xendesktop desktop virtualization bring your own device. To read &amp;hellip; Survey Points to BYOD Management Opportunities for Partners &amp;hellip; for using a personal device at work, and more than three-quarters are not familiar with their employer&amp;rsquo;s mobile-device management (MDM) software. Survey Points to BYOD Management Opportunities for Partners A new survey focused on bring your own device (BYOD) reveals that seven in 10 employees use a personal device for work, while only 39 percent of &amp;hellip; Tata Teleservices launches enterprise device management product Tata Teleservices has launched an enterprise mobile device management (MDM) product which will provide secure access to official data and emails &amp;hellip; Midwich distributing BenQ InstaShow for BYOD screen-sharing Midwich has announced it is the exclusive UK and Ireland distributor for the new BenQ InstaShow a no-software device that allows multiple &amp;hellip; Today in Apple history: PowerBook 100 series is a smash hit &amp;hellip; PowerBook 100 series proved to be something of an unexpected hit for Apple (which had been burned by its previous attempt at mobile computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Tata Teleservices launches MDM solution in Indian market &amp;hellip; and emails over mobile devices, easy data recovery in case of theft and loss of device, thereby aiding the BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) scenario. Tata Tele launches mobile device management tool in India The MDM service ensures a secure access to official data and emails over mobile devices, data recovery in case of theft/ lost device scenarios, &amp;hellip; Report explores the global bring your own device(BYOD) sales market WhaTech Global Bring Your Own Device(BYOD) Sales Industry 2016 Market Research Report provide the details about Industry Overview and analysis about &amp;hellip; Mobile Applications Leak Device, Location Data The report calls on companies to enforce stricter mobile device management programs to protect users and network assets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Chongqing Yubei District fuels mass entrepreneurship and innovation through Design and Reuse (press release) It is also a vital part of the area&amp;rsquo;s mobile computing technology platform, one of the eight key platforms at XTB. ARM has announced multiple strategic &amp;hellip; Construction company Arrow International opts for IBM mobile device Computerworld New Zealand &amp;hellip; company Arrow International opts for IBM mobile device management &amp;hellip; company Arrow International opts for IBM mobile device management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
VMware Inc.: VMware Introduces New Workspace ONE Innovations and Showcases The Wall Street Transcript Lufthansa selected VMware Workspace ONE with AirWatch for compliance enforcement, mobile device management, and application management &amp;hellip; Nokia May Re-enter with D1C Tablet There was a time when Nokia was the leader of the market. People were not able to think beyond Nokia while purchasing a new device. However &amp;hellip; AT&amp;amp;T and Skycure Team Up to Help Secure Millions of Mobile Devices To help mitigate these risks, organizations have traditionally deployed Mobile Device Management (MDM) and Enterprise Mobility Management &amp;hellip; Pokmon GO or No Go?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) Security Market Forecast from 2016 to 2020 The BYOD policy allows employees to use their personal devices to gain access to corporate networks. It helps organizations to enhance operational &amp;hellip; ManageEngine announces new ServiceDesk Plus MSP and support for Android for IT News Africa The company also announced it supports Android for Work in the latest version of its mobile device management (MDM) solution, Mobile Device &amp;hellip; Fog computing: Balancing the best of local processing with the cloud The mobile computing era changed the expectations we place on our personal computers and internet services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
ManageEngine Announces New ServiceDesk Plus MSP; Support for Android for Zawya (press release) &amp;hellip; also announced it supports Android for Work in the latest version of its mobile device management (MDM) solution, Mobile Device Manager Plus. Acer presents Switch Alpha 12, liquid-cooled two-in-one notebook &amp;hellip; product line and adds new features such as a fanless design, an ultra-thin attachable keyboard and the latest in mobile computing performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Renovotec launches new Mobile Device Management Service Renovotec, the UK&amp;rsquo;s fastest growing rugged hardware provider for warehousing and distribution, manufacturing and retail companies is launching a &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Enterprise mobility market in Australia to hit $5.5bn by 2020 with mobile Enterprise Apps Tech Perhaps confusingly, Telsyte uses MDM (mobile device management) as an umbrella term which can be interchangeable with EMM (enterprise &amp;hellip; Global Bring Your Own Device(BYOD) Market Demand, Growth, Opportunities and NewsMaker (press release) Wise Guy Reports is part of the Wise Guy Consultants Pvt. Ltd. and offers premium progressive statistical surveying, market research reports, analysis &amp;hellip; EMM: Balancing Mobility and Security in Healthcare Implementing BYOD policies in healthcare organizations allows employees to use personal devices securely at work place and access the data to &amp;hellip; EMM: Balancing Mobility and Security in Healthcare This is where MDM comes into picture; most of the industries are adopting mobile device management (MDM) solutions that are now productized &amp;hellip; IBM Earnings Preview: Marginal Decline In Revenues As Shift To Cloud Nasdaq Comprising 38% of the total, these imperatives include revenue generated from Analytics, the Cloud, Mobile Computing, Security and Social Media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Research delivers insight into the bring your own device (BYOD) industry WhaTech This report studies Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) in Global market, focuses on price, sales, revenue of each type in Global. This report also focuses &amp;hellip; Facebook Brings Workplace App for All Facebook has become a vital platform for many people across the globe. It is touching millions of lives across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Is mobile device management the next big partner opportunity? Mobile device management (MDM) could be the next big opportunity for the Australian channel, according to the latest research by analyst firm,Telsyte &amp;hellip; Aussie Enterprise Mobility Market Poised For Growth According to Telsyte estimates, almost half of all organisations in Australia now have enterprise-grade mobile device management, which it expects to &amp;hellip; MobileIron: Turnaround Play With Some Risk Since the company&amp;rsquo;s inception in 2007, mobile device management (MDM) and EMM has become a hot and increasingly crowded space as large &amp;hellip; BYOD at Abbotsford Traditional Middle School (ATMS) to establish a Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) program that &amp;hellip; 5 affordable MDM options for small businesses Small and medium sized businesses have embraced BYOD faster than large corporations, but research suggests SMBs aren&amp;rsquo;t taking security &amp;hellip; Be mindful of these 3 tech changes for recruiting success Traditional media isn&amp;rsquo;t dead, but you need to be sure your talent pool is comfortable with the brave new world of mobile computing and knows how &amp;hellip; Three Ways a Knox Device Enrollment Program Streamlines Mobile Security Samsung Business Insights (blog) Do you have a Help Desk just to make sure employees can get their devices set up and enrolled in your mobile device management (MDM) program?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
More virtualisation to come in mature Australian market Cloud computing, virtualisation, mobile computing and a growing number of business-critical applications and data is increasing datacentre &amp;hellip; More virtualisation to come in mature Australian market He said he had rarely seen demand for mobile virtualisation in Australia, with most enterprises choosing to use mobile device management &amp;hellip; Samsung Urges Users Not to Use Galaxy Note 7 It is now more than one month and it is really unfortunate for Samsung that they have still not solved the issues of Galaxy Note 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) eCOA - Instrument Validation Methodology, New EIN News (press release) However, with the advent of web-based instruments and bring-your-own-device (BYOD), validation becomes more challenging: due to an increasingly &amp;hellip; Military Mobile Computing Systems Market Trends, Price, Demand and Growth Technavio Announces the Publication of its Research Report Global Unmanned Aerial Vehicle (UAV) Landing Gear Market 2016-2020 Technavio &amp;hellip; Create a single Windows 10 management console with SCCM and Intune SCCM brings inventory management to the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Huawei Mate 9 May Have Kirin 960 Chip and 6GB RAM Huawei has managed to create its own space into the smartphone market. They didn&amp;rsquo;t take time to show their strength and now they are ready to &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
DURABOOK Rugged Computers for Oil and Gas Industry at PBIOS 2016 With an optional detachable keyboard, the R11 becomes a 2-in-1 that can work as a laptop and offer a high-performance, complete mobile computing &amp;hellip; Top 9 Vendors in the Global Military Mobile Computing Systems Market from Intelligent Aerospace LONDON&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash; Technavio has announced the top nine leading vendors in their recent global military mobile computing systems &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Wacom&amp;rsquo;s MobileStudio Pro 13 And 16 Tablets Are Targeted At Professional Tech Times These will purportedly include lightweight mobile computing technology that will come with a reinvented stylus and powerful creative tools. For those &amp;hellip; Sprint Decides to Offer New Exchange Program for Samsung Galaxy Note 7 Mobile Computing Today Sprint is not interested to take any chances as they have decided to keep the safety of their users ahead of their business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
App Security in a Mobile World This is often accomplished through some form of mobile device management solution or mobile app management service. Surrounding the app. SSA brings method to the mobile madness &amp;hellip; NetPlus, an expense management tool; and AirWatch, a mobile device management solution that handles configuration and security settings. Tata Teleservices enters Mobile Device Management space, differentiates on ETCIO.com Bring Your Own Device or BYOD has become a rule rather than exception in most corporate environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Employees sometimes frustrated with document management: Report Only 39 percent of IT managers report that their document management system possesses mobile device management (MDM) capabilities, which the &amp;hellip; Alternative Networks (LON:AN) Analyst Target Changes A number of investment brokers have recently updated their price targets on shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN). According to the latest broker &amp;hellip; Google Launches Pixel and Pixel XL with Premium Features You may already remember that a few days ago we were discussing about Google Pixel and Google Pixel XL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Google Pixel and Google Pixel XL Specifications Leaked Hours before the Mobile Computing Today A few days ago we told you how Google is planning to bring their upcoming gadgets. Company brought Google Nexus model few years ago and later &amp;hellip; BlackBerry Ltd. Finally Stops Making Smartphones &amp;hellip; BlackBerry Messenger, an enterprise messaging app; QNX, an embedded OS for connected cars; and mobile device management solution vendor &amp;hellip; Smart Lock Market Projected To Reach $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Trojanised apps in legitimate app stores new DressCode threat Trend says the cure is to use mobile device management (MDM) software to secure the handset and an encrypted VPN for all company &amp;hellip; Sony Xperia XZ Sale Officially Starts in the USA Sony Xperia models are undoubtedly attractive. They have classy appearance and many models by this brand show that we can surely trust them for &amp;hellip; Accusoft: Businesses Lack Proper Document Management Training According to Accusoft&amp;rsquo;s findings, 74 percent of organizations have implemented some form of a bring-your-own-device (BYOD) policy, but only half of &amp;hellip; WidePoint (WYY) Awarded U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Upgrades And Downgrades For Mandalay Digital Group, Inc (APPS) The O&amp;amp;O business is an advertiser solution for carrier and OEM inventory consisting of services, such as Ignite, a mobile device management platform &amp;hellip; New report: Market insights on global military mobile computing systems WhaTech Military mobile computing systems include electronic systems and devices that are used for the transmission of real-time data and reception of video, &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Oct 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-10-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Qualcomm Planning To Buy NXP Semiconductors For $30 Billion: How The Tech Times Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s plans of expanding its business beyond mobile computing is evident in the recent release of Snapdragon 600E and 410E SoCs, which &amp;hellip; Mobile Identity Management Top Market Drivers and Forecast from Technavio &amp;hellip; the market size, the study considers paid mobile identity applications for mobile application management (MAM) and mobile device management &amp;hellip; 3 Ways Cloud Computing Can Help Businesses Overcome BYOD Challenges BYOD or &amp;lsquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rsquo; is a strategy on the rise, with almost 74 percent of startups motivating employees to follow this path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Vivify Health Awarded Patent for Extending Remote Care to Your Television Their bring-your-own device (BYOD) solutions produce proven outcomes such as reducing readmissions by 65 percent, improving ROI by 144 percent &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Enable Remote Access with Cost-Efficient BYOD programs Access with Cost-Efficient BYOD programs Lynda Raley 0. Featured &amp;hellip; Group Mobile Announces Addition of Cat S60: The Revolutionary, PR Web (press release) &amp;hellip; Caterpillars&amp;rsquo;s S60 thermal imaging smartphone positions Group Mobile as the single destination for any and all rugged mobile computing devices. Security: It might not be the outside world that&amp;rsquo;s the largest threat to TechRepublic BYOD, mobile devices, cloud computing, and remote work policies are changing the face of business faster than IT departments can keep up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Research delivers insight into the mobile application development platform WhaTech Commenting on the report, an analyst from Technavios team said: Increased adoption of BYOD and BYOA will be a key trend for market growth. Eight of the best mobile device management tools: Best MDM software for IT ComputerworldUK Mobile device management software aims to secure, manage, and monitor any employee mobile device. With more and more business operations &amp;hellip; How to Enrich your MDM Tool to Purge BYOD Challenges BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) has combined corporate and personal world, allowing employees to use their devices for both personal and corporate &amp;hellip; Leveraging the Cloud Platform to Boost Mobile Productivity By effectively utilizing the cloud platform, enterprises are trying to implement the bring your own device (BYOD) to stoke mobility and inject a &amp;hellip; How to Enrich your MDM Tool to Purge BYOD Challenges Stop kicking tires on BYOD management program, there are many vendors in the market who provide mobile device management suitesAirWatch, &amp;hellip; Spok Survey Finds Increase in Mobility Planning but Gaps in Critical Yahoo Finance More than 550 healthcare organizations responded to this year&amp;rsquo;s questions about mobile strategy documentation, bring your own device (BYOD) &amp;hellip; Finncap reiterated Alternative Networks (LON:AN) as &amp;lsquo;Corporate&amp;rsquo; With 420 PT According to a report issued to investors by Finncap on Tuesday, shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN) had their rating reiterated by analysts to &amp;hellip; Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s OCZ Division Announces OCZ TL100 SATA SSD For Value-Oriented The SSD Review &amp;hellip; 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Global Carcinoembryonic Antigen (CEA) Market is Expected to Reach USD Mobile Computing Today The latest market report published by Credence Research, Inc. Global Carcinoembryonic Antigen (CEA) Market Growth, Share, Opportunities, &amp;hellip; Global Aramid Paper Market for Communication Equipment, Honeycomb Core and Mobile Computing Today According to a new market report published by Credence Research Aramid Paper Market Growth, Future Prospects, Competitive Analysis, and &amp;hellip; Toughbook Celebrates 20 Years of Mobile Computing Leadership In addition to Panasonic&amp;rsquo;s ongoing investments in mobile computing R&amp;amp;D, Toughbook mobile computer users also benefit from Panasonic&amp;rsquo;s extensive &amp;hellip; Panasonic Toughbook celebrates 20th anniversary of its rugged mobile Virtual-Strategy Magazine Bracknell, UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Global Mobile Phone Protective Cases Market is Expected to Reach US$ Mobile Computing Today According to a new market report published by Credence Research Mobile Phone Protective Cases Market Growth, Future Prospects, Competitive &amp;hellip; Panasonic Toughbook celebrates 20th anniversary of its rugged mobile RealWire (press release) Bracknell, UK. 26 September 2016 - Panasonic Toughbook is celebrating 20 years of the legendary rugged mobile computing brand on September &amp;hellip; How to implement an effective BYOD policy Companies have accepted that BYOD is a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Apple Brings iOS10.0.2 Update with Bug Fix and More Apple is now rolling out the update of their operating system iOS10 to remove many bug fixes. This new update is iOS10.0.2 and it helps to remove the &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Webinar: Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) eCOA Instrument Validation with the advent of web-based instruments and bring-your-own-device (BYOD), validation becomes more challenging. Can BYOD sharpen the line between work and home? Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) schemes whether officially or unofficially &amp;hellip; Many businesses believe that the BYOD revolution has improved the &amp;hellip; Stock Chart to Observe: Does Digital Turbine Inc Have Any Gas After Forming Chester News The company&amp;rsquo;s product include DT Ignite&amp;trade;, a mobile device management solution with targeted app distribution capabilities, DT IQ&amp;trade;, &amp;hellip; Is Mobileiron Inc a Buy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
New Security Features Make iOS 10 a More Reliable Business Platform In addition, a variety of other changes made iOS 9 friendlier for mobile-device management systems to provision and administer, Rege said. Analysis of GoPro Hero5 Black Camera GoPro just launched their new Hero5 Black tiny camera and they have added numerous functions to make the device useful. GoPro Hero5 has some &amp;hellip; BYOD and social media biggest internal security threats to organisations Employees bringing their devices to work (35 per cent), and accessing their social media accounts (43 per cent) are considered the biggest risks to &amp;hellip; How to Mitigate BYOD Risks and Challenges Consumerization or implementation of BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) programs facilitate employees with the freedom to access and use enterprise &amp;hellip; Stock Update (NASDAQ:MIFI): Here&amp;rsquo;s Why Novatel Wireless Inc Shares Are Up Smarter Analyst The company operates in two product categories: M2M Products &amp;amp; Solutions; and Mobile Computing Solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Metatron, Inc. (OTC Pink: MRNJ) Growth from Cannabis, Apps and Minyanville.com One company that stands to benefit from the projected growth in mobile computing and &amp;ldquo;freemium&amp;rdquo; apps is Metatron Inc. (OTC Pink: MRNJ). Metatron &amp;hellip; Deutsche Bank Reiterates Hold Rating for Fairchild Semiconductor Intl (FCS) The Business &amp;rsquo;s segments include Mobile, Computing, Consumer and Communication (MCCC); Power Conversion, Industrial and Automotive (PCIA), &amp;hellip; BlackBerry, Zimperium Combine Mobile Threat Protection Offerings; Dave ExecutiveBiz (blog) Zimperium combined its zIPS mobile threat management technology with BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s BES12 mobile device management software and Good &amp;hellip; Fairchild Semiconductor Intl (FCS) Posts Earnings Results, Meets Petro Global News 24 The Organization &amp;rsquo;s segments include Mobile, Computing, Consumer and Communication (MCCC); Power Conversion, Industrial and Automotive &amp;hellip; UEM is poised to revolutionize Windows desktop management VMware added support for Windows 10 mobile device management (MDM) in AirWatch, a part of Workspace One, in 2015, and in the intervening 12 &amp;hellip; BYOD could be losing its shine but is COPE ready to take its place?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Privacy Commissioner addresses privacy compliance and best JD Supra (press release) &amp;hellip; of Banks (the HKAB Guidelines), the trend towards Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) has come to the attention of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Privacy Commissioner. Global Specialty Milk Formula Market by Distribution Channel is Expected to Mobile Computing Today According to a new market report published by Credence Research Specialty Milk Formula Market Growth, Future Prospects, Competitive Analysis, &amp;hellip; Global Trientine Hydrochloride Market for Epoxy Curing and Wilson&amp;rsquo;s Disease Mobile Computing Today According to a new market report published by Credence Research Trientine Hydrochloride Market Growth, Future Prospects, Competitive Analysis, &amp;hellip; Global Audiology Devices Market is Expected to Reach USD 12715.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Global Mobile Device Management (MDM) Market Report 2016-2020 - Device Yahoo Finance Mobility is adopted across industries based on their needs and usage. One of the prime reasons is the rapid adoption of mobile devices at high &amp;hellip; Big data, mobile apps fuel surge in fintech venture funding Fueled by trends in mobile computing and big data, funding for venture-backed startups in financial technology has risen sharply in recent years, &amp;hellip; Global Mobile Wallet Market to Expand at a CAGR of 38.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Your school&amp;rsquo;s endpoint security: Solving the BYOD conundrum Everyone uses a smartphone. It&amp;rsquo;s a BYOD (bring your own device) world. Your students, their parents, your teachers, your staff and guests. Most of &amp;hellip; Your school&amp;rsquo;s endpoint security: Solving the BYOD conundrum For instance VMWare&amp;rsquo;s AirWatch mobile device management solution provides a flexible model for asset management, policy enforcement and &amp;hellip; DT Research Delivers Rugged Tablets Purpose-Built for Industry With Lower Yahoo Sports SAN JOSE, CA&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - September 19, 2016) - DT Research, the leading designer and manufacturer of purpose-built computing solutions for &amp;hellip; APPrise Mobile Raises $1 Million Seed Round &amp;hellip; to have its own proprietary branded app on the public app stores or as part of a mobile device management (MDM) or enterprise solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
finnCap announced Alternative Networks PLC (LON:AN), upholding its stock Breaking Finance News It also offers mobile device management solutions. Receive News &amp;amp; Ratings Via Email - Enter your email address below to receive a concise daily &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Microsoft includes Google Drive and Facebook photos in Outlook.com and iTWire &amp;hellip; and Azure Rights Management - for user identity and access management, mobile device management, and file and data protection capabilities. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
How To Fix Your Business BYOD Challenges With The Cloud BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) adoption has been on a growth spiral for several years now. According to a Tech Pro Research study, nearly 74% of &amp;hellip; Fairchild Semiconductor International (FCS) Receives Anayst Rating The Companys segments include Mobile, Computing, Consumer and Communication (MCCC); Power Conversion, Industrial and Automotive (PCIA), &amp;hellip; Research report explores the WLAN market growth, demand, overview and WhaTech &amp;hellip; anywhere are prompting organizations to adopt policies such as bring your own device (BYOD) and corporate-owned, personally enabled (COPE).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
IBM to offer cloud based mobile security services in India IBM MaaS360 helps enterprises simplify mobile device management by providing the tools needed to monitor and manage these devices. With more &amp;hellip; Battle for Network Control Plays Out in Channel Andr Kindness, an industry analyst with Forrester, observes that all these deals were driven mainly by the rise of mobile computing. But at this &amp;hellip; Global Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) Market Insights, Competitor Analysis, EIN News (press release) BYOD or Bring your own device refers to allowing the employees to bring &amp;hellip; The report for Global Bring Your Own Device Market of Market Research &amp;hellip; IBM to offer mobile security as a service in India IBM MaaS360 helps businesses simplify mobile device management by providing the tools needed to monitor and manage mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
IT Departments on the Hot Seat for BYOD, Mobility Policies As companies and their employees use more and more new technologies and devices, they continue to place IT departments on the hook for them. Viewpoint: How can you control company assets on employee&amp;rsquo;s devices? Bring Your Own Device (BYOD for short) is a term given to devices such as cell phones, iPads and computers which are owned by employees and &amp;hellip; Why the worst mobile security risks just won&amp;rsquo;t go away A lot of people are addressing this through good old-fashioned ActiveSync with Exchange, some newer [mobile device management] systems and &amp;hellip; Why video streaming to mobile devices is changing the way we watch the RCR Wireless News &amp;hellip; on monitoring and analyzing emerging trends, technologies and market behavior in mobile computing and wireless data communications devices, &amp;hellip; IBM Expands Global Footprint for Mobile Security and Management via the PR Newswire (press release) IBM MaaS360 helps clients simplify mobile device management by providing the tools needed to monitor and manage mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
VXL Software&amp;rsquo;s Fusion EMM to cut the cost of mobility management &amp;hellip; has today released Fusion EMM (enterprise mobility management), the company&amp;rsquo;s latest product offering mobile device management for Android &amp;hellip; Keeper Password Manager Available on Continuum for Windows 10 Phone Users &amp;hellip; CEO and Co-Founder of Keeper Security, Inc. &amp;ldquo;As mobile computing continues to converge into mobile apps, Continuum is a formidable solution for &amp;hellip; Qualcomm (QCOM): IoT and Consumer Drones to Boost Growth Qualcomm is also widening its presence in adjacent spaces, including automotive, networking, mobile computing and IoT which bodes well for &amp;hellip; MobileGuard Enables Federal Agencies to Easily Comply with SMS Logging and Yahoo Sports MobileGuard integrates with the major mobile device management (MDM) solutions, making provisioning efficient in large deployments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Panasonic unveils world-first fully rugged detachable laptop The laptop is suitable for field workers that need a highly mobile computing solution and the ability to capture large amounts of data. It is purpose-built &amp;hellip; Here&amp;rsquo;s How Getmii Is Solving Your Need By Reaching Out To Thousands Near Techstory He specializes in mobile computing, app development, web development, platform architecture, cloud infrastructure, automation, m2m and &amp;hellip; Whatsapp to Bring Low-light Selfie and Photo Doodling Features This year we have seen a lot of updates in Whatsapp as they have added numerous features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Harbourvest Partners Lowers stake in Mobileiron Inc (MOBL) The Company&amp;rsquo;s platform enables four areas of functionality which include Mobile Device Management (MDM) Mobile Application Management (MAM) &amp;hellip; Cisco leads growing WLAN market on the back of rising internet traffic Rising internet penetration and higher adoption of mobile computing devices are driving the deployment of WLAN solutions globally, caused by the &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
The Evolution of Industrial Automation in the Food and Beverage Industry Hard benefits long have provided the financial justification for plant automation projects. As information technology plays a larger role, food companies &amp;hellip; Apple Watch 2 Shows the Future of Smartwatches The market of smartwatches is increasing with every passing day. Apple recently brought their new Watch and many users around the world will &amp;hellip; Is Your Mobile Enterprise Subject to Law Enforcement Scrutiny?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Businesses can no longer ignore cyber security For instance, many organisations have overwhelmingly embraced the Bring -Your-Own-Device trend (BYOD) without factoring in the risks. BYOD is &amp;hellip; Dac Systems and Nintex offer workflow on the go! &amp;hellip; the ability to create custom-branded apps without writing code, easily deploy those apps through e-mail or mobile device management solutions, &amp;hellip; The Role of Data Analytics in Predictive Policing The exponential escalation of mobile computing and analytics has given officers intelligence on the go and greatly improved their chances of being in &amp;hellip; Webinar: Mining Journal Cyber Security Forum Thursday, October 6, 10am Mining Journal (subscription) Advances in big data, mobile computing and the internet of things have created many exciting operations technology (OT) opportunities for miners, EY &amp;hellip; Microsoft Working on an All-In-One Surface Machine The Commercial suite comes with various features such as Kiosk Mode: mobile-device management using products like Microsoft Intune; support for &amp;hellip; Solution to Files Not Showing in External Hard Drive Issue As you know, the external hard drive refers to a portable storage device which can be connected to a computer via a USB interface, Firewire or SATA &amp;hellip; New innovation hub officially opened at college &amp;hellip; and equipment such as touch screen desktops, hybrid laptop/tablet machines and mobile computing equipment from Japan&amp;rsquo;s Fujitsu company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
The Future of the Man Cave I&amp;rsquo;m talking about your car becoming a mobile computing platform that&amp;rsquo;s connected to everything around you via the Internet with all the same great &amp;hellip; World Patent Marketing Success Team Announces EyeInvent, A Software PR Web (press release) &amp;ldquo;This industry is multi-faceted and one of the fastest growing with new ideas such as the cloud and mobile computing.&amp;rdquo; Keeping an inventory is &amp;hellip; Guardian Mortgage Protects Customers and Maintains Trusted Reputation by Yahoo Finance ZixCorp offers industry-leading email encryption, a unique email data loss prevention (DLP) solution, and an innovative bring your own device (BYOD) &amp;hellip; Did Google really lose US$10b in the Motorola Mobility deal?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Experton Vendor Benchmark 2016 names Matrix42 as a leader in digital CSO Australia Experton also places Matrix42 as a leader in the mobile device management (MDM) solutions and enterprise mobility management (EMM) solutions &amp;hellip; 50 years of Star Trek inspires innovations in mobile computers, speech IPWatchdog.com &amp;hellip; and on which colored sheets could be displayed as the computer interface was a cheap option for creating a believable mobile computing platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Softbank Acquires ARM In One Of The Biggest Tech Deals Of The Year According to tech market analysts, one of the reasons why SoftBank decides to acquire ARM was because of its dominance in the mobile computing &amp;hellip; Scalable App Management with Workspace ONE from BYOD to strictly managed &amp;hellip; other features, it addresses the app management challenge that many companies face, especially in the context of Bring-Your-Own-Device (BYOD).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Crafting a mobile security and BYOD policy Recently, Enterprise Innovation hosted a CIO-level roundtable, supported by Singtel and Checkpoint, which aimed at sharing knowledge of IT security &amp;hellip; SoftBank completes $31 billion acquisition of ARM &amp;hellip; and Samsung, and ARM-designed chips dominate mobile computing in phones and tablets. 15 billion ARM-designed chips shipped last year alone, &amp;hellip; Discussing Android OS in the Enterprise With Zebra Technologies Does mobile computing and IoT come into play?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Digital Turbine Inc (NASDAQ:APPS) target price increased to $2 as announced Breaking Finance News The O&amp;amp;O business is an advertiser solution for carrier and OEM inventory consisting of services, such as Ignite, a mobile device management platform &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Prismetric advocates mobile apps for boosting BYOD culture, and how to deal WhaTech Mobile app development experts from the leading IT firm Prismetric talks about the importance of mobile apps to steer Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) &amp;hellip; Global Mobile Device Management Market 2016 Competitive Analysis, The QY Market research study, titled Worldwide Mobile Device Management Market 2016, presents critical information and factual data about the &amp;hellip; Prismetric advocates mobile apps for boosting BYOD culture, and how to deal WhaTech Lastly, a mobile device management approach must be at place to impose high-level control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
The ability to analyse live streams of mobile and sensor data is no longer The Register But the advent of mobile computing and the Internet of Things (IoT) means business now needs to monitor streams of incoming data generated by &amp;hellip; Mobile security risks abound: Here&amp;rsquo;s what you should be focusing on &amp;hellip; are worried about risks from mobile computing, with half saying they expect to experience more security breaches through those mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Sep 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
VMworld 2016 Day Three: End User Computing AirWatch Provides mobile device management and BYO including Windows 10. Identity Management Provides SSO, two factor authentication, &amp;hellip; VDI vs VDI 2.0: From total failure to comeback kid In fact, 46 per cent of IT professionals surveyed expect to see companies expand their BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) policies in 2016. But the tools &amp;hellip; Worth Watching Stocks Roundup: CyrusOne Inc (NASDAQ:CONE), Chicago Bridge &amp;amp; NYSE Journal (press release) &amp;hellip; enterprise dangers of employing the bring your own device (BYOD) model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
VMware just made some things easier for you to manage your endpoints The company is one of a handful of virtual desktop infrastructure leaders, but mobile computing is the next frontier that VMware will look to expand its &amp;hellip; Bring Your Own Device Risks in New Executive Report combat BYOD risks in the workplace. DALLAS (August 31, 2016) Global &amp;hellip; VMware Urges Partners to Pursue Public Cloud Education He said partners likely already offer PC management tools and mobile device management tools, but previously those services were separate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Sony May Show Xperia X Compact and Xperia XR in IFA 2016 Event We have not seen many models by Sony this year. They are now active after some time and some reports are claiming that company is gearing up to &amp;hellip; Apple may Release iPhone 7 on September 7th So finally the launch date has arrived and Bill Graham Civic Auditorium is the place from where the market will see the next prime model by Apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
TechnologyBring Your Own Device? Make Sure to Cover Your Security and Workforce Management WF_0916_legal Bring your own device has become the norm in the workplace. While many employers now allow BYOD in one form or another, &amp;hellip; TechnologyBring Your Own Device? Make Sure to Cover Your Security and Workforce Management &amp;hellip; by requiring employees who wish to use their own device to present their phones at the front-end for the installation of mobile device management, &amp;hellip; Global Pressure Sensors Market To Cross The US$ 10 Bn Mark By 2023  Mobile Computing Today According to a new market research report published by Credence ResearchPressure Sensors Market (Technology Piezoresistive, Electromagnetic &amp;hellip; WoundRounds Launches New Mobile App for Wound Management Diamond states, &amp;ldquo;The WoundRounds app works with the facility&amp;rsquo;s mobile device management (MDM) tools and meets strict security requirements to &amp;hellip; Sacred Heart College in Lower Hutt lets students use cellphones only at The Dominion Post The rule was simple no phones in class unless permission had been granted to use it as part of the school&amp;rsquo;s bring your own device (BYOD) policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Verizon- Unlocked-Works w/ BYOD Plans works with StraightTalk, ATT, Tmobile, MetroPCS And others. Top 3 collaboration trends for SMEs The rapid growth of mobile devices continue to redefine communication and productivity in the workplace resulting in exponential increase of BYOD &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Agencies making push for identity authentication changes The pilot will start with Apple iOS devices and use VMware&amp;rsquo;s AirWatch for its mobile device management. We were more interested in making sure the &amp;hellip; SECURED moves IoT and BYOD security to the network As to why, TechRepublic&amp;rsquo;s Brandon Vigliarolo offers several reasons in his post Pokemon Go: is it a BYOD security nightmare? As Vigliarolo&amp;rsquo;s title &amp;hellip; Enterprise mobility management poses many challenges &amp;hellip; Isizwe, focused on the challenges encountered by organisations when implementing EMM and mobile device management (MDM) strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
iPhone 6 and iPhone 6S Plus Gadgets Facing New Touch Disease A major manufacturing issue has started bothering some iPhone users. The second birthday of iPhone 6 and iPhone 6S Plus is approaching fast and &amp;hellip; The Wrap: Airlines adapting IFE offerings to meet changing consumer demands &amp;hellip; the industry as &amp;lsquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rsquo; (BYOD) are shaping airlines&amp;rsquo; IFE strategies now and impacting how they will look in the future, added the &amp;hellip; Health IT Pros Cooncerned About Mobile Security Threats &amp;ldquo;I was under the impression if hospital IT workers made the appropriate investments in mobile device management solutions to enforce security &amp;hellip; Survey: 8 in 10 Hospitals Concerned About Mobile Cyberattacks For the study Spyglass, a healthcare market intelligence firm focused on mobile computing, surveyed more than 100 members of the healthcare &amp;hellip; End-of-life AnnouncementParallels Mobile Device Management Management and re-focusing engineering and developmental resources on &amp;hellip; Windows 10 Build 14393.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Choosing the Right EMM Solution Provider As EMM technology evolves from the traditional mobile device management, they offer various functions and new features that enable firms to be &amp;hellip; Improving the safety of mobile technology One of the biggest issues is managing &amp;lsquo;bring your own device&amp;rsquo; (BYOD). Public sector work is increasingly mobile, so it isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual for work to be &amp;hellip; Xplore Sets Industry Record for 20 Years of Rugged Tablets &amp;ldquo;In a tech culture where new mobile computing devices enter the market on a frequent cadence, and a one-to-two year rip-and-replace model is &amp;hellip; Summer&amp;rsquo;s out for school: Parents&amp;rsquo; guide for first day At the high school this year, We&amp;rsquo;re expanding our BYOD (Bring your own device) pilot that we had with 9th grade last year for 9-12th grade, Luizzi &amp;hellip; ARBOR to Exhibit at InnoTrans 2016 in Berlin Germany &amp;hellip; computing to communication in healthcare, transportation, industrial automation, mobile computing, digital signage, retail, intelligent building and &amp;hellip; Microsoft Intune Features &amp;lsquo;Day Zero&amp;rsquo; Support for Android Nougat No matter when Android Nougat devices start showing up in the workplace, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Intune cloud-based mobile device management (MDM) and &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
For Hospitals, Mobile Devices Are a Blessing and a Curse &amp;ldquo;Despite increased investments in mobile device management solutions and secure text messaging solutions, cybercriminals have become more &amp;hellip; Managing MACS in the BYOD Environment Managing Macs in the BYOD Environment provides insight into managing Mac devices in your customer&amp;rsquo;s workplaces, and highlights N-central &amp;hellip; HP Inc. Touts Elite X3 As A &amp;lsquo;Device That&amp;rsquo;s Every Device,&amp;rsquo; Enabling Partners CRN The phablet is compatible with customers&amp;rsquo; existing mobile device management solutions and Windows environment, making it easier for teams to &amp;hellip; Why Huawei G9 Plus Can be a Good Choice Huawei is constantly growing into the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Fairchild Semiconductor International (FCS) Shares are Up 0.18% The Companys segments include Mobile, Computing, Consumer and Communication (MCCC); Power Conversion, Industrial and Automotive (PCIA), &amp;hellip; MVNO Monday: a guide to the week&amp;rsquo;s virtual operator developments &amp;hellip; Credo switched to Verizon for all of its new customer activations, except for those subscribers utilising the &amp;lsquo;bring your own device&amp;rsquo; (BYOD) scheme. Microsoft is about to fix your Surface Pro 3&amp;rsquo;s poor battery life Microsoft has provided an update on the major Surface Pro 3 battery flaw which has plagued some users, and the company has confirmed that a patch &amp;hellip; 10 biggest moments in computing history There have been huge advancements in computing technologies since the early 1900s, when calculators and typewriters were &amp;lsquo;new-fangled&amp;rsquo; &amp;hellip; More IoT devices mean states must get smarter about management panel &amp;hellip; IT administrator for Nebraska&amp;rsquo;s Office of the Chief Information Officer, noted that her state doesn&amp;rsquo;t currently use a mobile device management system, &amp;hellip; How Gartner&amp;rsquo;s tech trends will affect retailers &amp;hellip; computing, mobile computing, the Internet of Things and cloud computing in a common, connected framework of endpoints and supporting services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 18:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Galaxy C9 May Be the Next Galaxy C Series Model by Samsung Samsung brought two Galaxy C series models this year. It is not a long time when company brought Galaxy C7 into the market. However company is &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Revenue Update on Fairchild Semiconductor Intl Inc(NASDAQ:FCS) The Company&amp;rsquo;s segments include Mobile Computing Consumer and Communication (MCCC); Power Conversion Industrial and Automotive (PCIA) &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
NVIDIA Disputes Intel Benchmark Claims in Machine Learning Advantage Opportunities in this area could offset the slumping sales of personal computers, resulting in part from the rise of virtualization and mobile computing. Stanford&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Security Course Helps Professionals Protect Data Stanford&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Security Course Helps Professionals Protect Data Mobile devices have evolved from novelty to necessity. Smartphones and tablets &amp;hellip; Workspace-as-a-service market sees growth The growing enterprise mobility and developing bring-your-own-device (BYOD) trend are the key factors projected to drive the global WAAS market, &amp;hellip; Built-in mobile security features put power in users&amp;rsquo; hands Mobile devices are taking over the IT landscape, making Mobile Device Management (MDM) more important now than ever before; and at the top of &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Tableau 10: more data sources, even easier visualisations Tableau 10 also includes support for the Airwatch and MobileIron mobile device management systems to help protect data. Improvements aimed at &amp;hellip; Learn details of the global BYOD market 2016 capacity, production, cost, WhaTech Global BYOD Market 2016 BlueBox, IBM, Google, Cisco Systems, HP, Citrix Systems, IPASS, Apple, AirWatch, ForeScout Technologies these major &amp;hellip; New South Wales Justice Dept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Monk Law Office has Launched a New Website for 2016 &amp;hellip; new website has an updated look and feel and the technology behind the website ushers it into the new age of computing, mobile computing that is. Cyber adAPT supports ELITE mobile security partners Mobile device management and security firm Cyber adAPT has launched its ELITE channel programme for strategic consultants, system integrators &amp;hellip; BYOD Security: Uncovering the Threats of Free Wi-Fi and Hotspots The line between personal and corporate mobility is frequently blurred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Introduction to Cloud Based Mobile Device Management platform that provides over-the-air centralized management, secure BYOD &amp;hellip; Global Biological Safety Cabinets Market To Reach Worth USD267.2 Mn By Mobile Computing Today According to the latest report published by Credence Research, Inc. Biological Safety Cabinets Market (Class I, Class II type A1, type A2, type B1, &amp;hellip; Power play: How Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s Pascal laptops let you game for longer Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s new Pascal GPUs have made their way into at least 10 gorgeous (and incredibly powerful) gaming laptops, with more to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Vendors to rely on partnerships for managed security as BYOD drives ChannelLife NZ According to the forecast, the increasing adoption of bring your own device (BYOD) policies amongst enterprises plays a key role in augmenting the &amp;hellip; Zebra Technologies Corporation (ZBRA) Shares are Up 16.18% It operates through two segments: Enterprise, which consists of its mobile computing, data capture and WLAN products, and Legacy Zebra, which &amp;hellip; Enterprise mobile security tools may not protect BYOD For employees, bring-your-own-device workplace policies can increase efficiency and improve remote work capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Top Certifications for Mobile App Developers &amp;hellip; in mobile app development, software engineering, computer science or mobile computing stand a greater chance of being hired by an employer. Gmail will Now Warn Users of Unsafe Links Google is now making Gmail safer as they are now offering a new security update for their users. This new update will be available for web users as &amp;hellip; Pokmon GO Exposes Risks of Bring-Your-Own-Device (BYOD) Policies In particular, the app poses issues for businesses with bring-your-own-device (BYOD) policies, in which employees use their own computers, &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Wearable Cloud Could be Powerful Form of Mobile Computing Researchers at the University of Alabama at Birmingham are exploring the concept of a wearable personal cloud a fully functioning, yet compact &amp;hellip; Whatsapp Update Adds Voicemail and Call Back Feature Whatsapp is frequently bringing new updates for their users. These updates have helped them to stay on the top and it is a known fact that it is the &amp;hellip; 9 Enterprise Mobility Management Tools For IT Pros Mobile device management (MDM) offers a way to manage devices, such as mobile phones and tablets, over their lifecycles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
CMO&amp;rsquo;s top 10 martech stories for the week - 11 August This is back by mobile device management platforms to ensure governance and security. There&amp;rsquo;s also a cross-database feature to help people unite &amp;hellip; Apple may unveil iPhone 7 on September 7th Next month is going to be an exciting month for Apple fans. Some latest reports are saying that company is looking to unveil their next iPhone model &amp;hellip; The ultimate cloud accessory researchers develop wearable personal cloud The wearable system is billed as the ultimate smart device, bringing all mobile computing solutions together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
MediaTek MT8176 ends up in the ZenPad Rangoon Chang, General Manager of Mobile Computing Business Unit 2 at ASUS said that the outfit worked closely with MediaTek and he thinks the &amp;hellip; LG V20 May Have a Dual-Camera Setup A few days ago we told you that LG is getting ready to launch their new LG V20 in September. Now another report has arrived that company is looking &amp;hellip; Apple, iPhone courting corporate customers as consumer sales drop The company&amp;rsquo;s iPhones and iPads have become the preferred mobile computing devices for corporations, as industries from insurers to airlines aim &amp;hellip; New MediaTek MT8176 SoC selected to power ASUS ZenPad tablet &amp;hellip; ASUS ZenPad 3S 10 our best-ever ASUS ZenPad for entertainment, said Rangoon Chang, General Manager of Mobile Computing Business Unit &amp;hellip; Tableau 10 set to launch as Tableau invests big in R&amp;amp;D Deploying Tableau Mobile across an organization should also be more secure, with mobile device management platforms for IT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Increased acceptance of data analytics driving market growth A rise in the adoption of BYOD policy is an ongoing trend in the global market &amp;hellip; BYOD policies allow employees to access organisational data and &amp;hellip; Global Angioedema Treatment Market To Reach Worth USD 1658.0 Mn By 2022: Mobile Computing Today According to the latest report published by Credence Research, Inc. Angioedema Treatment Market Growth, Future Prospects and Competitive &amp;hellip; New MediaTek SoC Selected to Power ASUS ZenPad Tablet &amp;hellip; cutting-edge technology to consumers around the world,&amp;rdquo; said Rangoon Chang, General Manager of Mobile Computing Business Unit 2 at ASUS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Aug 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-08-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Mobile Computing news from @topmobilenews.
Online Orders of HP Elite X3 May Start From Next Month in The USA HP is now ready to expand their premium smartphone series. Their upcoming model is HP Elite X3 and it may belong to the premium category after &amp;hellip; Essential Components Governing an Enterprise Mobility Strategy The corporate mobility policy must outline the significance of integrating a mobile device management (MDM) service. The success of a mobile &amp;hellip; MobileIron (MOBL) Shares are Up 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>