<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CloudFeed</title>
    <link>//cloudfeed.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CloudFeed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>CloudFeed. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//cloudfeed.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bobsguide.com/guide/news/2016/Dec/5/how-data-analytics-and-visualisation-revolutionized-aml/&#39;&gt;How data analytics and visualisation revolutionized AML&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data solutions that support evolving business and regulatory requirements by maintaining an ecosystem of large datasets will become invaluable &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bangkokpost.com/tech/world-updates/1151473/big-data-helped-trump-even-after-he-scorned-it&#39;&gt;Big data helped Trump even after he scorned it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON - Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign &amp;ndash; but those techniques might well have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://guardian.ng/technology/big-data-helped-trump-even-after-he-scorned-it/&#39;&gt;Big data helped Trump even after he scorned it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign  but those techniques might well have propelled him to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.republic-news.org/news/43894/&#39;&gt;Big Data Pharmaceutical Advertising Market Research Report Now Available at&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Republic of East Vancouver Research Corridor has published a new research study titled Big Data Pharmaceutical Advertising Market  Growth, Share, Opportunities, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.claimsjournal.com/news/national/2016/12/05/275316.htm&#39;&gt;Why Analyzing Unstructured Data Benefits Every Claims Manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re just catching on to the fact that big data is shaking up the insurance industry in a big way, you&amp;rsquo;re a bit behind the curve. Across all industries &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itproportal.com/news/insurers-still-slow-to-pick-up-big-data/&#39;&gt;Insurers still slow to pick up Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insurance companies are mostly reluctant to use big data analytics to rate their customers&amp;rsquo; driving habits, but the trend is slowly picking up pace, a new &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/05/glow-color-genomics-big-data/&#39;&gt;How These Startups Plan to Use Big Data to Transform Women&amp;rsquo;s Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; is revolutionizing industries like technology and advertising, there is one field that is noticeably lagging when it comes to Big Data: health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/sinequa-ekimetrics-deliver-value-data-130000912.html&#39;&gt;Sinequa and Ekimetrics to Deliver Value from Data with Cognitive Search and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Sports &amp;ldquo;Sinequa&amp;rsquo;s platform is empowering our data scientists to create an end-to-end approach of big data. Teaming up with Sinequa is enabling us to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/12/05/above-the-trend-line-your-industry-rumor-central-for-1252016/&#39;&gt;Above the Trend Line  Your Industry Rumor Central for 12/5/2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week set a record in terms of pure volume of big data industry buzz! There&amp;rsquo;s so much happening, but we&amp;rsquo;re committed to keeping pace for our &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financialexpress.com/economy/big-data-can-drive-india-from-cashful-to-cashless/464972/&#39;&gt;Big Data can drive India from &amp;lsquo;Cashful&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Cashless&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digitization and big data analytics will make it more difficult to get away with under-declaration of wealth and income, help increase tax revenues and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://infocus.emc.com/william_schmarzo/big-data-analytics-customer-holiday-experience/&#39;&gt;Big Data Driving Customers&amp;rsquo; Holiday Experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hadoop is Just the Beginning: Realizing value from big data requires &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bio-itworld.com/2016/12/5/groundbreaking-big-data-platform-can-improve-the-quality-of-cancer-care.aspx&#39;&gt;Groundbreaking Big Data Platform Can Improve The Quality Of Cancer Care&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December 5, 2016 | I believe it is now possible to end cancer, said Vice President Joe Biden at a recent American Society of Clinical Oncology &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/nimble-storage-exhibit-predictive-flash-platform-2016-gartner-data-center-infrastructure-nyse-nmbl-2180628.htm&#39;&gt;Nimble Storage to Exhibit Predictive Flash Platform at 2016 Gartner Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) Learn how innovations around storage, big data and cloud are fundamentally disrupting datacenter infrastructure as companies embark on delivering &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/MapR-Announces-Speaker-Lineup-for-Big-Data-Everywhere-Bay-Area-and-Los-Angeles-20161205&#39;&gt;MapR Announces Speaker Lineup for Big Data Everywhere Bay Area and Los&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World Big data experts, including presenters from American Express, Qualcomm and SAP, will share their knowledge and discuss best practices related to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.insurancenetworking.com/blogs/data-analytics/assembling-a-top-notch-insurance-analytics-team-37778-1.html&#39;&gt;Assembling a Top-Notch Insurance Analytics Team&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But creating the kind of organization-wide change made possible through big data is easier said than done. A critical component of bringing about &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.sdcexec.com/article/12271216/taming-big-data-in-the-iot&#39;&gt;Taming Big Data in the IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though the story of the Internet of Things (IoT) and Big Data involves sensors and terabytes instead of wild animals, the overall theme is largely the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://technical.ly/brooklyn/2016/12/05/big-data-dark-side-art/&#39;&gt;These Brooklyn artists are exploring the dark side of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tega Brain and Surya Mattu, the creators of Unfit Bits, reveal how algorithms can reinforce social inequalities in an upcoming exhibit tour. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/05/cloud-creating-data-gravity-look-future-cloud-disruption-reinvent/&#39;&gt;Is the cloud creating its own &amp;lsquo;data gravity&amp;rsquo;? A look at the future of the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SiliconANGLE (blog) Cask.co, as Gray described it, is an open-source big data company really focused around big data applications. And a big part of leveraging that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://resources.cio.com/ccd/assets/125228/detail&#39;&gt;IBM Drives Deployment Choices with Latest Hadoop Distribution Release&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IBM is one of four vendors that continue to offer a commercial distribution of Apache Hadoop. In July, the company released its latest version of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchdatacenter.techtarget.com/feature/Challenges-of-IoT-include-big-data-data-analysis-for-enterprise&#39;&gt;Challenges of IoT include big data, data analysis for enterprise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Implementing big data and IoT is difficult for enterprise IT teams due to &amp;hellip; of data via technologies, such as Hadoop and distributed storage systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/05/clouds-role-making-big-data-accessible-reinvent/&#39;&gt;What is the cloud&amp;rsquo;s role in making big data accessible? - #reInvent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the many advantages of cloud regarding data management and analysis have received deep examination, one of the advantages brought to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2016/12/05/895246/0/en/Cloudera-Continues-Global-Momentum-in-Financial-Services-Sector.html&#39;&gt;Cloudera Continues Global Momentum in Financial Services Sector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This big data analytics platform, powered by Apache Hadoop, helps us gain customer insights to increase safety, make risk and underwriting more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/mapr-announces-speaker-lineup-for-big-data-everywhere-bay-area-and-los-angeles-2180700.htm&#39;&gt;MapR Announces Speaker Lineup for Big Data Everywhere Bay Area and Los&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) Big data experts, including presenters from American Express, Qualcomm and SAP, &amp;hellip; Big Data Everywhere (BDE) Los Angeles will be held on Thursday, &amp;hellip; development in open source technologies including Spark and Hadoop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://cornandsoybeandigest.com/technology/proagrica-s-adapt-plug-harnesses-power-big-data-ag-industry&#39;&gt;Proagrica&amp;rsquo;s ADAPT plug-in harnesses power of Big Data for ag industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Editor&amp;rsquo;s Note: Briefing Room is where we run press releases from companies unedited, for your use. Proagrica have announced that they have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.hotelsmag.com/Industry/News/Details/70340&#39;&gt;Labor costs, branding, big data&amp;rsquo;s impact on EMEA: Aethos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aethos Consulting Group Managing Directors Chris Mumford and Thomas Mielke, both based in London, share commentary regarding labor costs, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.healthdatamanagement.com/news/how-big-data-is-improving-breast-cancer-prediction-rates&#39;&gt;How big data is improving breast cancer prediction rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better predicting health outcomes through the analysis of big data are the goals of healthcare analytics. Now, a new method for differentiating between &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Cloud Computing News from @cloudfeednet - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Cloud Computing news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#34;&gt;@cloudfeednet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iothub.com.au/news/aws-launches-two-new-iot-products-443542&#39;&gt;Greengrass and Snowball Edge give more capabilities to edge devices.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services has announced AWS Greengrass and AWS Snowball Edge, two products designed to simplify the interaction between IoT &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thebitbag.com/crackdown-3-release-date-official-launch-before-xbox-one-scorpio-backwards-compatibility-on-first-two-games-hinted/208591&#39;&gt;Crackdown 3 Release Date: Official Launch Before Xbox One Scorpio!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bitbag This release window predates that of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s upcoming console, &amp;lsquo;Project &amp;hellip; This was achieved by tapping into Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure Cloud computing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Amazon-Web-Services-launches-Financial-Services-Competency-to-certify-fintech-firms-432920&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services launches Financial Services Competency to certify&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes The Amazon Web Services (AWS) has announced the launch of its Financial Services Competency, which is designed to recognize the partners of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.indiainfoline.com/article/news-top-story/tata-communications-launches-a-new-brand-campaign-in-india-116120500075_1.html&#39;&gt;Tata Communications launches a new brand campaign in India&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; IZO now connects to all of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest clouds of Amazon Web Services, Microsoft Azure, Office 365, Google Cloud Platform and Salesforce. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://opensource.com/article/16/12/openstack-news-december-5&#39;&gt;Powering NFV, Kubernetes integration, and more OpenStack news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in keeping track of what is happening in the open source cloud? Opensource.com is your source for news in OpenStack, the open &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mis-asia.com/tech/cloud-computing/aws-looks-to-take-the-drudge-work-out-of-data-analysis/&#39;&gt;AWS looks to take the drudge work out of data analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LAS VEGAS &amp;ndash; Amazon Web Services is looking to make it easier, and more efficient, for enterprises to analyze their data in the cloud. &amp;ldquo;Eighty percent &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2016/microsoft-hpe-enterprise-corporate-cloud-hybrid-saas-partnership-joint-venture/&#39;&gt;HPE, Microsoft Combine Forces For Cloud Adoption&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure platform will combine with HPE infrastructure and services, reports said, to introduce a new program of service offerings for joint &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://account.windowsazure.com/PremiumOffer/Index?offer=MS-AZR-0110P&amp;whr=azure.com&amp;l=tr-tr&amp;correlationId=4e9f8b00-d4d9-49e0-a0ac-fc578c19b078&#39;&gt;We can&amp;rsquo;t sign you in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;email address or phone number of the account you want to sign in with. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itechpost.com/articles/61759/20161205/echo-updates-hundreds-new-commands-amazon-take-back-smartspeaker-market.htm&#39;&gt;Echo Updates With Hundreds of New Commands: Amazon To Take Back&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;iTech Post One of his most recent public appearances, which was at the Amazon Web Services conference in Las Vegas, encompassed a long list of topics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizcommunity.com/Article/196/379/154787.html&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services unveils new intelligence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playing catch-up with rivals Google and Microsoft, Amazon Web Services announced the launch of three new artificial intelligence (AI) capabilities &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itweb.co.za/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=158085&#39;&gt;Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Alexa heads for the fast lane&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services (AWS) is making moves in the connected car space by putting its artificial intelligence (AI)-powered virtual assistant, Alexa, into &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.investopedia.com/news/amazon-ramps-cloud-position-rivals-emerge-amzn-msft/&#39;&gt;Amazon Ramps Up Cloud Position as Rivals Emerge (AMZN, MSFT)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services CEO Andy Jassy kicked off the event on Wednesday by discussing the big bets the e-commerce giant is making on &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techseen.com/2016/12/05/6-new-developments-aws-reinvent/&#39;&gt;6 new developments at AWS re:invent 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services&amp;rsquo; weeklong annual consumer and partner conference at Las Vegas came to an end last Friday. According to the company the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.infoworld.com/article/3147094/application-development/9-enterprise-tech-trends-for-2017-and-beyond.html&#39;&gt;9 enterprise tech trends for 2017 and beyond&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus, such cloud database-as-a-service offerings as Amazon Aurora and Google Cloud SQL make the scale-out problem moot. At the same time, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://github.com/kubernetes/kubernetes/issues/38098&#39;&gt;OpenStack Cinder: upon node failure kubernetes fails to relocate pods with&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenStack Cinder: upon node failure kubernetes fails to relocate pods with cinder volumes #38098. Open. suonto opened this Issue Dec 5, 2016  1 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.databasejournal.com/features/mssql/sql-server-in-azure-virtual-machines-performance-optimizations.html&#39;&gt;SQL Server in Azure Virtual Machines - Performance Optimizations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azure offers a wide variety of VM sizes and types. For their comprehensive, up-to-date listing, refer to Microsoft Azure documentation. A cursory &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/05/cloud-migrations-tech-trends/&#39;&gt;One Benefit of Cloud Migrations May Surprise You&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; businesses are supplementing or even replacing their own data centers with a cloud like Amazon Web Services is no longer a shock, or even news. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cloudpro.co.uk/cloud-essentials/public-cloud/6503/aws-adds-postgresql-compatibility-to-amazon-aurora&#39;&gt;AWS adds PostgreSQL compatibility to Amazon Aurora&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; databases like Oracle and Microsoft SQL Server,&amp;rdquo; said Raju Gulabani, Vice President, Databases, Analytics, and AI, Amazon Web Services. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2016/12/05/the-morning-download-salesforce-draws-step-closer-to-amazon-web-services-cloud/&#39;&gt;The Morning Download: Salesforce Draws Step Closer to Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wall Street Journal (blog) Good morning. Salesforce.com&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Amazon Web Services marks the first time that core Salesforce applications are available in a public &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.ft.com/content/bca4876c-b7c9-11e6-961e-a1acd97f622d&#39;&gt;Cloud computing titans battle for AI supremacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week, Amazon Web Services launched three new artificial intelligence services: one for image recognition, one for natural language &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.chesterindependent.com/2016/12/05/13f-activity-amazon-com-inc-com-amzn-market-valuation-rose-while-fisher-asset-management-llc-has-trimmed-its-position/&#39;&gt;13F Activity: Amazon Com INC Com (AMZN) Market Valuation Rose While Fisher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chester News The Firm has three divisions: North America, International and Amazon Web Services (AWS). The Company&amp;rsquo;s North America segment focuses on retail &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://techcrunch.com/2016/12/05/phenixp2p-helps-developers-add-real-time-video-to-their-apps/&#39;&gt;PhenixP2P helps developers add real-time video to their apps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you are watching the live video stream of a football game or any major event online, chances are that the stream usually isn&amp;rsquo;t really as live as &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/Kids-Charities-Take-Center-Ice-at-Barclays-Center-Marking-17th-Season-of-Commvaults-Hockey-Helping-Kids-Program-20161205&#39;&gt;Kid&amp;rsquo;s Charities Take Center Ice at Barclays Center, Marking 17th Season of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World Sponsors this year include: Microsoft, Microsoft Azure, Windows Server, ShopRite, RBA, SHI, NetApp, Arrow, Arrosoft Solutions and Harrington Search &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.senecaglobe.com/stocks-reaffirm-to-gain-attentions-amazon-com-nasdaqamzn-best-buy-nysebby/354605/&#39;&gt;Stocks Reaffirm To Gain Attentions- Amazon.com (NASDAQ:AMZN), Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seneca Globe Amazon.com, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) [Trend Analysis] tries to capture market sentiments, shares dropped -0.45% to $740.34. Amazon Web Services &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/connectria-delivers-hipaa-compliance-microsoft-150000392.html&#39;&gt;Connectria Delivers HIPAA Compliance For Microsoft Azure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the addition of Connectria&amp;rsquo;s HIPAA Compliance for Microsoft Azure, customers can choose the cloud environment and technology stack that&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2016/12/05/aws_to_blow_incumbents_out_the_water_in_blighty/&#39;&gt;AWS is coming for UK infrastructure suppliers&amp;rsquo; lunch  report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report noted that Microsoft Azure has &amp;ldquo;built momentum&amp;rdquo; over the past 18-24 months, with TechMarketView estimating it grew more than 60 per &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ciodive.com/news/salesforce-to-offer-core-services-on-aws-infrastructure/431623/&#39;&gt;Salesforce to offer core services on AWS infrastructure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services and Salesforce will expand their partnership to provide five new service integrations to help customers &amp;ldquo;simplify and expand &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://marketingland.com/ais-star-grows-brighter-marketing-new-announcements-amazon-facebook-emarsys-199848&#39;&gt;AI&amp;rsquo;s star grows brighter in marketing, with new announcements from Amazon,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketing Land We have thousands of people dedicated to AI in our business, Amazon Web Services CEO Andy Jassy told TechCrunch, validating the importance &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.baystreet.ca/viewarticle.aspx?id=450366&#39;&gt;Blog Coverage Amazon Web Services and Salesforce Take Their Relationship to&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Baystreet.ca LONDON, UK / ACCESSWIRE / December 5, 2016 / Active Wall St. blog coverage looks at the headline from Amazon.com Co. (NASDAQ: AMZN) and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.channelbuzz.ca/2016/12/cloud-vdi-vendor-workspot-to-offer-desktop-as-a-service-2-0-on-azure-19781/&#39;&gt;Cloud VDI vendor Workspot to offer Desktop as a Service 2.0 on Azure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, we believe Azure is more mature as a cloud now  and Microsoft is &amp;hellip; So we have only tightly coupled with Azure for this DaaS 2.0 offering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsfactor.com/story.xhtml?story_id=0110006KG509&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services Introduces New AI Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AWS (Amazon Web Services) introduced a handful of new artificial intelligence (AI) services at its re:Invent conference last week. Among the new &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161205006023/en/ZeroStack-Wraps-2016-10-Key-Milestones&#39;&gt;ZeroStack Wraps Up 2016 with 10 Key Milestones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ZeroStack is now the only company to offer bi-directional application portability across hypervisors, and to integrate with Amazon Web Services (AWS) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://hitinfrastructure.com/news/connectria-certifies-microsoft-azure-hosted-hipaa-compliance&#39;&gt;Connectria Certifies Microsoft Azure Hosted HIPAA Compliance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Connectria Hosting announced HIPAA compliant Microsoft Azure healthcare cloud deployment options so organizations can meet HIPAA regulations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thehostingnews.com/amazon-web-services-will-open-office-in-bahrain.html&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services Will Open Office in Bahrain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services or AWS is set to open a new office in Bahrain. The office will open on January 1, 2017 and will be found in Manama, the capital &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchitoperations.techtarget.com/news/450404159/QA-Former-Googlers-startup-nurtures-enterprise-Kubernetes&#39;&gt;Q&amp;amp;A: Former Googlers&amp;rsquo; startup nurtures enterprise Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;McLuckie: Just getting Kubernetes up and running on Amazon [Web Services] is hard. The way that installation works today is, it&amp;rsquo;s a relatively simple &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.rtinsights.com/recommendation-engine-microsoft-cognitive-services/&#39;&gt;Building a Better Recommendation Engine With a Cognitive API: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RTInsights (press release) (blog) Or at least that&amp;rsquo;s the idea. During a recent webinar, Fang Tu, a senior data scientist at Microsoft Azure Machine Learning, walked users through the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.informationweek.com/partner-perspectives/redhat/building-mysql-dbaas-on-openstack-and-ceph-clouds/a/d-id/1327638&#39;&gt;Building MySQL DBaaS on OpenStack And Ceph Clouds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For private clouds, architects who have selected OpenStack as the operating system for their software-defined data centers are increasingly asked to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.rcrwireless.com/20161205/telecom-software/nokia-looks-to-take-sting-out-of-vnf-management-tag2&#39;&gt;Nokia looks to take sting out of VNF management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nokia unveiled a templating system it said is based on ETSI NFV, TOSCA and OpenStack specs designed to simplify VNF management and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blogs.vmware.com/vcloud/2016/12/vmware-vcloud-air-recovery-service-glance.html&#39;&gt;VMware vCloud Air Recovery as a Service at a Glance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;multi-platform data protection solution that enables you to choose which workloads &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blogs.barrons.com/techtraderdaily/2016/12/05/citrix-mizuho-cheers-workspaces-catalysts-including-microsoft/&#39;&gt;Citrix: Mizuho Cheers &amp;lsquo;Workspaces&amp;rsquo; Catalysts, Including Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We think continued adoption of cloud technologies, especially Microsoft Azure, will take VMware&amp;rsquo;s back-end infrastructure out of the picture. As such &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcworld.com/article/3147389/cloud-computing/aws-wants-to-dominate-beyond-the-public-cloud-with-lambda-updates.html&#39;&gt;AWS wants to dominate beyond the public cloud with Lambda updates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services&amp;rsquo; big Re:Invent conference in Las Vegas brought a plethora of new features and upgrades to its cloud platform. But there was &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcworld.com/article/3147389/cloud-computing/aws-wants-to-dominate-beyond-the-public-cloud-with-lambda-updates.html&#39;&gt;AWS wants to dominate beyond the public cloud with Lambda updates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has its Azure Functions service, while Google Cloud Platform offers Google Cloud Functions. To comment on this article and other PCWorld &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mobihealthnews.com/content/sunovion-taps-empatica-phase-4-drug-trial-and-two-other-digital-health-projects-targeting&#39;&gt;Sunovion taps Empatica for Phase 4 drug trial &amp;ndash; and two other digital&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MobiHealthNews &amp;hellip; the Epilepsy Care Alliance have harnessed machine learning powered by Microsoft Azure to track patients&amp;rsquo; daily activities and detect when they are &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.accountingtoday.com/accounting-technology/news/xero-completes-transition-to-amazon-web-services-80044-1.html&#39;&gt;Xero Completes Transition to Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xero has moved 59 billion records onto Amazon Web Services, completing its transition to the platform. The move to AWS is part of Xero&amp;rsquo;s plan to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://redhatstackblog.redhat.com/2016/12/05/6-videos-on-how-to-install-red-hat-openstack-platform-and-cloudforms/&#39;&gt;6 videos on how to install Red Hat OpenStack Platform and CloudForms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Hat OpenStack Administration II (CL210) and Red Hat CloudForms &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/amazon-go-here-are-the-takeaways-business-tech-execs-need-to-know/&#39;&gt;Amazon Go: Here are the takeaways business tech execs need to know&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, Amazon will get a jump on brick-and-mortar competition, but rest assured that these technologies are going to be tied into Amazon Web Services &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.programmableweb.com/news/google-introduces-app-maker-app-development-tool-enterprises/brief/2016/12/05?qt-top_most_menu_other_directories=0&#39;&gt;Google Introduces App Maker, App Development Tool for Enterprises&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Developers can build a variety of Web and mobile applications with Google App Maker, applications that leverage Google cloud services and APIs &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thecerbatgem.com/2016/12/04/bank-of-america-corp-reiterates-buy-rating-for-amazon-com-inc-amzn.html&#39;&gt;Bank of America Corp. Reiterates Buy Rating for Amazon.com Inc. (AMZN)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com logo Amazon.com Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN)&amp;rsquo;s stock had its buy rating restated by equities researchers at Bank of America Corp. in a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://redmondmag.com/articles/2016/12/05/azure-active-directory-powershell-2.aspx&#39;&gt;Microsoft Goes Live with Azure Active Directory PowerShell 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft today announced that the Azure Active Directory PowerShell 2.0 module has reached the &amp;ldquo;general availability&amp;rdquo; (GA) milestone. The module &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3147385/cloud-computing/aws-wants-to-dominate-beyond-the-public-cloud-with-lambda-updates.html&#39;&gt;AWS wants to dominate beyond the public cloud with Lambda updates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has its Azure Functions service, while Google Cloud Platform offers Google Cloud Functions. To comment on this article and other CIO &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily IoT/Blockchain news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itwire.com/internet-of-things/76044-iot-eminently-hackable-%E2%80%93-900,000-routers-down-and-millions-vulnerable.html&#39;&gt;IoT eminently hackable  900000 routers down and millions vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hacked Internet of Things (IoT) devices are powering massive botnets and cybercriminals are offering DDoS attacks as a service. 900,000 XyXEL &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/iot-applied-in-retail-7-real-examples&#39;&gt;IoT Applied in Retail: 7 Real Examples&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many business have started hearing about Internet of Things. There are not too many cases of big retailers implementing pilots and incorporating &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.chinatechnews.com/2016/12/05/24550-chinas-huawei-to-build-rd-base-in-tokyo&#39;&gt;China&amp;rsquo;s Huawei To Build R&amp;amp;D Base In Tokyo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huawei plans to cooperate with Japanese enterprises to promote Internet of Things and 5G technologies. Huawei not only sees Japan as its target &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/machine-learning-will-scale-personalised-customer-interactions-flamingo/&#39;&gt;Machine learning will scale personalised customer interactions: Flamingo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much further down the track, Flamingo will play in the machine to machine interaction space, when humans rely on bots speaking to each other on &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.technologyreview.com/s/603015/security-experts-warn-congress-that-the-internet-of-things-could-kill-people/&#39;&gt;Security Experts Warn Congress That the Internet of Things Could Kill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MIT Technology Review A growing mass of poorly secured devices on the Internet of things represents a serious risk to life and property, and the government must intervene to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/national/2016/12/05/0301000000AEN20161205006000320.html&#39;&gt;Cyber attacks on gov&amp;rsquo;t agencies, ransomware programs to rise in 2017:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yonhap News The agency also said Internet of Things (IoT) devices will be also exposed to more ransomware programs as hackers are increasingly breaching &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Applications-open-for-South-East-Asias-first-blockchain-incubator-Satoshi-Studious-432824&#39;&gt;Applications open for South East Asias first blockchain incubator Satoshi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes Called Satoshi Studios, the incubator is backed by Amit Bharadwaj, the founder of Amaze Mining &amp;amp; Blockchain Research Ltd, which owns over 100 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.brecorder.com/market-data/stocks-a-bonds/0/110109/&#39;&gt;TMX says blockchain, fintech still a priority after executive exit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canada&amp;rsquo;s biggest stock exchange operator is committed to exploring new technologies such as blockchain despite the exit of its first chief digital officer &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mediafiledc.com/technology-fighting-facilitation-human-trafficking/&#39;&gt;Technology Fighting the Facilitation of Human Trafficking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aptly named Beacon of Hope is taking advantage of the Internet of Thingswhen everyday items are hooked up to the internetto allow victims &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizcommunity.com/Article/196/751/154756.html&#39;&gt;SAP comes on board as an official sponsor of the Blockchain Africa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bizcommunity.com SAP has done some exciting work with various blockchain technologies, including Ethereum and the bitcoin blockchain, and, having signed up as an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://eprretailnews.com/2016/12/05/overstock-com-to-help-rightholders-and-broker-dealers-successfully-participate-in-series-a-preferred-share-offering-7494858686/&#39;&gt;Overstock.com to help rightholders and broker-dealers successfully&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EPR Retail News (press release) SALT LAKE CITY, 2016-Dec-05  /EPR Retail News/  With the subscription deadline for participating in its historic blockchain share rights offering &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.fool.co.uk/investing/2016/12/05/3-stocks-that-turned-5000-into-113300/&#39;&gt;3 stocks that turned 5000 into 113300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And one company poised to benefit from the Internet of Things (IoT) revolution is Telit Communications. Despite revenue growth at Telit picking up &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.siliconrepublic.com/start-ups/gigliott-iot-drinks-dispenser-startup&#39;&gt;Start-up of the week: Gigliotti&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our start-up of the week is Gigliotti, an internet of things (IoT) company targeting the hospitality sector with its Smartdrinx system. Gigliotti started up &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.infoq.com/news/2016/12/amazon-alexa-update&#39;&gt;Amazon Adds Finer Granularity of Control to their Voice Recognition API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alexa is designed to be a developer API for companies looking to fine tune the growing market of &amp;ldquo;internet of things&amp;rdquo; (IOT) devices. A key issue with &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/lisks-max-kordek-touts-sidechain-flexibility-2017-1594856&#39;&gt;Blockchain: Lisk&amp;rsquo;s Max Kordek touts sidechain flexibility for 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lisk uses delegated proof of stake and introduces a new sidechain for every app built on the platform. Ian Allison. By Ian Allison. December 5, 2016 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prweb.com/releases/2016/12/prweb13895244.htm&#39;&gt;Picone Advisory Group Retained To Help Secure Funding For ELSE Nanosats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AstroCast is a network of nanosatellites that will provide global machine-to-machine (M2M) communication for businesses worldwide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digital.nyc/events/startup-talk-impact-blockchain-voting-w-ceo-founder-voatz&#39;&gt;Startup Talk: The Impact of Blockchain On Voting W/ CEO&amp;amp; Founder, Voatz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CEO and Founder ofVoatz,Nimit Sawhney. Voatz, based in Boston, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theinternetofthings.eu/vitality-agency-and-financial-incentives-need-pragmatic-cybernetics&#39;&gt;Vitality, agency, and financial incentives need a pragmatic cybernetics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forecast 2017: megatrends for the next year it became clear that there is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Illinois-DFPR-seeks-comment-on-Digital-Currency-Regulatory-Guidance-432987&#39;&gt;Illinois DFPR seeks comment on Digital Currency Regulatory Guidance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IDFPR release comes as it seeks to incorporate blockchain technology into the state&amp;rsquo;s official government operations. Last week, the IDFPR, along &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.globaltrademag.com/global-trade-daily/principles-securing-internet-things&#39;&gt;Principles For Securing The Internet Of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Department of Homeland Security (DHS) recently issued a set of Strategic Principles for Securing the Internet of Things (IoT), Version 1.0. These &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.siliconrepublic.com/enterprise/iot-devices-privacy-sweep&#39;&gt;MHC Tech Law: IoT devices under the regulatory microscope&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, the Global Privacy Enforcement Network (GPEN) published the results of its global privacy review of internet of things (IoT) devices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/12/05/govt-pledges-to-promote-and-increase-exports-of-rubber-gloves/&#39;&gt;Govt pledges to promote, increase exports of rubber gloves&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; want to look towards leveraging advanced technologies such as the Internet of Things and Industry 4.0, bridging automation and data connectivity, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theinternetofthings.eu/leo-sun-will-intels-new-hire-rejuvenate-its-internet-things-business%E2%80%A8&#39;&gt;Leo Sun: Will Intel&amp;rsquo;s New Hire Rejuvenate Its Internet of Things Business?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ofSoftbank&amp;rsquo;s chip designer ARM Holdings, as its senior VP and general &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://globenewswire.com/news-release/2016/12/05/894977/0/en/Nokia-showcases-5G-innovations-driving-next-era-of-communication.html&#39;&gt;Nokia showcases 5G innovations driving next era of communication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; the new opportunities created by IoT and increased machine-to-machine communications for smart cities, automated driving, connected healthcare, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/What-is-a-Blockchain-ICO-and-Why-It-Matters-433179&#39;&gt;What is a Blockchain ICO and Why It Matters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a new term. It stands for Initial Coin Offering. Blockchain projects issue their own scarce network tokens, in exchange for Ether (ETH); the scarce &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/alliance-between-prpl-foundation-iotsf-110000759.html&#39;&gt;Alliance between prpl Foundation and IoTSF puts &amp;lsquo;security by design&amp;rsquo; at the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Sports &amp;hellip; two influential not-for-profit organizations working to promote security and openness in the Internet of Things (IoT), today announced that they have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iottechnews.com/news/2016/dec/05/our-devices-may-be-talking-are-we-listening/&#39;&gt;Our devices may be talking  but are we listening?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things (IoT) isn&amp;rsquo;t something futuristic from a science fiction film, it is here and now  our &amp;lsquo;things&amp;rsquo; can connect with each other and affect &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://smarthighways.net/smart-cities-need-smart-public-transport-research/&#39;&gt;Smart cities need smart public transport  research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The machine-to-machine (M2M) and Internet of Things (IoT) market research provider, Berg Insight, has released a new report about the smart cities &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161205005121/en/Digital-Vikings-launching-blockchain-smart-contract-MVP-Platform&#39;&gt;Digital-Vikings launching blockchain smart contract MVP Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Digital-Vikings, a digital innovation company, announced today that it is launching a MVP version of a blockchain smart contract &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.the-blockchain.com/2016/12/05/blockchain-named-virgin-media-business-disruptor-10/&#39;&gt;Home News Blockchain  The World&amp;rsquo;s Most Popular Bitcoin Wallet  Named A&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain News Blockchain, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading provider of digital currency and distributed ledger software, has today been named in the inaugural Virgin Media &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coinspeaker.com/2016/12/05/illinois-department-of-financial-and-professional-regulation-launches-digital-currency-regulatory-guidance/&#39;&gt;Illinois Blockchain Initiative Aims at Creation Governance around&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coinspeaker Several Illinois agencies have teamed up to explore blockchain and the way how the technology can be integrated into government operations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pymnts.com/news/partnerships-acquisitions/2016/software-ag-buys-zementis-for-deep-learning-capabilities/&#39;&gt;Software AG Buys Zementis For Deep-Learning Capabilities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software AG sees machine learning and AI advances as the basis for the next iteration of Internet of Things applications, including self-driving cars, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/alliance-between-prpl-foundation-iotsf-puts-security-design-heart-embedded-computing-2180527.htm&#39;&gt;Alliance between prpl Foundation and IoTSF puts &amp;lsquo;security by design&amp;rsquo; at the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) The IoT Security Foundation (IoTSF) is a non-profit member association with a mission to help secure the Internet of Things in order to aid its adoption &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161205005009/en/Sysorex-Present-9th-Annual-LD-Micro-Conference&#39;&gt;Sysorex to Present at the 9th Annual LD Micro Conference on December 6,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) With an innovative approach to big data, analytics and the Internet of Things (IoT), we blend virtual data from software and networks with the huge &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lvb.com/article/20161205/LVB01/312019997/global-tech-firm-moves-rd-to-bethlehem&#39;&gt;Global tech firm moves R&amp;amp;D to Bethlehem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of Arkados&amp;rsquo; business plan is to make IoT technology and make it scalable from machine-to-machine communications to smart city &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/news/disruptors-like-blockchain-are-re-writing-the-business-rule-book/&#39;&gt;Disruptors like Blockchain are Re-writing the Business Rule Book&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain, the developer of cryptocurrency and blockchain software which recently issued its ten millionth bitcoin wallet, has just been named among &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Regulators-should-not-fear-use-of-smart-contracts-and-blockchain--Euroclear-433213&#39;&gt;Regulators should not fear use of smart contracts and blockchain Euroclear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Titled Blockchain settlement: Regulation, innovation and application, the paper said that central securities depositories (CSDs) would have an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.yourohiovalley.com/story/33874443/formal-launch-of-ma-blockchain-the-decentralized-global-public-welfare-system&#39;&gt;Formal Launch of MA Blockchain, the Decentralized Global Public Welfare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; On December 3rd a press conference to introduce M.A Blockchain, the decentralized public welfare system, was held in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/New-Qorvo%C2%AE-E-Book-Series-Explains-the-Internet-of-Things-IoT-433637&#39;&gt;New Qorvo E-Book Series Explains the Internet of Things IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet of Things For Dummies and Internet of Things Applications For Dummies will help technical and nontechnical professionals understand the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.geeky-gadgets.com/internet-of-things-light-provides-notifications-05-12-2016/&#39;&gt;Internet Of Things Light Provides Notifications About Your Wordpress Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Geeky Gadgets WordPress bloggers or users that would like to be notified when users make social interactions with their website might be interested in a new Internet &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/rti-presents-iso-26262-approval-automotive-software-components-complimentary-webinar-2180582.htm&#39;&gt;RTI Presents ISO 26262 Approval of Automotive Software Components&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) SUNNYVALE, CA&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - Dec 5, 2016) - Real-Time Innovations (RTI), the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) connectivity platform company, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.automationworld.com/preparing-growth-us-manufacturing&#39;&gt;Preparing for Growth in US Manufacturing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many companies are looking at new technologies like 3D vision, robotics and the Industrial Internet of Things to usher plants into the next era of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iottechnews.com/news/2016/dec/05/software-ag-acquires-zementis-ai-and-deep-learning-expertise/&#39;&gt;Software AG acquires Zementis for AI and deep learning expertise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software AG considers the current machine learning and AI advances as the basis for the next generation of Internet of Things (IoT) applications such &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/390892/Machine-to-Machine-M2M-Market-in-China-is-Propelled-to-grow-at-a-CAGR-of-26-20-over-2015-2019.html&#39;&gt;Machine to Machine (M2M) Market in China is Propelled to grow at a CAGR of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;openPR (press release) Albany, NY, Dec 05: M2M is a technology that enables machines to interconnect and securely interact over a network. M2M communications help &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/05/m2m-wireless-services-market-is-expected-to-witness-a-steady-growth-by-2024/&#39;&gt;M2M Wireless Services Market is Expected to Witness a Steady Growth by 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Machine to machine (M2M) wireless communication has helped the computer networks to expand beyond one-to-one system communication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/laurashin/2016/12/05/the-top-10-blockchain-takeaways-from-europes-trustech-conference/&#39;&gt;The Top 10 Blockchain Takeaways From Europe&amp;rsquo;s Trustech Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain brings time stamping to big data, which is much cheaper than previous versions of time stamping big data. I&amp;rsquo;m surprised how many &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.the-blockchain.com/2016/12/05/malta-stock-exchange-forms-new-blockchain-committee-and-think-tank/&#39;&gt;Malta Stock Exchange Forms New Blockchain Committee and Think Tank&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Malta Stock Exchange has formed a Blockchain Committee which includes members of the Exchange&amp;rsquo;s Board, its Chairman and Chief Executive &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/japans-central-bank-staff-running-blockchain-trials/&#39;&gt;Japan&amp;rsquo;s Central Bank Staff are Running Blockchain Trials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bank of Japan  the county&amp;rsquo;s central bank  is test-driving blockchain, or distributed ledger technology to understand the innovation, according to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-4001506/Cyber-criminals-mass-murderers-hacking-day-smart-devices-warn-security-experts.html&#39;&gt;Cyber criminals could become mass murderers by hacking into every day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daily Mail &amp;lsquo;The Internet of Things is bringing computerisation and connectivity to many tens of millions of devices worldwide. &amp;lsquo;We are connecting cars, drones, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.infoworld.com/article/3147099/internet-of-things/5-disruptive-technologies-to-track-in-2017.html&#39;&gt;5 disruptive technologies to track in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sign up now and get FREE access to hundreds of Insider articles, guides, reviews, interviews, blogs, and other premium content. Learn more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/sensify-security-joins-the-industrial-internet-consortium-to-strengthen-cyber-defense-within-industrial-iot-operations-300372507.html&#39;&gt;Sensify Security joins the Industrial Internet Consortium to strengthen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire (press release) &amp;hellip; member-supported organization that promotes the accelerated growth of the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT). Sensify Security is in the forefront of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/290274/how-many-devices-can-you-measure.html&#39;&gt;How Many Devices Can You Measure?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketers have accepted the idea that they can no longer measure attribution one device at a time. But what should they do? Drawbridge fields &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.qorvo.com/newsroom/news/2016/new-qorvo-ebook-series-explains-the-internet-of-things-iot&#39;&gt;New Qorvo E-Book Series Explains the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;applications and security. GREENSBORO, NC  December 5, 2016  Qorvo &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/digi-international-launches-lte-advanced-140000608.html&#39;&gt;Digi International Launches LTE-Advanced Router that Delivers the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Sports 5, 2016 /CNW/ &amp;ndash; Digi International, (NASDAQ: DGII, www.digi.com), a leading global provider of machine-to-machine (M2M) and Internet of Things &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://host.madison.com/business/investment/markets-and-stocks/will-intel-s-new-hire-rejuvenate-its-internet-of-things/article_fdfa79a1-fa7a-5d73-bca0-ee132c7459fa.html&#39;&gt;Will Intel&amp;rsquo;s New Hire Rejuvenate Its Internet of Things Business?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intel (NASDAQ: INTC) recently hired Tom Lantzsch, a 10-year veteran of Softbank&amp;rsquo;s chip designer ARM Holdings, as its senior VP and general &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com/slide-shows/channel-programs/300083007/10-game-changing-it-startups-that-raised-funding-in-november.htm&#39;&gt;10 Game-Changing IT Startups That Raised Funding In November&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the Internet of Things catches fire in the IT world &amp;ndash; and particularly in the channel &amp;ndash; plenty of startups are helping to push IoT innovation forward. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/zebra-technologies-and-iot-industry-leaders-identify-intelligent-enterprise-as-decades-most-impactful-trend-300372409.html&#39;&gt;Zebra Technologies and IoT Industry Leaders Identify Intelligent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire (press release) As the Internet of Things industry is expected to continue to grow, Zebra Technologies, along with global leaders from healthcare, retail, transportation &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.secureworks.com/blog/exposing-the-risks-of-the-internet-of-things&#39;&gt;Exposing the Risks of the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;after portions of the Internet, including popular websites such as Amazon, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/intel-winning-blockchain-critics-reimagining-bitcoins-dna/&#39;&gt;Intel is Winning Over Blockchain Critics By Reimagining Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s DNA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With so much R&amp;amp;D ongoing in the blockchain sector, it&amp;rsquo;s hard for any new tech to separate from the pack. In addition to the sheer volume of designs for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.kitguru.net/channel/jon-martindale/ethereum-leveraged-for-new-smart-contract-blockchain/&#39;&gt;Ethereum leveraged for new smart-contract blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public blockchain platform, Ethereum, is being used as the backbone for a new, smart-contract system built on blockchain technology, which should &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newswire.ca/news-releases/blockchain-fintech-and-disruption-ey-demystifies-top-10-business-buzzwords-of-2016-604767646.html&#39;&gt;Blockchain, FinTech and disruption: EY demystifies top 10 business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canada NewsWire (press release) Blockchain  Think of blockchain as a version of the Internet that can carry out various transactions, but is virtually impossible to hack. It has the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/12/05/india-satoshi-studios-first-incubator/&#39;&gt;India&amp;rsquo;s Satoshi Studios Becomes South Asia&amp;rsquo;s First Blockchain Incubator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to reports on Indian news media, the Indian Bitcoin company, GBMiners has laid the foundation for South Asia&amp;rsquo;s first Blockchain incubator, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itworld.com/article/3146712/manufacturing/how-manufacturers-make-the-most-of-machine-data.html&#39;&gt;How manufacturers make the most of machine data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies like GE and Siemens are working to standardize platforms for machine-to machine communication. The leading ERP vendors have all &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.wired.com/2016/12/obama-cybersecurity-plan/&#39;&gt;Obama Has a Plan to Fix Cybersecurity, But Its Success Depends on Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its recommendations, in a hundred-page report, cover a lot of ground. It proposes fixing the shambolic security of internet-of-things consumer devices &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.sdcexec.com/article/12271216/taming-big-data-in-the-iot&#39;&gt;Taming Big Data in the IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though the story of the Internet of Things (IoT) and Big Data involves sensors and terabytes instead of wild animals, the overall theme is largely the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.redherring.com/uncategorized/deck-halls-christmas-2016s-top-tech-gifts/&#39;&gt;Deck The Halls: Christmas 2016&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Tech Gifts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a bona fide nerd or technophobic luddite there&amp;rsquo;s something for you this year, which has seen the Internet of Things (IoT) market &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://cio.economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/internet-of-things/digital-tools-can-help-traditional-manufacturers-transform-their-business/55814365&#39;&gt;Digital tools can help traditional manufacturers transform their business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If they have to reach a particular goal, they need to have the right tools, it may be digital, IoT (internet of things), cloud (cloud computing), these would &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3164517&#39;&gt;Status and Etherisc Named Winners of the Blockchain Startup Contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Blockchain Startup Contest saw participation by contestants from over 29 different nations showcasing a variety of blockchain use cases. Out of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://embedded-computing.com/guest-blogs/growing-the-internet-of-things-part-2-ease-of-use/&#39;&gt;Growing the Internet of Things, part 2: Ease of use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What will it take to really grow the Internet of Things (IoT)? The answer is complex and multifaceted, and we have to consider the following areas:. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3963180&#39;&gt;How the &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; Can Battle Generational Gaps - @ThingsExpo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SYS-CON Media (press release) The Internet of Things (IoT) or the growing trend to have internet connectivity in traditionally non-tech devices such as clothing, accessories, and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.telecomengine.com/article/singapores-smart-nation-uses-gd-test-seamless-cellular-switching&#39;&gt;Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation Uses G&amp;amp;D to test seamless cellular switching&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; to enable always-on, machine-to-machine communications without the hassle of having to physically replace SIM cards when switching operators.&amp;ldquo;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/malta-stock-exchange-blockchain-testing/&#39;&gt;Malta Stock Exchange Lays Groundwork for Blockchain Testing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exchange quietly announced late last month that it was forming an internal &amp;lsquo;Blockchain Committee&amp;rsquo; to guide the development of a strategic &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.readitquik.com/news/fintech/etherisc-and-status-win-blockchain-startup-contest/&#39;&gt;Etherisc and Status Win Blockchain Startup Contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Blockchain Startup Contest was organized by BlockchainHub Graz, which is a collaboration between Coinfinity, lab10 and MakerSpace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Bristol-is-Open-Wins-Internet-of-Things-Award-for-Programmable-City-Initiative-434744&#39;&gt;Bristol is Open Wins Internet of Things Award for Programmable City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes 05, 2016 &amp;ndash; Bristol is Open, an ambitious joint venture between the University of Bristol and Bristol City Council, received the Internet of Things award &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/05/the-internet-of-things-is-a-huge-opportunity-for-payment-firms/&#39;&gt;The Internet of Things Is a Huge Opportunity for Payment Firms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roswell, GA  (SBWIRE)  12/05/2016  The Internet of Things, also known as IoT, is the network between household items that will come to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.rfidjournal.com/articles/view?15295&#39;&gt;RIOgaleo Airport Adopts 3000 BLE Beacons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet of Things technology is helping passengers at the main airport in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, find services via their smartphones. By Edson Perin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cointelegraph.com/news/her-majestys-royal-mint-launches-gold-trading-on-blockchain&#39;&gt;Her Majesty&amp;rsquo;s Royal Mint Launches Gold Trading On Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distributed ledger technology is a game changer and supplying gold on a Blockchain has been on our minds for some time. But only after partnering &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cityam.com/255023/googles-deepmind-using-blockchain-related-technology&#39;&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s DeepMind is using blockchain related technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie is leading the work on what a Google spokesperson confirmed is a blockchain-like technology to which Suleyman referred while speaking at &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.internetsociety.org/blog/tech-matters/2016/12/your-reputation-safe-blockchain&#39;&gt;Is Your Reputation Safe on the Blockchain?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;mutable blockchains to implement the so-called &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; (RTBF) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/economy/policy/trai-extends-feedback-deadline-on-machine-to-machine-communications-paper/articleshow/55823587.cms&#39;&gt;Trai extends feedback deadline on machine-to-machine communications paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KOLKATA: The Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (Trai) has for a second time extended the deadlines for stakeholder comments and counter &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchdatacenter.techtarget.com/feature/Challenges-of-IoT-include-big-data-data-analysis-for-enterprise&#39;&gt;Challenges of IoT include big data, data analysis for enterprise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data and the internet of things are outputs of business demands that drive changes in applications. These changes create unique challenges for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itbusinessedge.com/blogs/infrastructure/disk-or-solid-state-is-only-the-first-of-many-options.html&#39;&gt;Disk Or Solid State Is Only The First Of Many Options&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solid-state storage comes in many forms, so even after the decision to forgo traditional tape or hard disk is made, the enterprise still faces a number of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.coursera.org/courses/?languages=en&amp;query=an+introduction+to+programming+the+internet+of+things+(iot)&#39;&gt;An Introduction To Programming The Internet Of Things (Iot)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;courses. 1000+ courses from schools like Stanford and Yale - no application &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.euroinvestor.com/news/2016/12/05/bristol-is-open-wins-internet-of-things-award-for-programmable-city-initiative/13493514&#39;&gt;Bristol is Open Wins Internet of Things Award for Programmable City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The World Communications Awards and Internet of Things Awards are hailed to be one of the industry&amp;rsquo;s most prestigious awards, recognizing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://readwrite.com/2016/12/05/history-industrial-internet-of-things-il4/&#39;&gt;Our (info)graphic, short history of the Industrial Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; information, American inventor and businessman Theodore G. Paraskevakos was working on the world&amp;rsquo;s first machine to machine (M2M) devices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://techcrunch.com/2016/12/05/how-blockchain-can-help-fight-cyberattacks/&#39;&gt;How blockchain can help fight cyberattacks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the promise behind blockchain, the distributed ledger that underlies cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum and challenges the traditional &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3146522/internet-of-things/10-giant-steps-for-the-internet-of-things-in-2016.html&#39;&gt;10 giant steps for the Internet of Things in 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again. The 10 technology trends and 5 ways the Internet of Things (IoT) will change your business next year prognostications &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://morningconsult.com/2016/12/05/wheeler-floats-fcc-cybersecurity-certification-iot-devices/&#39;&gt;Wheeler Floats FCC Cybersecurity Certification for IoT Devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 and released by Warner on Monday, Wheeler proposed an FCC-mandated cybersecurity certification process for Internet of Things devices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.business2community.com/business-innovation/blockchain-disruption-opportunity-01720762&#39;&gt;Blockchain Is A Disruption and An Opportunity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rapidly evolving technology of blockchains represents a Hard Trend that will continue to grow. It holds enormous promise for game changing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itbusinessnet.com/article/Status-and-Etherisc-Named-Winners-of-the-Blockchain-Startup-Contest-4724519&#39;&gt;Status and Etherisc Named Winners of the Blockchain Startup Contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Blockchain Startup Contest saw participation by contestants from over 29 different nations showcasing a variety of blockchain use cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mariner-usa.com/blog/azure-machine-learning-model-to-market/&#39;&gt;Should We Send the Azure Machine Learning Model to Market?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;model may be the final decider because human review may create an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.npr.org/sections/alltechconsidered/2016/12/05/504467134/despite-its-promise-the-internet-of-things-remains-vulnerable&#39;&gt;Despite Its Promise, The Internet Of Things Remains Vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The term for these Internet-enabled devices  like connected cars and home appliances  is the Internet of things. They promise to make life more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iotevolutionworld.com/iot/articles/427762-bringing-order-the-disorder-iot.htm&#39;&gt;Bringing Order to the Disorder of IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things (IoT) is growing fast, but it hasn&amp;rsquo;t arrived in full force yet. Over the next few years, we&amp;rsquo;ll likely see billions of new devices and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://edscoop.com/why-university-networks-face-heightened-cyber-risks&#39;&gt;Why university networks face heightened cyber-risks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things is poised to change our lives for all time in a wide range of different ways. According to a study conducted by Intel, the total &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.coursera.org/courses/?query=introduction%20to%20the%20internet%20of%20things%20and%20embedded%20systems&#39;&gt;Introduction to the Internet of Things and Embedded Systems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;courses. 1000+ courses from schools like Stanford and Yale - no application &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bangkokpost.com/business/telecom/1152557/nbtc-auction-to-prepare-for-5g&#39;&gt;NBTC auction to prepare for 5G&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; attempt to serve skyrocketing data traffic demand, fuelled by the proliferation of connected consumers and machine-to-machine connectivity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dcvelocity.com/articles/20161205-panel-key-to-internet-of-things-is-handling-data-overload/&#39;&gt;Panel: Key to Internet of Things is handling data overload&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logistics companies are embracing the Internet of Things (IoT) as a tool to handle the pressure of rising e-commerce fulfillment volumes, but as the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nwptv.org/blogs/local-national-news/despite-its-promise-the-internet-of-things-remains-vulnerable/&#39;&gt;Despite Its Promise, The Internet Of Things Remains Vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and Security technologist Bruce Schneier fears it will take a disaster for that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.the-blockchain.com/2016/12/06/chinas-huiyin-group-launches-20-million-blockchain-venture-capital-fund/&#39;&gt;China&amp;rsquo;s Huiyin Group Launches $20 Million Blockchain Venture Capital Fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Huiyin Group, a multibillion-dollar Chinese investment company, has announced the launch of a subsiduary called Huiyin Blockchain Venture &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/smart-manufacturing-market-global-industry-010600531.html&#39;&gt;Smart Manufacturing Market - Global Industry Analysis, Size, Share, Growth,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Finance Several developed economies have experienced mass scale adoption of the machine-to-machine communication and internet of things technologies &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bit.com.au/News/443698,five-winning-internet-of-things-startups.aspx&#39;&gt;Five winning Internet of Things startups&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month we mentioned the Spotless Hack @ the &amp;lsquo;G, a hackathon aimed at uncovering and fostering ideas for applying Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/manifold-technology-blockchain-platform/&#39;&gt;Californian Fintech Firm Releases Easy-To-Use Blockchain Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manifold Technology has made its patented blockchain platform available to allow non-technical developers to build enterprise-ready, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/run-for-cover-here-comes-the-blockchain-60664/&#39;&gt;Run for Cover: Here Comes the Blockchain!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain, most notably linked to Bitcoin, is very much a technology on the rise. Blockchain has recently made its way to Wall Street, with the largest &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Mobile Computing news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topmobilenews&#34;&gt;@topmobilenews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesstimes.com.sg/technology/cybersecurity-threats-loom-larger-from-within-survey&#39;&gt;Cybersecurity threats loom larger from within: survey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They are stepping up against the security risks posed by the widespread use of Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) practices, where employees use their &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.whatech.com/market-research/industrial/234285-discover-the-project-portfolio-management-ppm-market-overview-size-share-trends-analysis-and-forecast-to-2025&#39;&gt;Discover the project portfolio management (ppm) market overview, size,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WhaTech The demand is further projected to be driven by factors like the increasing trend of bring your own device (BYOD) or workforce mobility. BYOD enables &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.insidehighered.com/news/2016/12/05/st-norbert-colleges-computerless-computer-lab-shows-impact-byod-higher-ed&#39;&gt;St. Norbert College&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;computerless&amp;rsquo; computer lab shows impact of BYOD in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inside Higher Ed The last phase of the project included plans for a computer lab, but with the college about to phase in a bring-your-own-device (BYOD) policy &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mobilecomputingtoday.co.uk/4860/whatsapp-end-support-millions-smartphones/&#39;&gt;Whatsapp to End Support for Millions of Smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatsapp is taking another step to enhance their quality and they are now focussing only on the latest technology available around the globe. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ukmarketnews.co.uk/2016/12/05/outstanding-analyst-ratings-for-alternative-networks-lonan/&#39;&gt;Outstanding Analyst Ratings For Alternative Networks (LON:AN)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Numerous investment brokers have in recent days changed their price targets on shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN). According to data retrieved &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/391000/Global-Mobile-Device-Management-MDM-Market-to-grow-at-a-CAGR-of-25-40-over-Forecast-2015-2019.html&#39;&gt;Global Mobile Device Management (MDM) Market to grow at a CAGR of 25.40%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;openPR (press release) Albany, NY, Dec 05: MDM (mobile device management) is a tool used to manage, monitor, and track personal devices used in the workplace. It allows &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/391000/Global-Mobile-Device-Management-MDM-Market-to-grow-at-a-CAGR-of-25-40-over-Forecast-2015-2019.html&#39;&gt;Global Mobile Device Management (MDM) Market to grow at a CAGR of 25.40%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;openPR (press release) &amp;hellip; data, and configuration settings for devices such as tablets, smartphones, cell phones, and other mobile computing devices (such as phablets). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161205006029/en/Security-Orchestration-Market-Reach-1.6-Billion-2021&#39;&gt;Security Orchestration Market to Reach $1.6 Billion by 2021 - Dramatic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) The security orchestration market size is estimated to grow from USD 826.1 million in 2016 to USD 1682.4 million by 2021, at Compound Annual &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchdatabackup.techtarget.com/tip/Mobile-device-security-management-practices-enhance-data-protection&#39;&gt;Mobile device security management practices enhance data protection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While mobile security is a challenge, file sync-and-share products and mobile device management software can help protect your organization&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161205006267/en/Global-Mass-Notification-Systems-Market-2016-2020-Demand&#39;&gt;Global Mass Notification Systems Market 2016-2020: Demand for Mobile-Based&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) One of the primary drivers in the market is increase in BYOD adoption. The BYOD trend is taking the corporate world by storm. The percentage of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.whatech.com/market-research/medical/234768-byod-enterprise-mobility-market-expected-to-grow-73-30-billion-usd-by-2021-at-a-cagr-of-15-87-according-to-new-research-report&#39;&gt;BYOD &amp;amp; enterprise mobility market expected to grow 73.30 billion USD by&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WhaTech The mobile device management software has the largest market share in the BYOD &amp;amp; enterprise mobility software market during the forecast period. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://itbrief.co.nz/story/byod-causing-headaches-enterprises-when-not-managed-correctly/&#39;&gt;BYOD causing headaches for enterprises when not managed correctly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Failing to properly manage BYOD in the enterprise poses a big risk, according to NETSCOUT. As Bring Your Own Device policies become more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.geekwire.com/2016/17-microsoft-researchers-offer-bold-computer-science-predictions-2017-2027/&#39;&gt;17 Microsoft researchers offer bold computer science predictions for 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GeekWire What will be the key advance in mobile computing in 2017? In 2017, systems will increasingly re-architect themselves to support interactions without &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Security News from @trustpath - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-trust-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-trust-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Security news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/trustpath&#34;&gt;@trustpath&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.networksasia.net/article/security-brawn-brain-prevent-data-breaches.1480937265&#39;&gt;Security brawn with the brain to prevent data breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly interconnected businesses competing in the digital economy have to be ever more vigilant in protecting their core business assets. They have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/05/world-situation-awareness-system-sas-market-market-was-valued-at-19-billion-in-2015-and-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-8-2-during-the-forecast-period-2016-2022/&#39;&gt;World Situation Awareness System (SAS) Market market was valued at $19&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) &amp;hellip; radiological, and nuclear (CBRN) system, sonar, physical security information management (PSIM)/access control (including HMI) and others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.news18.com/news/tech/atms-easy-target-for-hackers-intel-security-1319325.html&#39;&gt;ATMs Easy Target for Hackers: Intel Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; Bank, Axis Bank and YES Bank blocked millions of debit cards that were compromised in one of the biggest data breaches in the financial sector. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.networksasia.net/article/security-brawn-brain-prevent-data-breaches.1480937265&#39;&gt;Security brawn with the brain to prevent data breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In NSS Labs&amp;rsquo; Breach Detection Systems (BDS) Group Test, Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s ATP solutions have managed to detect 100% of all the exploits delivered by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcquest.com/five-biggest-data-breaches-in-history/&#39;&gt;Five Biggest Data Breaches in History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the data collected by Breach Level Index (BLI) database, there were 974 data breaches worldwide in the first half of 2016, up 15 percent &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://it-online.co.za/2016/12/05/cybercrime-threat-trends-for-the-holiday-season/&#39;&gt;Cybercrime threat trends for the holiday season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Tis the season to be joyful, for family and gifts, fun and relaxation. In general, this is the time of year when people like to indulge themselves and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3965652&#39;&gt;Cyber Insurance Market to Reach $14 Billion, Globally, by 2022-Allied&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SYS-CON Media (press release) &amp;hellip; cyber insurance products that manage various degrees of risks and cover cost-associated data breaches, credit monitoring, forensic investigations, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scmagazineuk.com/russias-banks-will-be-hacked-today-apparently/article/576887/&#39;&gt;Russia&amp;rsquo;s banks will be hacked today, apparently&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emily Orton, director at Darktrace told SCMagazineUK.com, What we are seeing now is a shift away from relatively straightforward data breaches, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.hotelsmag.com/Industry/News/Details/70340&#39;&gt;Labor costs, branding, big data&amp;rsquo;s impact on EMEA: Aethos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; the risks associated with big data, headlines during 2016 have shown hospitality firms ill-equipped to deal with data breaches or security threats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.datanami.com/2016/12/05/ai-will-spoof-steal-identify/&#39;&gt;How AI Will Spoof You and Steal Your Identify&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The combination of massive data breaches and the rapid evolution of AI technology is a bad recipe for good security, the Sendr CEO and co-founder &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lexology.com/library/detail.aspx?g=ef3cfa42-1016-422a-ba3a-4f867d0a3e69&#39;&gt;Amateurs hack computers. Professionals hack humans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; for a business, coupled with the publicity and brand damage, is often far more of an incentive for companies to prepare for inevitable data breaches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.gospelherald.com/articles/68564/20161205/a-computer-expert-shows-its-incredibly-easy-to-steal-millions-online-now-how-to-protect-yourself.htm&#39;&gt;A Computer Expert Shows It&amp;rsquo;s Incredibly Easy to Steal Millions Online&amp;ndash;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gospel Herald This year has seen tremendous pressure from the public with small and large companies breached by in-country and foreign hackers. The US &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itnewsafrica.com/2016/12/retailers-be-vigilant-card-and-cybercrime-threat-trends-for-the-holiday-season/&#39;&gt;Retailers, be vigilant! Card- and cybercrime threat trends for the holiday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT News Africa Criminals then use this information to apply for legitimate banking cards using stolen credentials. Criminals attempt to install malware and other &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.todayonline.com/business/workers-are-biggest-security-risk-one-three-cios-say&#39;&gt;Workers are biggest security risk, one in three CIOs say&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; employees using their own devices at work, nearly all (97 per cent) of CIOs are taking action to protect their company from potential data breaches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.govinfosecurity.com/health-data-breach-tally-more-more-hacker-attacks-a-9577&#39;&gt;Health Data Breach Tally: More and More Hacker Attacks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since federal regulators began tracking major health data breaches in September 2009, some 1,757 incidents impacting a total of 169.7 million &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.techrepublic.com/article/microsoft-still-has-work-to-do-when-it-comes-to-malware-security/&#39;&gt;Microsoft still has work to do when it comes to malware security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the enterprise test, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s System Center Endpoint Protection fell in the fair-to-middling range, achieving an overall score of 14 out of a possible &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.waterstechnology.com/waters/analysis/2479008/buy-side-technology-awards-2016-best-buy-side-cyber-security-platform-tool-esentire&#39;&gt;Buy-Side Technology Awards 2016: Best Buy-Side Cyber-Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;www.waterstechnology.com &amp;hellip; network anomaly and forensics capabilities with Carbon Black&amp;rsquo;s endpoint capabilities, allowing eSentire to pivot from network to endpoint protection, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://itbrief.co.nz/story/byod-causing-headaches-enterprises-when-not-managed-correctly/&#39;&gt;BYOD causing headaches for enterprises when not managed correctly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But faster access and throughput also means the risk of faster and more extensive data breaches, if organisations fail to consider the full security &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cosmosmagazine.com/physics/china-s-quantum-satellite-could-make-data-breaches-a-thing-of-the-past&#39;&gt;China&amp;rsquo;s quantum satellite could make data breaches a thing of the past&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new satellite has the ability to send information securely, not with mathematical encryption but by using the fundamental laws of physics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iamwire.com/2016/12/top-7-cyber-security-predictions-for-2017-and-beyond/145494&#39;&gt;Top 7 Cyber-Security Predictions for 2017 and Beyond&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data breaches are getting more prevailing and attack trends show no proof of slowing down. Again, we tend to see these breaches target high-value &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Venture/Startup news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topventurenews&#34;&gt;@topventurenews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techcircle.vccircle.com/2016/12/05/weekly-startup-funding-roundup-in-charts/&#39;&gt;Weekly startup funding roundup in charts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As many as 23 startups raised angel/seed and venture capital last week, according to VCCEdge, the data research arm of News Corp VCCircle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://venturebeat.com/2016/12/05/data-center-hardware-startup-datrium-raises-55-million/&#39;&gt;Data center hardware startup Datrium raises $55 million&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The startup sells to organizations that are building their own private clouds or that &amp;hellip; cofounder and CEO Brian Biles said in an interview with VentureBeat. &amp;hellip; It will invest the new money in sales, marketing, support, engineering, and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/05/tyson-foods-launches-vc-fund/&#39;&gt;Tyson Foods Launches $150 Million VC Fund to Invest in Startups&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tyson Foods has unveiled the launch of a venture capital fund that will invest as much as $150 million into food startups, a venture that aims to target &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/smebiz/news/2016/12/05/boomtime-startups-fizzle-out-as-venture-capital-declines/&#39;&gt;Boom-time startups fizzle out as venture capital declines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DECLINES in the venture capital market are hitting startups of all sizes, but the &amp;hellip; This year, as he looked for a second round of funding, he found that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizjournals.com/newyork/news/2016/12/05/personal-finance-startup-moneylion-to-sink-teeth.html&#39;&gt;Personal finance startup MoneyLion to sink teeth into Series A funding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New York-area startups and venture capitalists are making funding deals with &amp;hellip; It is the latest startup, along with SoFi and Lending Club, to disrupt the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.enterpriseinnovation.net/article/singapore-startup-spacemob-raises-5-5-m-seed-funding-1511684363&#39;&gt;Singapore startup Spacemob raises $5.5 M in seed funding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Led by Vertex Ventures Southeast Asia, which was the first VC investor in Grab, Reebonz, Paktor and many other start-ups, the funding round is the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://themerkle.com/a-chinese-20-million-dollars-venture-fund-is-ready-to-finance-bitcoin-startups/&#39;&gt;A Chinese 20 Million Dollars Venture Fund is Ready to Finance Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Merkle The Bitcoin startup scene is about to receive up to $20 million from a venture fund. The money is coming from a Chinese family who owns a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17 Microsoft researchers offer bold computer science predictions for 2017</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/17-microsoft-researchers-offer-bold-computer-science-predictions-for-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/17-microsoft-researchers-offer-bold-computer-science-predictions-for-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GeekWire What will be the key advance in mobile computing in 2017? In 2017, systems will increasingly re-architect themselves to support interactions without &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.geekwire.com/2016/17-microsoft-researchers-offer-bold-computer-science-predictions-2017-2027/&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;http://www.geekwire.com/2016/17-microsoft-researchers-offer-bold-computer-science-predictions-2017-2027/&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topmobilenews&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/topmobilenews&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@topmobilenews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese 20 Million Dollars Venture Fund is Ready to Finance Bitcoin</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/a-chinese-20-million-dollars-venture-fund-is-ready-to-finance-bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/a-chinese-20-million-dollars-venture-fund-is-ready-to-finance-bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Merkle The Bitcoin startup scene is about to receive up to $20 million from a venture fund. The money is coming from a Chinese family who owns a &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://themerkle.com/a-chinese-20-million-dollars-venture-fund-is-ready-to-finance-bitcoin-startups/&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;http://themerkle.com/a-chinese-20-million-dollars-venture-fund-is-ready-to-finance-bitcoin-startups/&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topventurenews&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/topventurenews&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@topventurenews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS wants to dominate beyond the public cloud with Lambda updates</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/aws-wants-to-dominate-beyond-the-public-cloud-with-lambda-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/aws-wants-to-dominate-beyond-the-public-cloud-with-lambda-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has its Azure Functions service, while Google Cloud Platform offers Google Cloud Functions. To comment on this article and other CIO &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cio.com/article/3147385/cloud-computing/aws-wants-to-dominate-beyond-the-public-cloud-with-lambda-updates.html&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3147385/cloud-computing/aws-wants-to-dominate-beyond-the-public-cloud-with-lambda-updates.html&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@cloudfeednet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Californian Fintech Firm Releases Easy-To-Use Blockchain Platform</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/californian-fintech-firm-releases-easytouse-blockchain-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/californian-fintech-firm-releases-easytouse-blockchain-platform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Manifold Technology has made its patented blockchain platform available to allow non-technical developers to build enterprise-ready, &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/manifold-technology-blockchain-platform/&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/manifold-technology-blockchain-platform/&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five winning Internet of Things startups</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/five-winning-internet-of-things-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/five-winning-internet-of-things-startups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month we mentioned the Spotless Hack @ the &amp;lsquo;G, a hackathon aimed at uncovering and fostering ideas for applying Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bit.com.au/News/443698,five-winning-internet-of-things-startups.aspx&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;http://www.bit.com.au/News/443698,five-winning-internet-of-things-startups.aspx&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run for Cover: Here Comes the Blockchain!</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/run-for-cover-here-comes-the-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/run-for-cover-here-comes-the-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Blockchain, most notably linked to Bitcoin, is very much a technology on the rise. Blockchain has recently made its way to Wall Street, with the largest &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/run-for-cover-here-comes-the-blockchain-60664/&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;http://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/run-for-cover-here-comes-the-blockchain-60664/&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Manufacturing Market - Global Industry Analysis, Size, Share, Growth,</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/smart-manufacturing-market--global-industry-analysis-size-share-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/smart-manufacturing-market--global-industry-analysis-size-share-growth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Finance Several developed economies have experienced mass scale adoption of the machine-to-machine communication and internet of things technologies &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/smart-manufacturing-market-global-industry-010600531.html&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/smart-manufacturing-market-global-industry-010600531.html&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 7 Cyber-Security Predictions for 2017 and Beyond</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/top-7-cybersecurity-predictions-for-2017-and-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/top-7-cybersecurity-predictions-for-2017-and-beyond/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Data breaches are getting more prevailing and attack trends show no proof of slowing down. Again, we tend to see these breaches target high-value &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.iamwire.com/2016/12/top-7-cyber-security-predictions-for-2017-and-beyond/145494&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;http://www.iamwire.com/2016/12/top-7-cyber-security-predictions-for-2017-and-beyond/145494&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/trustpath&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/trustpath&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@trustpath&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Goes Live with Azure Active Directory PowerShell 2.0</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/post/microsoft-goes-live-with-azure-active-directory-powershell-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 17:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/post/microsoft-goes-live-with-azure-active-directory-powershell-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft today announced that the Azure Active Directory PowerShell 2.0 module has reached the &amp;ldquo;general availability&amp;rdquo; (GA) milestone. The module &amp;hellip;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://redmondmag.com/articles/2016/12/05/azure-active-directory-powershell-2.aspx&#34; onclick=&#34;trackOutboundLink(&#39;https://redmondmag.com/articles/2016/12/05/azure-active-directory-powershell-2.aspx&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#34; onclick=&#34;trackTwitterLink(&#39;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#39;); return false;&#34;&gt;@cloudfeednet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>