<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Venture on Crypt0 News</title>
    <link>//crypt0.net/categories/venture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Venture on Crypt0 News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Dataence. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crypt0.net/categories/venture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Venture capital funding better than bank loans for small businesses Investment from venture capital appears to help new startup businesses grow and boost entrepreneurship better than funding from bank loans, &amp;hellip; Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [5 December - 10 December] This week 14 startups raised over $12 Mn in funding altogether. &amp;hellip; $250K from Venture Catalysts, a Mumbai-based Seed fund and innovation platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
New $10M fund aims to aid NE Wis. startups The Badger Fund of Funds, a $25 million venture capital fund started by the &amp;hellip; Trotter said the seed fund&amp;rsquo;s investments should give startups enough &amp;hellip; Exclusive: Fashion e-commerce startup StalkBuyLove raises funding from VCCircle Existing investors including early-stage VC fund Singularity Ventures, Asia Venture Group, Asian E-Commerce Alliance, Kabs Ventures and FabIndia &amp;hellip; High-Profile But Secretive Funding For B2B FinTechs For startups, 2016 wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best year in venture capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Venture capitalists check out StartUP FIU companies Kathari and others from Athenian Venture Partners, MIT Enterprise Forum of South Florida, Florida Angel Nexus Fund, Urban Us and Keiretsu Forum &amp;hellip; This VC is backing one tech startup a month; transportation, IoT ventures VCCircle This VC is backing one tech startup a month; transportation, IoT ventures &amp;hellip; We don&amp;rsquo;t expect significantly large startups to get funded but this number &amp;hellip; Apache Zeppelin open-source analytics startup reveals new name, fresh Network World ZEPL is among a slew of open-source oriented startups attracting venture funding this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Exclusive: Automobile IoT startup Vehico raises angel funding from Calcutta VCCircle He worked with IBM and Tata Steel before launching his startup venture. Its flagship product Vehico Fleet is a telematics-based fleet management and &amp;hellip; Venture capital heavyweight Menlo backs Montreal startup Breather Silicon Valley venture capital heavyweight Menlo Ventures has made its &amp;hellip; The funding will enable Breather to keep building its rapidly expanding &amp;hellip; Why Venture Funders Are Shunning Baby Unicorns To be sure, the amount of total venture money spent on startups is still large, even though it has slipped to $55.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
One funded Indian tech startup shut shop every 10 days this year While shutdowns increased, fewer tech startups attracted funding. The number of angel, seed and venture capital funding in 2016 for tech startups fell &amp;hellip; Goldman Sachs leads funding round for Toronto consumer products platform The Globe and Mail Toronto startup Hubba Inc. has landed a venture capital investment from Goldman Sachs Investment Partners, an early backer of Uber, Facebook and &amp;hellip; Unpitch Is Back, Because We Still Need It An outfit called YoungStartup Ventures wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say how much founders &amp;hellip; These days, Unpitch is an event of the New England Venture Capital &amp;hellip; It can still be tough for first-time founders, especially when it comes to raising money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Weekly startup funding roundup in charts As many as 23 startups raised angel/seed and venture capital last week, according to VCCEdge, the data research arm of News Corp VCCircle. Data center hardware startup Datrium raises $55 million The startup sells to organizations that are building their own private clouds or that &amp;hellip; cofounder and CEO Brian Biles said in an interview with VentureBeat. &amp;hellip; It will invest the new money in sales, marketing, support, engineering, and &amp;hellip; Tyson Foods Launches $150 Million VC Fund to Invest in Startups Tyson Foods has unveiled the launch of a venture capital fund that will invest as much as $150 million into food startups, a venture that aims to target &amp;hellip; Boom-time startups fizzle out as venture capital declines DECLINES in the venture capital market are hitting startups of all sizes, but the &amp;hellip; This year, as he looked for a second round of funding, he found that &amp;hellip; Personal finance startup MoneyLion to sink teeth into Series A funding New York-area startups and venture capitalists are making funding deals with &amp;hellip; It is the latest startup, along with SoFi and Lending Club, to disrupt the &amp;hellip; Singapore startup Spacemob raises $5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Many boom-time startups fizzle out as venture capital declines Declines in the venture capital market are hitting startups of all sizes, but the &amp;hellip; They&amp;rsquo;re on track to raise the most money since the 2000-era bubble. Startups with global operations attract funds from Indian venture capital ETtech.com John Paul, founder of period tracker app Maya, had to wait for four long years before starting operations in India this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [28 November - 3 December] This week 19 startups raised over $48 Mn in funding altogether. &amp;hellip; A funding, led by Prime Venture Partners and Kalaari Capital as a co-investor. Expert warns of &amp;lsquo;disaster&amp;rsquo; as start-ups face investment surge in China Despite the boom in venture capital in the country, startup funding is down significantly this year as sky-high valuations make it tough for VCs to find &amp;hellip; UChicago Endowment to Invest in Startups with Roots on Campus Newswise The University of Chicago is designating $25 million from its endowment to invest alongside established venture funds in startups led by &amp;hellip; Startups with global operations attract funds from Indian venture capital Economic Times Indian venture capitalists are not surprised to see overseas startups raising money from India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
How Entrepreneurs Can Help Their Startup Communities Get More Funding How Entrepreneurs Can Help Their Startup Communities Get More Funding &amp;hellip; With nearly 80 percent of venture capital managed and invested in &amp;hellip; American Express Ventures leads $4m funding in fintech startup IndiaLends Delhi-based financial technology platform IndiaLends has raised $4 million (Rs 26.6 crore) in Series A round of funding led by American Express &amp;hellip; St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Is startup funding stuck in the Sebi maze Globally, such platforms, which are essentially equity crowdfunding in nature, have acted as a viable alternative to the interfering venture capital &amp;hellip; Exfinity Venture Partners Pump $2 Mn In AI Based Marketing Startup Inc42 Magazine (press release) (blog) Exfinity Venture Partners Pump $2 Mn In AI Based Marketing Startup &amp;hellip; Talking about the funding, Venkat Nagaswamy, CEO and co-founder, &amp;hellip; Marketing Startup MarianaIQ Raises $2 MN Via Venture Capitalist Marketing Startup MarianaIQ Raises $2 MN Via Venture Capitalist &amp;hellip; help of new venture capitalist, Exfinity Venture Partners in a Seed funding round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
BDC boosts clean-technology venture fund BDC Capital acts like a private venture capital fund taking seats on boards &amp;hellip; SDTC provides venture funding for startup companies at the pilot stage, &amp;hellip; Payments Startup Stripe Valued at $9 Billion in New Funding Given that startups rarely use venture capital financing to pay back debt, the fact that Stripe is borrowing cash suggests lenders believe the company &amp;hellip; Here&amp;rsquo;s what UK tech thinks of the 400m promised for VC startup investment &amp;hellip; as Philip Hammond announced plans to plough 400m into venture capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Nearly half of Vietnam Silicon Valley startups get external funding: Han DEALSTREETASIA It has so far trained four batches of Vietnamese startups, attracting investors to fund a few of them, notably Golden Gate Ventures&amp;rsquo; 7-digit US dollar &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Skolkovo Foundation new funds; IIDF, university pact The Skolkovo Foundation will be setting up three venture capital funds to help startups with funding while Internet Initiatives Development Fund (IIDF) &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
MAS reviewing rules to boost venture-capital funding It is working with the VC industry to grow the funding landscape for start-ups in Singapore and the region, said Deputy Prime Minister Tharman &amp;hellip; With Funds Drying up, Indian Startups Go on a Consolidation Spree! Finally the irrationality that had been driving the startup funding trends last year is &amp;hellip; In this FY ending March 2016, mergers and acquisitions in the startup &amp;hellip; a consolidation in the market where there were too many &amp;lsquo;me too&amp;rsquo; ventures, &amp;hellip; Network with the region&amp;rsquo;s savviest investors at Echelon Vietnam Startups and Investors are pre-matched based on Funding Round, Vertical and &amp;hellip; Linear Venture China Linear Capital (Linear Venture) focuses on &amp;hellip; Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [7 November - 12 November] Altigreen: Bengaluru-based cleantech startup Altigreen is in advanced discussions with existing investors and venture capital firms to raise a new &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Venture Capital Funding Inquiries for Startup Cannabis.net Surge after PR Web (press release) With the passage of marijuana initiatives on November 8th, startup Cannabis.Net has seen a surge in venture capital and angel funding questions. Family Travel Planning Site Winnie Raises $2.5 Million: Travel Startup Skift Family Travel Planning Site Winnie Raises $2.5 Million: Travel Startup &amp;hellip; raised a $3 million venture round from new investors IT-Farm, Justin Kan, &amp;hellip; Venture capitalists say they&amp;rsquo;ll keep pumping money into startups even with Quartz US markets aren&amp;rsquo;t the only ones being relatively sanguine about a Donald Trump presidency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
New deeper pool of venture capital to refresh local startup scene Vancouver is home to a half-dozen significant venture capital funds focused on tech: Version One Ventures, Pangaea Ventures Ltd., Chrysalix Venture &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Co-working space Z Nation Lab shortlists 13 startups for its bootcamp Among the 13 shortlisted startups, about three or four selected startups would raise funding, while venture capital firms such as Matrix Partners and &amp;hellip; Indonesia to use USO fund for startups Other than venture capitals, Indonesia is also seeing some growth in angel investing an alternative to traditional funding. Last year saw the forming &amp;hellip; Solar startup d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Startups capital drying up: Study - Chennai NYOOOZ There are indications that investors are now cautious about putting their money in new ventures With insufficient capital available, startups are going &amp;hellip; Nasscom 10000 Startups Supports Asia&amp;rsquo;s Largest Startup Expo World Startup Expo (WSE) is a unique three-day platform for startups, &amp;hellip; a venture capital firm that specialises in providing growth funding for startups &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Sources of Startup Funding Workshops to be held in Melbourne, Brisbane, NewsMaker (press release) Sources of Startup Funding Workshops to be held in Melbourne, Brisbane, &amp;hellip; Scale Investors (MEL), Blue Sky Venture Capital (BRI) and Right Click &amp;hellip; Start small, think big, move fast, IBM Venture Capital tells Malaysian New Straits Times Online &amp;ldquo;While IBM does not invest directly in start-ups or venture capital funds, we continue to have a relationship with people who manage funds in the Asian &amp;hellip; Ottawa bio-tech startup gets major cash investment Turnstone&amp;rsquo;s deal is the second-largest round of venture capital funding in Canada this year for a biotech startup, according to Invest Ottawa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Are fears of a slump in startup investments overplayed? SEBI data suggests ETtech.com Venture capital funds (or VCFs) have managed to lock down investments worth Rs 7,296 crore in the second quarter of current fiscal alone, making it &amp;hellip; Seed rounds get VC knock as valuation seem attractive MUMBAI: Are fears of a slump in startup investments overplayed? That seems to be the case as funding commitment from investors to venture capital &amp;hellip; Seed investment rounds get VC knock as valuation seen attractive There are several quality start-ups out there, in diverse sectors, wanting seed and early-stage capital, Jain added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
In startup funding, is Seattle&amp;rsquo;s loss Portland&amp;rsquo;s gain? I&amp;rsquo;ve talked with lots of people about whether Portland&amp;rsquo;s lack of a homegrown venture fund the size of a Voyager (which counts $420 million under &amp;hellip; Mobile Check-In App OpenKey Raises $8 Million: Travel Startup Funding This Skift The startup, based in London and San Francisco, raised a $2.6 million venture round this week and its total funding now stands at about $5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Exclusive: Bangkok Venture Club to raise $20m SE Asia-focussed fund Bangkok-based angel investor lobby Bangkok Venture Club has announced a $20 million fund to invest in startups across Southeast Asia, The funds &amp;hellip; SME Bank kicks off startup fund The Small and Medium Enterprise Development Bank (SME Bank) has launched a 1-billion-baht venture fund to help startups, says Somchai &amp;hellip; Emami group receives applications to fund startups The group is, however, yet to decide on the nature of funding and the equity it will take up with the start-up ventures it will fund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Nov 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-11-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
GIF start-up Giphy raises $72 mn funding at $600 mn valuation GIF start-up Giphy raises $72 mn funding at $600 mn valuation &amp;hellip; fresh round of funding led by Draper Fisher Jurvetson, Institutional Venture Partners, &amp;hellip; Skyscanner Leads Europe&amp;rsquo;s Record Year for Venture Capital Funding in Travel Skyscanner is the most well-funded travel tech company in Europe. For travel startups in Europe, though, funding has taken a downturn across the &amp;hellip; Washington University details new startup seed fund This new venture-capital fund will help us further support the science, &amp;hellip; Brian Feldt covers technology, venture capital, startups, real estate and sports &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Postmates buoyed by $141 million as startup funding gets tougher The number of venture deals has been falling, and it&amp;rsquo;s hitting non-unicorn companies with valuations below $1 billion, such as Postmates, especially &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Location, funding, skills: Is this country Europe&amp;rsquo;s best-kept secret for ZDNet File it under: Underrated startup ecosystems in Europe. &amp;hellip; of Vienna-based Speedinvest venture-capital fund, Marie-Hlne Ametsreiter says. &amp;hellip; Given the extent of public grants and private support, funding for startups in Austria &amp;hellip; Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [24 October - 29 October] Early-stage technology investor firm, Blume Ventures marked the final close of its second fund at $60 Mn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
SIDBI launches fund to promote innovation &amp;amp; entrepreneurship Under the Scheme, a fund of fund with a corpus of `60 crore has been &amp;hellip; various Venture Capital Funds registered with SEBI for investing in startups in &amp;hellip; Truck aggregator FR8 raises venture funding Truck aggregator FR8 raises venture funding &amp;hellip; The startup plans to grow 10 times over the next one year and expand its network from seven cities to &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Venture Capitalist Bill Gurley Warns of Dumb Money LAGUNA BEACH, Calif.Unsophisticated investors continue to pour money into Silicon Valley startups, warned venture-capital investor Bill Gurley on &amp;hellip; Ho Chi Minh City mulls $45m startup fund, reiterates stock exchange plan Funding into Vietnamese startups have also come from a spate of other regional VCs, like Golden Gate Ventures, Gobi Partners and Expara Ventures &amp;hellip; Exclusive: Astarc Ventures backs fashion discovery app Wooplr Astarc fund manager Hari Krishnan and Wooplr CEO Arjun Zacharia &amp;hellip; in a startup, based on the deal size and whether it leads the funding round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
FinTech startup Kredx raises $6M in Series A funding led by Sequoia Invoice discounting platform, KredX has raised about $6 million as Series A investment led by Sequoia Capital and existing investor, Prime Venture &amp;hellip; Exclusive: Fashion discovery app Wooplr gets fund from Astarc Ventures Astarc Ventures, the investment arm of Mumbai-based automotive solutions group Astarc Group, typically invests $300,000 in a startup, based on the &amp;hellip; Propel Ventures invests in insurtech startup Hixme Propel Ventures invests in insurtech startup Hixme &amp;hellip; (13m) Series &amp;lsquo;B&amp;rsquo; investment round, which takes total funding for Hixme to $26.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Vietnam plans new law for venture capital investments Vietnam plans to implement a new law that will govern the establishment of domestic venture capital funds, and help funnel investments into startups &amp;hellip; We Will Raise Money from a Venture Capital Firm to Fuel a Number of BW Businessworld We Will Raise Money from a Venture Capital Firm to Fuel a Number of &amp;hellip; a co-working space is a cost saving mechanism for Start-ups, we believe a &amp;hellip; Food delivery startup Box8 raises Rs 50 cr in Series B Funding Box8, one of the India&amp;rsquo;s fastest growing food delivery start ups has raised Rs 50 Cr in funding from IIFL Seed Ventures Fund &amp;amp; Mayfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Startup Street: Boman Irani Turns Angel Investor For Sports Startup Rooter Venture capital funding in the startup space has been showing signs of drastic slowdown when compared to last year&amp;rsquo;s funding frenzy. A recent report &amp;hellip; For funding, start-ups turn to corporate capital If you&amp;rsquo;re a start-up seeking investment, the traditional route would take you to a dedicated venture capital firm or angel investor. But these days, there&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [17 October - 22 October] 3Dexter: Delhi-based edtech startup 3Dexter secured $150K in funding &amp;hellip; an undisclosed amount of funding from Venture Highway, Vishy Poosala &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
The Startup Scene: Frustrations and Futures for Venture Capitalists in Corporate Counsel (registration) There is no greater marker of Silicon Valley success than venture capital funding. But while enterprise technology in other information &amp;hellip; Venture Capital Funding Floods Into Life Insurance Online insurance startups have been drawing significant funds from venture capital firms as these investors look for the next area that will offer them &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Investors&amp;rsquo; Favourites: Ten Most Funded Startups In Indonesia Most of the startups that are attracting Venture Capitalists&amp;rsquo; attention and money belong to the ecommerce sector, as local Indonesian players dominate &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
SafetyCulture app raises $23 million to end workplace accidents The founder of Australian startup SafetyCulture, Anear told Mashable he realised &amp;hellip; the Townsville-based company announced a Series B funding round Tuesday. Backed by respected venture capital firm Index Ventures, Blackbird &amp;hellip; Indonesia: Gadjian gets funding from Golden Gate, Maloekoe Ventures Gadjian, an Indonesian software company specializing in human resources management tools and payroll, has raised an undisclosed round of &amp;hellip; Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Engineering Director invests in real-time bot prevention startup e27 ShieldSquare, a Bengaluru-based startup providing real-time bot &amp;hellip; an undisclosed sum in funding from Venture Highway (through VH Capital).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Indonesian HR software startup Gadjian bags funding by Golden Gate Ventures GADJIAN, an Indonesian software company specializing in payroll and HR management tools, has raised an undisclosed amount of funding led by &amp;hellip; China Dealbook: Redpoint Ventures closed its China focused $180m VC fund; DEALSTREETASIA China Dealbook: Redpoint Ventures closed its China focused $180m VC fund; General Motors invests in Chinese car-sharing start-up &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Why fundraising by Flipkart is an event in India&amp;rsquo;s startup space? Flipkart, they argue, is no longer the benchmark for either funding or &amp;hellip; Between 2007 and 2015, venture capital-backed companies in India raised &amp;hellip; DIPP Secretary announces Rs 2000 crore credit guarantee fund for startups BGR India The government is in plans to set up a credit guarantee fund for startups &amp;hellip; the start-ups would receive financial support for their ventures, which will &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [10 October - 15 October] This week 13 startups raised about $97 Mn in funding altogether. &amp;hellip; round of Funding. The investment was led by Hyderabad-based Naya Ventures. Bike rental startup Tazzo raises seed funding from DSG Consumer Partners DSG Consumer Partners is a venture capital fund focused on identifying, &amp;hellip; Bangalore-based bike rental startup Wheelstreet raised Rs 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
SME foundation to provide support to startups Regarding venture capital, SMEDF would provide counterpart funds to startups, which received investment from angel investors, in exchange for stake &amp;hellip; In leaner third quarter for venture capital, four Tampa startups still land Tampabay.com Total venture dollars deployed to startup companies for the quarter fell 32 percent and the &amp;hellip; In 2015, CareSync attracted $18 million in VC funding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Travel Startup Funding This Week: $12 Million on Nomadic Workers Travel Startup Funding This Week: $12 Million on Nomadic Workers &amp;hellip; figure out the attraction for venture capital, except perhaps the desire to live &amp;hellip; VC funding hits 2 year low, drops 18% to $14.4 billion in North America as VentureBeat At long last, venture capital&amp;rsquo;s long-awaited return to normalcy appears to be happening. VC funding for the third quarter of 2016 slid for nearly every &amp;hellip; VC funding in startups falls to two-year low in 2016: Report According to Venture Pulse, Q3 saw a 14% decline in funding and $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
BEAM secures a six-digit seed funding from Tinkbig Venture to scale The Tech Portal The startup will utilize the freshly-raised funds to increase its presence in &amp;hellip; The Singapore and Malaysia-based startup believes in fostering strong &amp;hellip; Mist Insists On Selling Through The Channel: Startup&amp;rsquo;s $28M Funding Round CRN Networking startup Mist Systems, founded by former Cisco executives, has &amp;hellip; funding from Cisco, Lightspeed Venture Partners and Norwest Venture &amp;hellip; Start-ups expanding their horizons: Venture Catalysts co-founder Looking to address all start-up requirements, from funding to networking, Venture Catalysts even provides office space to promising entreprises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Silicon Valley Mobile Startup, PacketZoom, Secures New Venture Funding and PR Newswire (press release) Mobile Acceleration Leader Raises $4.3M Led by First Round Capital and Baseline Ventures to Support Expansion; Through Software Defined Mobile &amp;hellip; Breakout Labs backs 4 startups that are reprogramming nature A venture fund that backs very early-stage advanced tech and science startups, Breakout Labs, has invested in 4 new deals, according to founder and &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Indian Bitcoin startup Zebpay raises $5m in funding Indian Bitcoin wallet startup Zebpay is expected to close a Series A funding round &amp;hellip; the highest ever raised for a cryptocurrency venture in the country. Indian bitcoin startup Zebpay seeks $5m series A funding The startup is in talks with several Indian investors for this funding round and a US-based venture capital fund, which focuses on blockchain &amp;hellip; Funds &amp;amp; Angel Investors Participates in Venture Catalyst Delhi&amp;rsquo;s Pitch Day Leading investment Fund Venture Catalyst Delhi organised its first Pitch &amp;hellip; investment funds, Angel Investors and Start-ups were brought together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Wharton India Economic Forum Invites Startup Applications For Wharton India Inc42 Magazine (press release) (blog) The Wharton India Startup Competition (WISC) conducted in India, aims to &amp;hellip; a cash prize of $25K, along with funding mentorship from a leading venture fund. &amp;hellip; The winning team was awarded $10K in prize money, of $10K, a $20K &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [3 October - 8 October] This week 26 startups raised about $42.5 Mn in funding altogether. &amp;hellip; Kalaari Capital, Qualcomm Ventures, Russian venture capital fund, Ru-Net, and &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Menstrual Disc Startup Flex Raises $3M Funding To Help Make Periods Less Forbes Add The Flex Company to this growing list. The menstrual disc startup has just closed a $3 million seed round led by Better Our World Venture Fund. 45 digital health startups that raised money in Q3 2016 The startup, which grew out of healthcare investment firm Oxeon Holdings, &amp;hellip; Insight Venture Partners led this funding round, which will enable &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Stripe acquires team behind NoSQL database startup RethinkDB Started in 2009, RethinkDB participated in the Y Combinator startup &amp;hellip; The company raised $12.2 million in venture funding from among a bevy of &amp;hellip; TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Dining Reservations Investment and More in Travel Startup Skift It&amp;rsquo;s been an active week for travel startup funding. &amp;hellip; investors Bessemer Venture Partners, Fortify Ventures, Middleland Capital and Thayer Ventures. &amp;lsquo;Hustle&amp;rsquo; and a heart: Beth Engel dishes on the ethos of Dundee Venture Startland News Dundee in September announced it&amp;rsquo;s raised two-thirds of its targeted $30 million fund for startup deals in Kansas City, St Louis, Omaha, Lincoln, &amp;hellip; Venture funding, exits, continued to drop in Q3 A report on third quarter venture activity shows the number of startup funding deals has dropped for five straight quarters but the total invested this year &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
AI Software Startup DocSynk Nabs $1M in Seed Money From Naya Ventures To help further develop the software, DocSynk has just raised $1 million in seed funding from five-year-old Naya Ventures, a North Texas-based &amp;hellip; Early stage fund Ventureast secures $83M to invest in startups Early-stage investor Ventureast is planning to raise $150 million in what would its sixth fund at a time when there&amp;rsquo;s been a palpable slowdown in &amp;hellip; Metamorphic Ventures has a new, $50 million fund and a new brand Metamorphic Ventures, a six-year-old, New York-based seed-stage fund, &amp;hellip; Compound has already funded five startups with its newest fund, though &amp;hellip; Startups Can Now Raise $3 Mn Of External Commercial Borrowings: RBI The SIDBI has approved $139 Mn (INR 930 Cr) in disbursals from the $300 Mn (INR 2,000 Cr) fund-of-funds, it launched in August, to support venture &amp;hellip; Microsoft Venture Helps Finance 13 Startups So Far Describing the move as a shift in its investment strategy, Microsoft said the fund would focus on early-stage startups that are developing technologies &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Why Asia&amp;rsquo;s Healthcare Startups Don&amp;rsquo;t Need VC To Disrupt The Market I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed that the bulk of funding for health and medical technology startups are from venture capital. American startups such as ZocDoc are backed &amp;hellip; Malaysia: 500 Startups launches $50m Durian II fund for Southeast Asia Silicon Valley Venture Capital firm 500 Startups is launching a $50 million fund 500 Durians II for Southeast Asia with the fund destined to invest in &amp;hellip; Social Tables Closes $13M Series B Funding Round Washington, D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Is Singapore&amp;rsquo;s startup funding fever starting to cool down? Unfortunately for many would-be unicorn treaders, despite the influx of money, including Venturecraft Two, a $50m fund aimed at boosting medtech &amp;hellip; Beyond IPOs: Alternative Funding Options For Biotech Startups Taking this alternate route allows startups to address two big biopharmaceutical financial marketplace issues constricted venture funding and &amp;hellip; Which type of startup funding is best for your startup?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Stanford, MIT lead in graduating funded startup founders Certain universities are known to produce a high number of funded startup &amp;hellip; Founder-CEOs of the most five valuable private U.S. venture-backed &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Oct 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-10-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Why this top tech investor is funding a startup that could chop away at his Business Insider When Andy Weissman began to look at investing in a startup called &amp;hellip; Weissman is a partner at iconic New York VC firm Union Square Ventures, and &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
This Online Startup Tool Is Helping Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Entrepreneurs Find Funding It&amp;rsquo;s a new tool for entrepreneurs and startups to get the lay of the land in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s venture community and also figure out how best to raise money. Men&amp;rsquo;s grooming brand Beardo secures $500k seed funding from Venture The Tech Portal Beardo, an Ahmedabad-based startup is one such startup which provides products for men&amp;rsquo;s grooming, has raised around $500,000 from Venture &amp;hellip; Home Articles Bootstrap your way to start-up success: 5 tips on being a Anthill online In 2014, only one per cent of US start-ups were funded through venture capital and a similar sentiment has been echoed here in Australia 66 per &amp;hellip; RIL may invest in mature start-ups to deploy Rs 5000 crore fund Early this month when Mukesh Ambani announced Rs 5,000 crore proprietary venture capital fund, Reliance Industries (RIL) joined the growing club &amp;hellip; Funding wave boosts Birmingham tech startup scene All the funding activity shows Birmingham has the right ingredients to fuel a &amp;hellip; which is supported by an economic development venture philanthropy fund, made &amp;hellip; Tony Summerville is founder and CEO of Birmingham startup Fleetio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
YourNest raises Rs 300cr to fund early-stage startups, ropes in tech YourStory.com The YourNest India Fund II, which will tap into Indian HNIs, will focus on pre-Series A funding in 25-30 technology startups with globally-focussed B2B &amp;hellip; Qatar Foundation, 500 Startups to launch new fund for MENA region 500 Startups is a global venture capital seed fund and start-up accelerator based in Silicon Valley with over $250 million in assets under management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
YourNest launches Rs 300 cr fund for startups New Delhi, Sep 27, () Early stage venture capital firm YourNest today announced the launch of its second fund with a corpus of Rs 300 crore. Intrexon Funds Two Startups in New Venture (XON) To assist development centered on its core technology, Intrexon Corp. (XON) launched a $245 million startup fund this January. The fund, named &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Start-ups can take long-term risk with Indian money: Nilekani &amp;ldquo;The very nature of start-ups is that many ideas get funded; some ideas &amp;hellip; to be revisited or pivoted&amp;hellip;that&amp;rsquo;s the nature of this whole venture economy&amp;rdquo;. Let&amp;rsquo;s Barter India Raises Angel Round Led by Scale Ventures The team aims to use this funding amount to fuel the growth rate of Let&amp;rsquo;s Barter, &amp;hellip; venture capital firm that invests primarily in early-in-revenue startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Bounty: 8 startup funding really big this week [19 September 25 knowstartup (press release) This week, Swiggy has raised around $15 million led by US-based venture capital firm Bessemer Venture Partners in Series D round of funding. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [19 September - 24 September] Online food delivery startup Swiggy raised $15 Mn led by US-based venture capital firm Bessemer Venture Partners in Series D round of funding. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Fifth biggest ad agency in the world Havas launches Australian venture StartupSmart We don&amp;rsquo;t use the word startups, Wilson tells StartupSmart. &amp;hellip; Ensure the model is predicated on ventures beyond the startup phase we need to be &amp;hellip; Enterprise Startup Cloudcherry Secures Funding From Vertex Ventures, Others SaaS-based real-time customer sentiment mapping and experience analytics startup, Cloudcherry has reportedly raised $6 Mn (INR 40 Cr) from &amp;hellip; New Rules For Raising Venture Capital The reality is that snagging venture funding is getting much harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
VN must develop start-up ecosystem: deputy PM Corporations and big cities needed to support start-up businesses. &amp;hellip; to issue a circular on foreign venture capital funds for start-up businesses. Mobile gaming startup Flixy Games raises $425K in seed funding Mobile games publisher Flixy Games Pvt Ltd has raised $425,000 (Rs 2.8 crore) in seed funding from Rebright Partners, a Japan-based venture &amp;hellip; Hanoi wants to get in on Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s start-up race The city hopes incentives such as funding, training and simply a place to &amp;hellip; make it easier for foreign venture capital funds to invest in local start-ups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
What&amp;rsquo;s the best way to get start-up funding? While elevator pitches are important, venture capitalists (VCs - big funds that bet large sums of cash on start-ups in exchange for equity) and angel &amp;hellip; Dubai startup MoveSouq closes $3m funding round Dubai-based home services startup MoveSouq.com has closed a $3m &amp;hellip; The funding round was led by venture capital company AddVenture and is &amp;hellip; Most tech startups exit without raising funds, sell for under $50M But a new report shows that the majority of tech startups exit before they raise any venture or private equity funding and their valuation on exit is less &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Dundee Venture Capital Raises $20M Fund III to Back Midwest Startups BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Dundee Venture Capital, an Omaha-based seed-stage investment firm, today announced the firm has raised $20M for its Fund III. Dubai-based Home Services Startup MoveSouq.com Closes $3 Million Funding Zawya (press release) The funding round was led by AddVenture, an international venture capital &amp;hellip; interest in the region is a great signal for Middle East-based startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Online Food Delivery Startup Swiggy Secures $15 Mn From Bessemer Venture Inc42 Magazine (press release) (blog) Online food delivery startup, Swiggy has raised $15 Mn (INR 100 Cr) led by &amp;hellip; capital firm Bessemer Venture Partners in Series D round of funding. Food-tech startup Swiggy raises $15 million f&amp;hellip; Existing investors (Accel Partners, SAIF Partners and Norwest Venture Partners), also participated in the fresh round of funding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Bounty: 8 startup funding really big this week [11 September 18 knowstartup (press release) This week, GoPigeon had raised $1.5 million (around Rs 10 crore) in a pre-Series A funding round from venture capital investor Nexus Venture &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [12 September - 17 September] This week 16 startups raised $17 Mn in funding altogether. &amp;hellip; foodtech venture IdeaChakki raised an undisclosed amount of funding from Ratan Tata. AngelList braces for rainy days as startup seed funding falls AngelList calculates its returns using valuations assigned by investors in subsequent funding rounds, which can drop if the startup stumbles. Venture &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Salesforce Rises in Benioff&amp;rsquo;s Shadow to Become a Force in Venture Capital Benioff, working with adviser Mark Goldstein and their fund Efficient Capacity LLC, &amp;hellip; The venture arm currently has stakes in more than 160 startups. Big Banks Invest $55 Million in Blockchain Startup Ripple&amp;rsquo;s Series B Distributed ledger settlement startup Ripple has raised $55m in venture &amp;hellip; However, the investment is distinct for Ripple in that some of the funds could &amp;hellip; Exclusive: Health-tech startup Doctor Insta gets funding from RoundGlass VCCircle Munjal said the startup will use the funding for marketing two new &amp;hellip; in its pre-Series A round of funding led by early-stage venture fund YourNest, &amp;hellip; IT Minister Priyank Kharge Aims To Boost Karnataka&amp;rsquo;s Startup Ecosystem, Inc42 Magazine (press release) (blog) Speaking about the funding, Priyank Kharge, IT Minister, Karnataka said, An &amp;hellip; The policy includes a startup venture capital fund that aims at boosting &amp;hellip; This week in N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Sapphire Ventures Raises $1 Billion Fund To Connect Startups To SAP Forbes Sapphire Ventures has more money under management than many venture firms without the glitz. The investors at Sapphire have backed 38 &amp;hellip; Betting high on small ticket funding, Mumbai-based White Unicorn Ventures YourStory.com White Unicorn Ventures follows a diligent pre-screening process before signing deals with startups. The scouting process covers incubation centres &amp;hellip; Cambridge security startup gets an unexpected $40M in funding Turner said part of the funding would also be used to make acquisitions beyond &amp;hellip; Sara Castellanos covers technology, startups and venture capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
University invests $6 million in UC Berkeley startup institute The university allocated funds for the House through its UC Ventures Program a program run by the Office of the Chief Investment Officer, or OCIO. Prota Ventures Launches Startup Rocket to Assist Pre-Funded Entrepreneurs Prota Ventures, a venture-building and early-stage investment firm with &amp;hellip; Startup Rocket offers a framework that serves as a comprehensive and &amp;hellip; Prota Ventures Launches Startup Rocket to Assist Pre-Funded Entrepreneurs CHICAGO &amp;amp; SEATTLE &amp;amp; JACKSONVILLE, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
AirTree has raised $250m for &amp;lsquo;Australia&amp;rsquo;s largest&amp;rsquo; startup venture fund AirTree Ventures has announced that it has raised $250 million to create what it calls Australia&amp;rsquo;s largest venture fund. The capital will be split &amp;hellip; AirTree Ventures closes $250 million startup fund, the largest ever tech VC StartupSmart AirTree Ventures has closed the largest ever tech VC fund in Australia, securing $250 million to back local startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Dublin-based medical start-up secures 15m in funding round An Irish medical-related start-up has raised 15m from a funding round to &amp;hellip; The 15m investment was provided by Novartis Venture Funds and &amp;hellip; Is it time to fix Ireland&amp;rsquo;s venture funding imbalance? If 80pc to 97pc of venture capital funding in Ireland is going to Dublin, that is a serious problem for start-ups in Cork, Limerick, Galway and elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Why Kishore Biyani is scared of start-ups India: Why Future Group founder Kishore Biyani is scared of start-ups &amp;hellip; 5,000 technology start-ups in the country, funded or not by venture capital. Startup Street: India To Get A Desi Version Of Shark Tank? Looks like Christmas came early for digital startups. Mukesh Ambani&amp;rsquo;s Jio has set up a Rs 5,000 crore venture capital fund dedicated to startups which &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [4 September - 9 September] The Bihar Government launched the state&amp;rsquo;s startup policy. The policy includes a startup venture capital fund with a value of $750 Mn formed as part of &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Mark Zuckerberg venture invests Rs.332.3 crore in education startup Byju&amp;rsquo;s Online education start-up Byju&amp;rsquo;s has raised $50 million (about Rs.332.3 &amp;hellip; D funding included Sofina, Lightspeed Ventures and Times Internet Ltd. First time VC funds finding it difficult to raise money The correction in the startup arena does not bode well for debut venture funds. First-time fund managers are struggling to attract money from startup &amp;hellip; Signifyd raises $19M to protect online retailers from fraud E-commerce protection startup Signifyd secured $19 million in venture funding on Thursday to scale infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Start-up Deadpool in India: Government says it is only a lean phase On the Tracxn list what could be called a Start-up Deadpool for &amp;hellip; Funds are constantly coming in through angel funding and venture funding. Term Sheet: Startup funding roundup for August Coworking startup and code academy Galvanize announced last month that it had raised $45 million, accounting for more than half of venture funding &amp;hellip; Top 50 UK tech startups catching the eye of venture capitalists Venture capitalists are putting their money where their mouths are by investing in startups they believe in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Winston-Salem company state firms pitching for investment funds at business Winston-Salem Journal Before that, the startups beat out more than 230 companies in the New Ventures Challenge to get access to inception-stage investment money and be &amp;hellip; Bain&amp;rsquo;s Italian venture fund R204 Partners invests in Qurami R204 Partners, a private venture fund run by Bain &amp;amp; Company Partners, &amp;hellip; Folli, has invested a &amp;lsquo;sizeable&amp;rsquo; amount of money in Italian startup Qurami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Julie Bishop visits Australian-funded tech start-up warehouse in Tel Aviv Julie Bishop visits Australian-funded tech start-up warehouse in Tel Aviv &amp;hellip; absorbed in their laptops and working away on their latest start-up venture. &amp;hellip; help connecting with some of the most successful start-up brains in the world. Startup Deadpool: It is only a lean phase, says government The startups which failed (did so) either due to lack of funding, faulty &amp;hellip; Funds are constantly coming in through angel funding and venture funding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Bruce Macfarlane: What MMC Ventures is looking for in tech startups Unlike many tech startups, though, it has now raised more than $140m in venture capital funding, having closed a $30m Series F round earlier this &amp;hellip; Garena, SEA&amp;rsquo;s move valuable tech startup, raises funding from SeaTown, GDP DEALSTREETASIA Garena, a Singapore-based Internet company, announced a new investment from SeaTown Holdings International, subsidiary of Singapore state &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
RGPV sets aside 20 cr for startups - Bhopal NYOOOZ He added: &amp;ldquo;We have formed a corpus of Rs 10 crore venture fund for startups and another Rs 10 crore for innovation. RGPV has decided to invite &amp;hellip; Funding Bounty: 10 startup funding really big this week [29 August 04 knowstartup (press release) This investment will be channelled through Jio Digital India Startup fund. &amp;hellip; Existing investors like Footprint Ventures and undisclosed new investors &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
RGPV sets aside 20 cr for startups Startups can help students start new ventures.&amp;rdquo; He added: &amp;ldquo;We have formed a corpus of Rs 10 crore venture fund for startups and another Rs 10 crore &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Government-backed $20 million venture capital fund launched to back clean StartupSmart A new $20 million venture capital fund has launched with the backing of the federal government to support and encourage startups focusing on clean &amp;hellip; Reliance Jio sets aside Rs 5000 crore venture capital fund for startups Reliance Jio Digital India Startup Fund sets aside Rs 5,000 crore of venture capital to be invested over the next five years to encourage young &amp;hellip; Bridging The Funding Gap: An Interview With The Women Behind Aspect Forbes With companies like Chime, mobile-first banking that automates savings, Cato Networks, a startup that puts network security in the cloud and Vida &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Sep 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
India: AI startup Mad Street raises funds from Sequoia, existing investors India: AI startup Mad Street raises funds from Sequoia, existing investors &amp;hellip; Exfinity Venture Partners LLP and GrowX Venture Management Pvt. Ltd. AI Startup Mad Street Den Raises Series A Funding From Sequoia And Others The couple thus came up with Mad Street Den a computer vision and artificial intelligence (AI) startup. The venture aims to bring AI into daily lives of &amp;hellip; Indo-US relationship key to start-up success: Amitabh Kant &amp;ldquo;While we have venture funds here, we need them to grow 10x in India&amp;hellip; Our objective is that the ecosystem for venture funds grows and expands and &amp;hellip; Reliance to set up 5000-cr venture fund for start-ups On Thursday, Ambani announced plans to set up a 5,000-crore VC fund Reliance Jio Digital India Startup Fund to boost entrepreneurship in &amp;hellip; When Has a Startup Over-Shopped For Funding?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Who needs seed funding? Not this Indian VR startup The venture has been able to gain this traction without any external aid or funding according to its core team, FlipSpaces explained. We believed &amp;hellip; Property startup Zipmatch gets funding from Kickstart and Monk&amp;rsquo;s Hill Confident in a rising property market in the Philippines, property-oriented startup ZipMatch has recently secured venture funding from Kickstart &amp;hellip; Look for cockroaches, not unicorns and other things you can learn from Salon After U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Online startup Livspace raises Rs 100 cr; Anuj Srivastava says will reach Financial Express &amp;hellip; Venture Partners and Jungle Ventures in a series C funding, the company &amp;hellip; The company aims to utilise the fresh funds to expand its geographical &amp;hellip; The Changing Face of Accelerators, the Travel Industry and Startup Skift Startup accelerators have shelled out billions of dollars in funding and &amp;hellip; at 500 Startups, says travel has been out of favor for awhile in the venture &amp;hellip; Rev1 Ventures Launches $22 Million Seed Fund to Fuel High-Growth Startups Today, Rev1Ventures, a top VC investor in the Great Lakes Region, announced the launch of Rev1 Fund I, the company&amp;rsquo;s most significant fund to-date &amp;hellip; Orios Capital plans $1m startup fund It also forms part of its strategy to engineer funding for startups, helping &amp;hellip; has metamorphosed into one of Africa&amp;rsquo;s emerging venture capital funds for &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Bengal Joins Startup Party in Effort to Shed Anti-Industry Image Roy, whose firm Kolkata Ventures now provides seed funding for startups and joins the government in building an eco-system of support in the eastern &amp;hellip; 7 Ways To Bootstrap Your Tech Startup Without Venture Capital You can launch your tech startup without venture capital, and with only a few changes to &amp;hellip; Find your early adopters who will help fund development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Indonesian start-ups take to global stage &amp;hellip; Anis Uzzaman, CEO of Fenox Venture Capital, which invests multimillion dollar funds in start-ups across the US, Asia, the Middle East and Europe. Agritech startup Krishi Star secures seed funding Agri-business venture Krishi Star has raised seed funding from Artha Venture Challenge, Menterra Social Impact Fund and Upaya Social Ventures. Indore-based EngineerBabu bags seed round funding from Scale Ventures I realised that here was a two and a half year old startup that&amp;rsquo;s bootstrapped and didn&amp;rsquo;t build a business in order to get a valuation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Indonesian start-ups take to global stage An unnamed venture capitalist from Ukraine has even shown an interest in funding specific start-ups in Indonesia, Fadjar said. Last year, $590 million &amp;hellip; Leverage venture debt early on, panellists at TechCircle tell entrepreneurs &amp;hellip; capital funding, venture debt is coming to the rescue of VC-backed startups, &amp;hellip; funding crunch is opening doors for an alternative source of funding. Indian Startups Are Tapping Into New Sources Of Capital As Funding Dries Up As 2016 progresses into its second half, a KPMG and CB report shows that Venture Capital Investments in India have fallen to $583 million, down from &amp;hellip; Noise around consolidation becomes louder among Indian startups Noise around consolidation becomes louder among Indian startups &amp;hellip; What we have is a robust ecosystem of early stage venture fundingyou see an &amp;hellip; Dreamlines, Dufl and More in Travel Startup Funding This Week Dreamlines, Dufl and More in Travel Startup Funding This Week &amp;hellip; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; Dreamlines raised a $15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Singapore Reviews Venture Capital Regime to Push Startup Funding Singapore is reviewing the rules for venture capital firms as it attempts to draw more capital to the country&amp;rsquo;s financial technology startups, according to &amp;hellip; Online Wedding Planning Startup Shaadisaga Raises Funding from ah! BW Businessworld Shaadisaga, is an online platform that caters to the to-be-weds in terms of their wedding needs, focusing primarily on weddings ranging between INR &amp;hellip; Singapore reviews venture capital regime to push startup funding Monetary Authority of Singapore managing director Ravi Menon listens during a lecture organised by MAS on November 17, 2014 in Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Tata&amp;rsquo;s $300m venture fund plans to invest in startups The newly set up RNT Capital Advisers, a venture fund launched by Tata Sons chairman emeritus Ratan Tata, will deploy $300 million across startups &amp;hellip; Artificial intelligence start-up Octo.ai raises $200000 New Delhi: Delhi-based artificial intelligence start-up Octo.ai has raised &amp;hellip; investor Outbox Ventures, Rahul Khanna, managing partner of venture debt fund &amp;hellip; Some of the other start-ups who raised funds this year include Snapshopr &amp;hellip; Kelly Services And Temp Holdings Launch $10 Mn VC Fund For HR Startups Gurgaon-based recruitment firm Kelly Services has launched a corporate venture capital fund in association with its joint venture partner for Asia &amp;hellip; Dubai&amp;rsquo;s TURN8 Launches US$60 Million Venture Fund If you are a seed-stage or early-stage startup seeking initial investment to build your product, then there&amp;rsquo;s a new regional VC fund that you can &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
DC Cybersecurity Startup Virtru Raises $29M to Protect Your Emails Washington, D.C. encryption software startup Virtru has closed a $29 million funding round. The new funding was led by Bessemer Venture Partners, &amp;hellip; Kobe Bryant is launching a $100 million investment fund Bryant has teamed up with investor Jeff Stibel to launch a $100 million fund for &amp;hellip; The point is to add real value, Stibel whose past ventures include &amp;hellip; Curry are among those who are involved in financing or managing startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Funding Galore: Startup Fundings Of The Week [15 August - 20 August] This week, 16 startups raised about $260 Mn in funding altogether. &amp;hellip; and Lightspeed Venture Partners did not participate in this round of funding. Why are early stage Venture Catalysts offering much more than startup Economic Times Early-stage funds are now offering a bouquet of services to startups, from &amp;hellip; Venture Catalysts is not the only investor riding the value-added &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Venture capital firm Scale Ventures acquires Guerilla Ventures Till date, Guerrilla Ventures has funded over 21 startups including Asimov Robotics, Radix Healthcare, Harvin Academy, Fin, Innov8 and many more &amp;hellip; These 3 Trends Are Changing How Startups Get Funding While many startups used to rely exclusively on venture capital firms to providing funding, the amount of VC firms in existence today has dropped &amp;hellip; Cambridge University controlled tech startup fund raises 75m Cambridge Innovation Capital, an investment fund which commercialises &amp;hellip; New investors include Winton Ventures, the Oman Investment Fund and &amp;hellip; ET India Startup Ecosystem Barometer Part 2: Issues impacting the sector Read: The ET India Startup Ecosystem Barometer part 1 &amp;hellip; It was a busy 2015 for venture capitalists as funding hit a peak, with 473 deals registered &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Greg Hunt flags new fund to encourage innovation, but it&amp;rsquo;s not just for Business Insider Australia While we have already established the Biomedical translation Fund and the CSIRO commercialisation fund, the venture capital sector has made it &amp;hellip; More Unicorns But Fewer Deals: The Current State Of Venture Capital Funding Although the percentage may appear incremental, startup and earlystage company growth are important &amp;hellip; And that doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen without funding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Khosla Ventures leads $61M funding for cloud data manager Rubrik Rubrik, a cloud data management platform, raised $61 million in funding on Tuesday to scale its hybrid backup technology. Khosla Ventures led the &amp;hellip; Female-led Pakistani startup BeautyHooked raises $280000 seed funding Home-grown beauty services platform, BeautyHooked, has just closed their seed funding round of $280,000 led by Fatima Ventures. Through this &amp;hellip; Good times continue for early-stage startups, four more ventures raise YourStory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
How India was shaped from being a risky venture to a startup destination According to historian Ramachandra Guha, no venture capitalist would have funded a startup called India in 1947, as it was then avery risky venture. Startups&amp;rsquo; mid-life funding crisis deepens Mid-stage venture funding, which showed some promise of picking momentum in the beginning of the year after a major dip in October last year, &amp;hellip; Start-up emergency funding gets a fancy name in pre-series A A few times, even the existing investors including angels and seed stage venture capital funds pump in some money to boost their promising portfolio &amp;hellip; Retail Jewellery Marketplace, Joolz Raises $500K Funding from ah!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
One Year Later &amp;lsquo;Startup India&amp;rsquo; Grapples With Taxes, Funding, Infrastructure It (government) gives money to funds that in return invest in start ups. &amp;hellip; is not directly pumping money into start ups. it will be via funds/venture capital. Octopus Ventures leads $22m funding round in Berlin menswear startup London-based venture capital firm Octopus Ventures has led a new $22m funding round in Outfittery, the curated shopping startup for men that is &amp;hellip; Through venture fund, Constellation gets intel while startups get funding When Constellation Energy Group decided to back Astrum Solar in 2011, it was a huge boon for the Baltimore energy startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Venture on: Local entrepreneurs ready to bet on startup funding But startup funding, often called venture or angel investing, is risky. &amp;hellip; Hagmaier said he didn&amp;rsquo;t raise venture capital for his Roanoke startup, Interactive &amp;hellip; Funding Bounty: 10 startup funding really big this week [08 August 14 knowstartup (press release) This week, cloud-based service provider Zenoti has raised $15 Million funding in a round led by Norwest Venture partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
How This Woman Went From Homelessness to Running a Multimillion-Dollar Inc.com Now, she&amp;rsquo;s leading a $5 million venture fund focused in finding the most &amp;hellip;. says Alicia Thomas, CEO of Dibs, a Backstage Capital-backed startup &amp;hellip; Startups Are Struggling To Achieve Pre-Series A Funding To fill the vacuum created by no pre-series A funding happening in the market, and lack of enablers for the startups to help them achieve it Venture &amp;hellip; Big data startup Innovaccer raises $15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
UAE&amp;rsquo;s Startup Scene Heats Up With Launch Of TURN8&amp;rsquo;s $60 Million Venture Forbes Middle East Dubai-based startup accelerator TURN8 has launched a $60 million venture capital fund targeting opportunities in Middle East startups. With the move &amp;hellip; In Startup Funding This Week, AirHelp Raises $12 Million to Help Passengers Skift In Startup Funding This Week, AirHelp Raises $12 Million to Help &amp;hellip; &amp;gt;&amp;gt;MI Airline raised a $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Australia&amp;rsquo;s Future Fund leads $77 million raising in US big data startup The Australian Financial Review Australia&amp;rsquo;s Future Fund leads $77 million raising in US big data startup &amp;hellip; MapR Technologies, which also included Google&amp;rsquo;s venture capital funds. Finland&amp;rsquo;s hot startup scene has huge ambitions there&amp;rsquo;s just one problem The Finnish startup scene has shown great promise through the years: It has &amp;hellip; Swedish startups can tap into much more locally-led venture funding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Equity Venture Partners and Microequities team up to launch a $20 million StartupSmart Startup advisory firm Equity Venture Partners and small cap fund manager Microequities have teamed up to launch a new $20 million venture capital &amp;hellip; Finexio Nabs Funding To Fight Paper In Virtual B2B Payments According to B2B payments startup Finexio, about half of B2B payments in the U.S. are conducted via paper check due to high fees associated with &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Aug 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-08-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Venture/Startup news from @topventurenews.
Investors get set and go for city startups &amp;hellip; grabbing the attention of angel investors and venture capitalists (VC). &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;The angel and seed funding in Ahmedabad-based startups is certainly &amp;hellip; Hunger deaths don&amp;rsquo;t deter fund flow to food startups In January, FreshMenu, an online food-tech venture that delivers meals prepared at its kitchens, had raised $17 million (around Rs 110 crore) in its &amp;hellip; A dot-com-era venture capitalist, still in the local trenches Venture capitalist Bruce Luehrs, who weighed startups and pitched investors for Princeton&amp;rsquo;s pioneering Edison Venture Fund back in the dot-com &amp;hellip; $60m venture capital fund formed by Dubai firm The fund will continue to support the startup ecosystem and look for opportunities in technology innovation that match our portfolio requirements and &amp;hellip; Babson Research Shows What Startup Funding Looks Like Globally Eleven percent - the second highest percentage for a continent - of North American entrepreneurs working on early stage ventures received funding &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>