<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data on Crypt0 News</title>
    <link>//crypt0.net/categories/data/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data on Crypt0 News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Dataence. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crypt0.net/categories/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
World Human Rights Day: Six Ways In Which Big Data Is Helping Fight Child Techstory Child trafficking is growing fast across the world. According to the International Labor Organization 1.2 million children are trafficked each year, often &amp;hellip; Innovation On Global Population Health Management Industry Analysis To Medgadget (blog) As per the research, the rising aging population and the implementation of big data are two of the major factors expected to drive the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Navigating the World of Big Data Analytics Leveraging our Agile Analytics Lab, we created reusable data processing pipelines, loaded the data into Hadoop and readied it for analysis. Once the &amp;hellip; BGU, PayPal form partnership in cybersecurity research PayPal&amp;rsquo;s involvement in big data and machine learning technology has been supported by its significant research and development (R&amp;amp;D) activity in &amp;hellip; Amazon Redshift Engineering&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Table Design Playbook Playbook: Table Data Durability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Commercial Pharmaceutical Analytics Market to Provide over USD 1.5 Billion PharmiWeb.com (press release) The tools such as Big Data, Tablue, Hadoop, and such others actually made it possible to handle such a huge data from these industries. Big Data has &amp;hellip; ZNV &amp;amp; Cloudera target big data analytics management in data centers The company says this need must be addressed, so it launched WeKeeper, a big data solution that will aid data center managers in their choices &amp;hellip; A guide to data innovation for development: From idea to proof-of-concept Global Pulse has served as a big data innovation hub within the UN for the past five years, testing new approaches and designing big data pilot &amp;hellip; Global Big Data and Analytics in Telecom Industry Growth, Analysis, and NewsMaker (press release) The Global Big Data and Analytics in Telecom Industry Industry 2016 Market Research Report is a professional and in-depth study on the current state &amp;hellip; The megatrends that will rock the property industry A number of potential disrupters were uncovered, including sustainable cities, the move to carbon zero, big data, the sharing economy, virtual reality, &amp;hellip; Interactive Analysis of Genomic Datasets Using Amazon Athena running a big data system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Etiya&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Serdoo&amp;rsquo; uses AI to automate customer service management Etiya, the leading independent software vendor providing telco CRM, catalog-driven BSS/OSS, social CRM and big data analytics, announced the &amp;hellip; Using big data to combat illegal fishing The international community is desperately trying to crack down on illegal fishing and is increasingly harnessing the power of big data to achieve this. subroutine in ABAQUS read big data file some data file and then pass is to the other subroutine &amp;lsquo;DLOAD&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Managing Enterprise Data Strategies with Hadoop, Spark, and Kafka failures can be time-consuming and expensive. This hands-on course &amp;hellip; Big data for development and humanitarian action: Towards responsible Reliefweb In 2014, Global Pulse established a Data Privacy Advisory Group comprised of experts from public and private sector, academia and civil society from &amp;hellip; Cmr. McSweeny will participate in seminar on Competition and Big Data and Big Data sponsored by King&amp;rsquo;s College London, Safra Lecture &amp;hellip; Big data, big hype, getting bigger but not grown up quite yet Big data, big hype, getting bigger but not grown up quite yet &amp;hellip; When it comes to big data there has certainly been plenty of hype, but not a lot of facts from &amp;hellip; from big-data-as-a-service through to full-blown platforms like Hadoop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
How data analytics and visualisation revolutionized AML Big data solutions that support evolving business and regulatory requirements by maintaining an ecosystem of large datasets will become invaluable &amp;hellip; Big data helped Trump even after he scorned it WASHINGTON - Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign &amp;ndash; but those techniques might well have &amp;hellip; Big data helped Trump even after he scorned it Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign but those techniques might well have propelled him to &amp;hellip; Big Data Pharmaceutical Advertising Market Research Report Now Available at The Republic of East Vancouver Research Corridor has published a new research study titled Big Data Pharmaceutical Advertising Market Growth, Share, Opportunities, &amp;hellip; Why Analyzing Unstructured Data Benefits Every Claims Manager If you&amp;rsquo;re just catching on to the fact that big data is shaking up the insurance industry in a big way, you&amp;rsquo;re a bit behind the curve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Market researchers embrace the world of Big Data The first Friday in December every year ushers in the beginning of Christmas for many Irish marketers. With their budgets for the following year in the &amp;hellip; Big Data Helped Donald Trump Even After He Scorned It Donald Trump had developed a digital strategy even after winning the nomination. (AFP File Photo). Washington, United States: Donald Trump &amp;hellip; Big data helped Donald Trump even after he scorned it WASHINGTON: Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign &amp;ndash; but those techniques might well have &amp;hellip; More companies paying to pinpoint big-data weather forecasts A growing number of construction companies, farmers and railways are benefitting from area-specific weather forecasts based on supercomputer &amp;hellip; Attunity Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
David Eden on the many facets of AI The behind-the-scenes algorithms process big data to make our lives more predictable. Big Data offers such insights and often, this is because of an &amp;hellip; Oracle Big Data Spatial and Graph create two Hadoop Configuration object to access the vertices and edges &amp;hellip; Global Big Data Market 2015-2020 1, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; NOVONOUS estimates that Global Big Data market will &amp;hellip; Technologies such as NoSQL databases and MapReduce/Hadoop &amp;hellip; How Will Big Data Affect Evolution of Social Science?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Poised to Get Much Bigger in 2017 Big Data is only going to get much bigger, so big in fact that companies attempting to deal with massive and more complex data sets are going to find it &amp;hellip; Siemens And Northwell Announce Alliance, Enter Big Data Arms Race Today I am at the Forbes Healthcare Summit where Northwell Health and Siemens Healthineers announced a major collaboration to utilize big data in &amp;hellip; 4 Gotcha&amp;rsquo;s in Risk Analysis for Big Data Initiatives Evaluating risk vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data in Global Retail market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 35% Big Data in Retail Industry controls the 9% market share in terms of revenue in &amp;hellip; Technologies such as NoSQL databases and MapReduce/Hadoop &amp;hellip; Big Data analytics Nostradamus of the 21st century data, according to a Griffith University researcher who correctly predicted &amp;hellip; Telecom Industry: Big Data Analytics Adoption / Usage Trends 2016-2018 Pyramid Research&amp;rsquo;s Big Data Analytics Adoption / Usage Trends 2016-2018 report examines the overall spend on BDA, market opportunities &amp;hellip; AWS Delivers More AI, Analytics, Partnerships And A Big Rig For Moving Big CRN Amazon Web Services (AWS) showcased several artificial intelligence and data services Wednesday for partners to use in building applications that &amp;hellip; Hadoop Industry Major Key Players (Active networks) are IBM, Dell, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
New website uses big data to address underrepresentation of women in EurekAlert (press release) BINGHAMTON, NY - A new website created by faculty and students at Binghamton University, State University of New York ranks university &amp;hellip; A panel of leaders to discuss, &amp;lsquo;Assessing the Value of Your Big Data Broadway World CHICAGO, Nov. 29, 2016 /PRNewswire/ Investments in big data analytics continues to rise. Due to today&amp;rsquo;s technology, business leaders now have &amp;hellip; 2nd Watch Earns AWS Financial Services Competency 2nd Watch has previously earned AWS competencies in Migration, DevOps, Big Data, Marketing and Commerce, Life Sciences and SharePoint and is &amp;hellip; How Big Data Reveal Your Behavior Thirty-five billion words are exchanged by more than 700 million internet users in China each day, according to a new report examining the behaviour &amp;hellip; Telecom Structured Data, Big Data, and Analytics: Business Case, Market PR Newswire (press release) Communication Service Providers (CSP) acquire and maintain substantial structured and unstructured (Big) data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=http://techblog.netflix.com/search/label/big%2520data&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYASoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNEYMlTikWjHydYhiWHLAX4xr_beMw Big Data https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://ssrn.com/abstract%3D2394683&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYAyoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNH3PJGIUPui1aksxWCQkhKz5wH6cA Strata Hadoop Conference 2016 Strata + Hadoop World Conference &amp;hellip; Fusionex Big Data Analytics helps you make the best decisions possible; and who knows, you might even &amp;hellip; https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://www.imi.europa.eu/sites/default/files/uploads/documents/Events/SF%25202015/BigData_Concept_29May2015.pdf&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYBSoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHnyxc5O4rn2f7VUcIsCR1JF3jkQw Oracle Big Data Preparation Cloud Service Oracle Big Data Preparation Cloud Service is a managed Platform as a Service (PaaS) cloud-based offering that enables you to rapidly ingest, repair, &amp;hellip; Big Data Coming In Faster Than Biomedical Researchers Can Process It Biomedical research is going big-time: Megaprojects that collect vast stores of data are proliferating rapidly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data SQL Quick Start. Big Data SQL over complex data types in Oracle Big Data SQL over complex data types in Oracle NoSQL. &amp;hellip; In this example we are going to show you how to use Oracle Big Data SQL over these &amp;hellip; .oracle.com/cd/NOSQL/html/examples/hadoop/hive/table/package-summary.html# &amp;hellip; David Leach appointed boss of Spark Ventures&amp;rsquo; big data division Qrious David Leach, the former senior vice-president at Orion Health, has been appointed chief executive of Spark&amp;rsquo;s big data venture Qrious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
How Predictive Analytics Boosts the Customer Experience at the Georgia InfoQ.com Managing Big Data has become a major competitive advantage for many organizations and hence maintaining a proper analytics platform is vital for &amp;hellip; Managers push back against the certainties of big data Clay Christensen tells a good joke about a tour of heaven. How come there&amp;rsquo;s no data here? the Harvard professor asks his celestial guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big debate about Shakespeare finally settled by big data: Marlowe gets his NewsOK.com Now, for the first time and with a bit of help from computers and big data, the Oxford University Press will add Christopher Marlowe as a co-author in all &amp;hellip; Consumer Confidential: Medical Privacy Threatened By &amp;lsquo;Big Data&amp;rsquo; It&amp;rsquo;s the most prominent example of how public and private insurers are spending millions of dollars on big data using advanced technology to &amp;hellip; Predictive World can forecast your future using big data Every day, internet users leave associated data series of over 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Informatica Named a Leader in Hybrid Integration for Enterprises Report by Satellite PR News (press release) Any integration pattern: (data integration, application integrations, big data, IoT, etc.)Any data (on-premise, cloud, structured, unstructured, &amp;hellip; Informatica Big Data Management and PowerCenter on the AWS Cloud &amp;hellip; and transformation without writing or maintaining Apache Hadoop code. &amp;hellip; You can also choose to deploy Big Data Management or PowerCenter into &amp;hellip; Big Data 2016 Market Segmentation,Application,Technology &amp;amp; Market Analysis NewsMaker (press release) WiseGuyReports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Azure Data Lake Service for Big Data Analyses Now Available It has HDInsight, which is Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Hadoop-based Big Data service. Another component is the new Data Lake Store (GA this week), a repository for &amp;hellip; Another View: Big Data failed, but don&amp;rsquo;t discard it In the aftermath of the alleged failure of Big Data on Election Day, many Americans will judge predictions, projections and premonitions with more &amp;hellip; Connotate Raises $11 Million in Follow-on Funding to Support Continued Bobsguide (press release) Their web data extraction platform is at the forefront of big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Capital Markets Firms Upgrade to True Real Time Analytics for Improved Big GlobeNewswire (press release) NEW YORK and LONDON, Nov. 16, 2016 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) &amp;ndash; With the understanding that the value of a piece of data can perish in less than a &amp;hellip; Microsoft offers concessions to EU regulators eyeing its $26.2B LinkedIn TechCrunch A Microsoft spokesperson declined to comment on what concessions it is offering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Yangpu innovation base working with web trends, big data The Yangpu Cloud Computing Innovation Base in Shanghai is on its way to becoming a first-class innovation center in the fields of cloud computing &amp;hellip; Airlines aim to increase revenue and efficiency, improve services using big CAPA - Centre for Aviation SITA president Asia Pacific Ilya Gutlin, speaking at the CAPA Asia Aviation Summit, said (15-Nov-2016) the priorities of airlines in using big data are &amp;hellip; Travel industry well placed to take advantage of big data: Adara Adara VP sales Asia Jonathan Hardy, speaking at the CAPA Asia Aviation Summit, said (15-Nov-2016) the travel industry is well placed to take &amp;hellip; Amazon QuickSight Now Generally Available Fast &amp;amp; Easy to Use Business Amazon QuickSight Now Generally Available Fast &amp;amp; Easy to Use Business Analytics for Big Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Data Science and Big Data, Explained Big data (as defined soon) is a special application of data science. &amp;hellip;. The most popular systems include Apache Hadoop, Cloudera, Hortonworks, and &amp;hellip; How Nike And Under Armour Became Big Data Businesses Like the Yankees vs the Mets, Arsenal vs Tottenham, or Michigan vs Ohio State, Nike and Under Armour are some of the biggest rivals in sports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Faculty Coffee and Networking - Big Data, Machine Learning, and Frontiers The explosion of data is rapidly changing our everyday life and is impacting every aspect of our society, including higher education. This leads to a &amp;hellip; Thesis defence S. Gupta: big data Prof.dr. C. Witteveen (EWI). How President Trump could abuse big data and the surveillance state Jon Stokes is one of the founders of Ars Technica, an author, and a former Wired editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
How Big Data Drives The Sharing Economy The advent of &amp;ldquo;Big Data&amp;rdquo; has resulted in an internet landscape where every major company tracks their users&amp;rsquo; information. When a website warns you &amp;hellip; Big Data And The War For Right Talent Big data starts with the fact that there is a lot more information floating around than ever before, and it is being put to newer usages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
3 Ways Big Data and Machine Learning Affect Consumer Behavior Transformed By AI, Machine Learning And Big Data In The Next Decade &amp;hellip; The Big Data Market: 2016 - 2030 - Opportunities, Challenges, Strategies, PR Newswire (press release) NEW YORK, Nov. 10, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Big Data&amp;rdquo; originally emerged as a term to describe datasets whose size is beyond the ability of traditional &amp;hellip; Big Data Summit: Commercial Breaks Are Hurting Traditional TV, Says Fox&amp;rsquo;s Yahoo TV (blog) Linear television has become disadvantaged as a viewing experience by its reliance on traditional commercial breaks, Fox Networks Group &amp;hellip; How Verizon is Solving Big Data Problems with Interactive BI multi-dimensional OLAP solution that runs natively on Hadoop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Got the Election Wrong; Some Analytic Models Got It Right One poll and a behavioral model seemed to find patterns in the 2016 election that most polls missed. If there&amp;rsquo;s an analytics lesson to be learned from &amp;hellip; The Day Big Data Analytics Died The pre-election big data analytics systems used by pundits, media and prediction markets used incomplete data that resulted in operational &amp;hellip; Yes, Big Data Did Triumph on Election Day Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s win surprised many around the world, but none more than the modelers and big league prognosticators who were calling for a likely &amp;hellip; Lessons for Marketers: Why Big Data got the US Election Wrong tremendous amounts of disparate, parallel data in milliseconds and delivering &amp;hellip; Big Data Security, Privacy and Trust to provide significant benefits, such as the availability of automatic tools to &amp;hellip; Hyundai Motor to Establish Big Data Center in China Hyundai Motor will establish its first global big data center in Guizhou Province, China, to accelerate the development of future connected car &amp;hellip; Big Impact Isn&amp;rsquo;t Big Data A common heuristic for estimating the quality of something is: what has it done for me lately?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Apache Spark Survey Reveals Increased Growth in Users and New Workloads insideBIGDATA In order to better understand Apache Spark&amp;rsquo;s growing role in big data, &amp;hellip; batch, real-time, and advanced analytics on the Apache Hadoop platform. China Sets Up Big Data Zone in Inner Mongolia Xu Shaoshi, chairman of the National Development and Reform Commission, said the commission will draw up policies to bring big data products, &amp;hellip; Big data research papers 2016 ford expensive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
How to Respond When FINRA Comes Knocking Next-generation analytics to manage Big Data, however, are capable of consolidating billions of prior data classifications across documents from prior &amp;hellip; China unveils big data zone being built in Inner Mongolia China unveiled Monday a big data zone being built in Inner Mongolia. The zone, centered at the regional capital Hohhot, is one of the seven under &amp;hellip; Big Data Based Security Solutions Need Of Hour Disruptive technologies such as Big Data and Machine learning can be effective tools to define enterprise&amp;rsquo;s security posture and avert advanced cyber &amp;hellip; SAP adds Microsoft Surface Hub, big data source support to BusinessObjects ZDNet SAP added to its cloud BusinessObjects analytics lineup with support for machine learning and big data sources such as Amazon Redshift, Google &amp;hellip; Big Data Improves Productivity For Oil Companies Modern technologies such as Big Data and Analytics are bringing wide-ranging changes throughout the world across industries and introducing new &amp;hellip; How big data can be used for the development and regulation of medicines November 2016 to identify opportunities for big data in medicines &amp;hellip; A fifth of Dutch companies analyze Big Data A fifth of Dutch companies with at least 10 employees analyze so-called Big Data - large amounts of unstructured data, according to Statistics &amp;hellip; Nearly half Dutch telecom providers using big data analysis A fifth of all Dutch companies with at least 10 employees used big data techniques in 2015, according to a survey by the state statistics bureau CBS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Alibaba looks to expand Singles Day shopping spree beyond China The company is exploiting a trove of big data gathered through its retail, streaming and payment platforms in China, and this year it is launching a pilot &amp;hellip; Big Data Privacy and Why You Should be Concerned Big data privacy is a topic that is becoming increasingly important as the methods we are using to accumulate big data are becoming more &amp;hellip; BRIEF-Hakim Unique Internet to buy 5 pct stake in big data trading firm Reuters BEIJING, Nov 7 China&amp;rsquo;s parliament adopted a controversial cybersecurity law on Monday, the official Xinhua news agency said, a move likely to trigger &amp;hellip; Analytics of Textual Big Data: Text Exploration of the Big Untapped Data Big Data for Enriching Analytical Capabilities Big data is revolutionizing the world of business intelligence and analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data is now the new oil The buzzword in business these days is undoubtedly Big Data. From our PCs and laptops to mobile phones, social media messages and digital &amp;hellip; MapR Big Data Everywhere Roadshow, London Apache Hadoop, Apache Spark and other big data technologies that brings &amp;hellip; Dataguise Powers DgSecure Monitor with Apache Eagle for Immediate Data insideBIGDATA &amp;hellip; Eagle is an open source monitoring platform for instantly identifying security and performance issues on big data platforms such as Apache Hadoop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Was the big bang big data plan simply too much information for CSPs to VanillaPlus (press release) (blog) There are no dumb pipes any more, neither in telecoms or the industries its infrastructures were likened to. In fact, there is an argument to be made &amp;hellip; New Analyst Ratings For WANdisco (LON:WAND) Its technology enables real-time data access across distributed deployments of the open source tools, Hadoop (for Big Data) and Subversion or Git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Banker HSBC Joins UK Data Effort While no stranger to data analysis, observers note that econometrics, a field that has approached big data with caution, increasingly requires a &amp;hellip; Improving urban environment with 3D modeling and big data 3D modeling and big data technology can be applied to simulate the combined effects of multiform changes in the urban environment. Photo: ForCity. Barclays Capital Upgraded Talend (NASDAQ:TLND) To &amp;lsquo;Overweight&amp;rsquo; The Company&amp;rsquo;s platform enables users to connect data and applications on-premise or in the cloud, in real time or in batch, Big Data or reference data &amp;hellip; Data Science Initiative to offer one-year master&amp;rsquo;s Big data drives research in nearly every field, wrote Provost Richard Locke P&amp;rsquo;17 in an email to The Herald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
IBM Gives &amp;lsquo;Cognitive&amp;rsquo; Businesses an All-Flash Edge &amp;hellip; File System (GPFS), it offers unified file and object storage management and support for the big data-friendly Hadoop distributed file system (HDFS). UNC Health Care Looks to Big Data to Reduce Readmissions UNC Health Care is a sprawling enterprise with huge amounts of data flowing across six hospitals, including an academic medical center, a cancer &amp;hellip; Practical Deep Learning in Theano and TensorFlow He has created new big data pipelines using Hadoop/Pig/MapReduce, and created machine learning models to predict click-through rate, news feed &amp;hellip; Dell EMC Hortonworks Hadoop Reference Architecture &amp;hellip; for information on configuring Hortonworks Data Platform Hadoop clusters within their information technology environment for big data analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data and Voters: Federal Judge Set To Hear Purging Case A federal judge in Winston-Salem will hear arguments Wednesday over the recent cancellations of up to 4,500 voter registrations. The North Carolina &amp;hellip; Big Data Reveals Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s Plays Had Marlowe As Collaborator ! Using new-era technology such as Big Data and Analytics, it is now confirmed that the world&amp;rsquo;s greatest playwright William Shakespeare collaborated &amp;hellip; UAE Shipping Association breakfast on Big Data but not ready to feast That was the takeaway from a business breakfast where smart shipping thought leaders shared Big Data intel and opportunities with a small &amp;hellip; WHITE 2016: Health Care Poised for Big Data &amp;lsquo;Arms Race&amp;rsquo; annual workshop, hosted by the Center for Health Information and Decision &amp;hellip; The Big Data Market to 2016 - 2030 : Vendor Market Share, Challenges, openPR (press release) Big Data originally emerged as a term to describe datasets whose size is beyond the ability of traditional databases to capture, store, manage and &amp;hellip; 10 Places to Study Big Data Analytics Online Big Data analytics is among the fastest developing fields in enterprise technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
RAC maps big data future with Microsoft Azure cloud RAC has turned to Microsoft to boost the scale of its telematics platform and to create new data services. The motoring organisation is adopting &amp;hellip; 5 Big Data And Analytics Learning Resources That Most People Miss (But Forbes It&amp;rsquo;s 2016, and pretty much everybody who&amp;rsquo;s interested in analytics (or politics or sports) has read a bit of FiveThirtyEight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
TFRecord file support with Hadoop Mapreduce/Spark this Issue 2 minutes ago 0 comments &amp;hellip; Big Data: Advancing Science, Changing the World Symposium, Big Data: Advancing Science, Changing the World. The symposium &amp;hellip; There&amp;rsquo;s More To Big Data Than Just Big Data (By Bob McCurdy) Big data is getting a lot of headlines and has made the process of purchasing media more sophisticated over the past several years &amp;hellip; A manual for citizens taking on the machines O&amp;rsquo;Neil brings the ethical quandaries arising from the use of big data into sharp focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
How One University Used Big Data To Boost Graduation Rates Whenever you surf the web, sophisticated algorithms are tracking where you go, comparing you with millions of other people. They&amp;rsquo;re trying to predict &amp;hellip; How One University Used Big Data To Boost Graduation Rates go, comparing you with millions of other people. They&amp;rsquo;re trying to predict. China issues first big data report on B&amp;amp;R Initiative Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
The Guardian view on big data: segmentation feeds discrimination Facebook&amp;rsquo;s ability to offer real estate advertising to the exclusion of certain ethnic groups is a worrying illustration of the power of big data. Photograph: &amp;hellip; Meet October&amp;rsquo;s Big Data Hero part of our work to address the Big Data skills gap. Big Data Analytics for Sport: MSM shares expertise on global platform October 2016. On 4 October 2016, Davy Cielen, Senior Lecturer in Business &amp;hellip; Stocks Buzz: AbbVie (ABBV), Teradata (TDC) Valero Energy (VLO) &amp;hellip; and support services for data warehousing and big data analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Ten Chinese Angel Firms Jointly Launch AI-Big Data Accelerator Ten Chinese angel and venture firms, including the Zhen Fund, Innovation Angel Funds and CAS Star, have jointly launched an accelerator focused &amp;hellip; Big Data and the cloud: match made in (data) heaven Organizations today are flooded with big data from a growing number of sources. According to Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, the global data traffic will cross 100 &amp;hellip; China issues first big data report on B&amp;amp;R Initiative China released its first big data report on the Belt and Road Initiative &amp;ldquo;Belt and Road in Big Data 2016&amp;rdquo; in Beijing on Oct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Trends: Real Time, Stateful Customer Engagement More recently, Gartner surveys indicate that Big Data strategies based on Hadoop and map reduce have met similar outcomes, with 49 percent of &amp;hellip; Best Telco Big Data Analytics Platform Europe&amp;rsquo; summit, Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Big Data analytics platform (FusionInsight-Universe &amp;hellip; What Can Big Data Analytics Do? Rewrite History: eDiscovery Trends In the Washington Post article Big debate about Shakespeare finally settled by big data: Marlowe gets his due by Travis M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big data reveals mixed authorship in 17 Shakespeare plays A book of Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s plays, the &amp;lsquo;first folio&amp;rsquo; dating back to 1623 and containing 451 out of the original 454 leaves, at Sotheby&amp;rsquo;s auctioneers in &amp;hellip; Optus and La Trobe invest AU$8m to create cybersecurity degree, digital ZDNet The partnership between the two will see them focus on the &amp;ldquo;significant challenges&amp;rdquo; of cybersecurity, smart cities, and big data, Optus said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Former AOL Counsel, Big Data Expert Joins Venable as Partner in Privacy, Corporate Counsel (registration) Law firm Venable recently announced the addition of former AOL Inc. chief counsel Charles D. Curran as a partner in its privacy and data security &amp;hellip; Big data and social media research papers Potsdam suny admissions essay. Theorizing modernism essays in critical &amp;hellip; In association with Swiss Re, Baden-Baden Today conducted a survey Big data provides a tremendous opportunity for the industry to reignite and reimagine its purpose in society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Analytics services to overcome in-house data gaps in Asia Pacific Big data and analytics is the new, cloud-enabled frontier for companies capitalise on, to speed up business growth and develop and maintain their &amp;hellip; Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Jack Ma Urges China to Use Online Data to Fight Crime Chinese billionaire Jack Ma proposed that the nation&amp;rsquo;s top security bureau use big data to prevent crime, endorsing the country&amp;rsquo;s nascent effort to build &amp;hellip; Apollo Hospitals uses big data analytics to control Hospital Acquired ETCIO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
China&amp;rsquo;s government harnesses big data for citizen rating system BEIJING Imagine a world where an authoritarian government monitors everything you do, amasses huge amounts of data on nearly every &amp;hellip; In insurance Big Data could lower rates for optimistic tweeters This could lead to future insurance cover based on &amp;ldquo;sentiment analysis&amp;rdquo;, in which Big Data and artificial intelligence make predictive models ever more &amp;hellip; In insurance Big Data could lower rates for optimistic tweeters comment on the great evening they enjoyed with good food and &amp;hellip; Solving Big Problems With Big Data &amp;amp; Cancer Moonshot Founder of Civis Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
The Amazing Ways Citigroup Is Using Big Data To Improve Bank Performance As the foundation for its Big Data strategy, Citi has invested in its own &amp;hellip; the whale geologist and the radio astronomer Two speakers at this year&amp;rsquo;s TEDxChristchurch event are using big data to stretch knowledge in wildly different fields. Will Harvie reports. Two scientists &amp;hellip; 5 Reasons to Attend Data Natives 2016: #5: Best Kept Secrets Last, but not least, comes the Big Data in FinTech panel, which features a mixture of newcomers to the FinTech space, represented by Devie Mohan, &amp;hellip; How SAP started addressing cloud demands of SMBs SAP&amp;rsquo;s multipronged big data approach will enable customers to process and analyze Hadoop data with Altiscale in the cloud, or to do the same on &amp;hellip; ClassNK wins Big Data Award at the Lloyd&amp;rsquo;s List Asia Awards Leading classification society ClassNK picked up the Lloyd&amp;rsquo;s List Intelligence Big Data Award for its condition based monitoring suite ClassNK CMAXS &amp;hellip; New strategic credit weapons in the 2017 banking battle on cost income This is a missed opportunity as it keeps big data and machine learning in an infant testing phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
HelloFresh Optimizes Fresh Meal Delivery Experience Worldwide HelloFresh selected a data platform based on Hadoop and other big data technologies after realizing its home-brewed business intelligence solution &amp;hellip; Guizhou villagers join the digital revolution Today Guizhou is investing in education to try to establish itself as a global big-data and cloud-computing center. It might be largely overlooked by &amp;hellip; The Sharing Economy - What It Is, Examples, And How Big Data, Platforms And Forbes In the future, we may own much less and share much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
NxtGen adopts Cloudera for its new analytics service They can use NxtGen&amp;rsquo;s hyper-converged infrastructure and now big data analytics as service as well to minimize on cost and maximize on capabilities. First Big Data center to appear in Azerbaijan British BP and the ADA University have announced about creation of the first Scientific-Research and Training Center Big Data in Azerbaijan. How Ford Is Solving Problems Using Data And Analytics Previously, Ford Motor Company had a whole range of different data and analytics teams, as most companies likely do: one for manufacturing, one for &amp;hellip; Get Smart Turning PV Big Data into Actionable Information There is a tremendous amount of data available from PV plants today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Deals: Master The Tools Of Big Data Analytics When companies need to make big decisions, they call in their Big Data experts to help them understand the whole picture. Packed with training in &amp;hellip; Running sparklyr RStudio&amp;rsquo;s R Interface to Spark on Amazon EMR provides the latest version of Spark and other Hadoop ecosystem &amp;hellip; Big data has arrived, not big insights: Suresh Acharya, JDA Labs : I imagine a lot of what you folks are working on revolves around big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
With Alimama and YunOS in tow, Alibaba is set to reach &amp;lsquo;Cloud 9 with a big e27 In a collaboration with the National Astronomical Observatory of China, Alibaba Cloud will help develop a cloud-based Big Data platform to support its &amp;hellip; BIG DATA is on ERSA Agenda on November 22 creative way to tackle key issues in today&amp;rsquo;s regional policy like smart &amp;hellip; Big Data SQL Quick Start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Is Data Analytics The Panacea For Better HR Management? The challenge with data is that they are usually an indicator and not the absolute truth. While Big Data analytics has made a favorable impact on many &amp;hellip; One Of Asia&amp;rsquo;s Leading HR Execs Discusses How Big Data Can Help You Hire Forbes Is it possible to predict if your team&amp;rsquo;s best performer is going to leave you in six months?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Where do you Begin with your (Big) Data Initiative? like a data warehouse, analytical tools, or perhaps event to invest in Hadoop. Microsoft Azure HDInsight Big Data Analyst source technologies like Hadoop, Spark, Storm, and HBase on the Microsoft &amp;hellip; How Organizations Build Back-Ends for Big Data Change is always based on decisions and just about every Fortune 500 company knows that any important decision is always based on big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
HR profession bitten by the data bug, but here&amp;rsquo;s why it must be handled Financial Express The HR profession has been bitten by a bug; using big data, analytics and numbers to predict organisational and individual behaviour. The theory of &amp;hellip; Obama Health Care: US President Promises Better Patient Care through Data iTech Post Patients will have complete access to their medical history, and with big data being utilized by the health care system, treatments can be individualized &amp;hellip; Big data analytics the next step in security Kathy Gibson reports from Huawei Safe City Summit in Nairobi Ensuring the security of citizens will eventually go beyond surveillance and response, &amp;hellip; Top Big Data Stocks to Buy Today way a number of powerful software providers add value for their &amp;hellip; Award for EEMCS team in Big Data Apache Spark hackathon won the $25000 2nd prize in the Big Data Apache Spark hackathon &amp;hellip; CREDIT SUISSE: Tech Talk on Big Data and Interview Tips Session industries, in financial services and at Credit Suisse from Nan Lu, a Vice President in &amp;hellip; Big Data: Finding value in diverse types of data Similarly, businesses today find value in bringing together diverse types of data in the search for competitive insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Maths becomes biology&amp;rsquo;s magic number The answer can be summed up in two words: big data. What Dr Sottoriva brings to the fight against cancer is the expertise in mathematical modelling &amp;hellip; Hadoop, Storm, Samza, Spark, and Flink: Big Data Frameworks Compared technologies needed to gather, organize, process, and gather insights from large &amp;hellip; UA Uses Big Data To Solve Bus Woes In Brazil In Fortaleza &amp;ndash; the fifth-largest city in Brazil &amp;ndash; cars jam the streets, bicycles weave through traffic and bus stops are crowded with passengers who might &amp;hellip; Time for Hong Kong to catch up on Big Data Hong Kong has lagged far behind mainland China and the United States in the field of big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
UA Uses Big Data to Solve Bus Woes in Brazil Fortaleza, Brazil&amp;rsquo;s fifth-largest city, struggles with bus delays and overcrowding. The city&amp;rsquo;s mayor, a UA alumnus, turned to big-data experts at his alma &amp;hellip; How to Use Big Data to Sell in Account Management Even people who regularly work with big data can get lost in the mire and draw false conclusions. As the number of ways to collect data increases, the &amp;hellip; Applying Big Data Analytics to Tackle 3 Financial Marketing Challenges Embracing big data and analyzing both internal and external data, structured and unstructured, can help bank and credit union marketers keep pace &amp;hellip; Personalised doesn&amp;rsquo;t make it personal With so much hyper-targeted communication missing the mark, advertisers must reassess the role of big data in building relationships, writes VCCP&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; Libraries Pool Big Data Analytics Investments Ten libraries joined together to use a big data analytics service that applies fuzzy logic technology to card catalog data to identify patterns and trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Baidu hopes big data can improve care for patients Teaming up with healthcare professionals , China &amp;lsquo; s internet search giant Baidu has launched &amp;ldquo; Medical Brain &amp;rdquo; to help patients and doctors by &amp;hellip; Weapons of Math Destruction: How Big Data Increases Inequality Report is a daily progressive talk show and Podcast hosted by Sam Seder. Talend Announces Strategic Big Data Partnership with T-Systems cloud ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Moritz&amp;rsquo;s Distinguished Lecture to tackle big data governance vs. Moritz College of Law will host a Distinguished Lecture on Oct. 27 of one of today&amp;rsquo;s hottest topics not just in data analytics but in society: balancing the &amp;hellip; DHL: Using Big Data for Better Deliveries This involves the application big data technologies, including cross-referencing the names and addresses provided by shippers to databases of postal &amp;hellip; Why preparation is key to securing your cloud migration The benefits of big data are real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Why Java in Big Data? What about Scala? Apache NiFi is written in Java and so is most of Hadoop, so it&amp;rsquo;s Big Data &amp;hellip; Python has its own huge ecosystem, but for many Hadoop things the JVM &amp;hellip; 5 Amazing Things Big Data Helps Us To Predict Now &amp;ndash; Plus What&amp;rsquo;s On The Forbes Big data is predicting things about your life almost every minute of your day &amp;hellip; But today, big data can provide accurate snapshots of current weather &amp;hellip; SMEs Struggle To Find The Cash To Invest $203 billion to be spent on Big Data analytics solutions by 2020, said IDC, highlighting banking and manufacturing as the industries that will fuel this &amp;hellip; WANdisco strengthens boardroom after winning largest big data contract As well as securing two sizeable contracts, big data software developer WANdisco&amp;rsquo;s boardroom drama continued as it appointed a new non-executive &amp;hellip; More money in big data initiatives, Gartner argues but is the ROI still Cloud Tech A recent report from Forrester Research found that, in terms of big data technologies, NoSQL and Hadoop were forecast to grow the quickest, with the &amp;hellip; Big data industry development trends, competitive landscape and key regions WhaTech Global Big Data Market 2016 Research Report initially provides a basic overview of the industry that covers definition, applications and manufacturing &amp;hellip; Above the Trend Line Your Industry Rumor Central for 10/10/2016 In this week&amp;rsquo;s installment of our regular Big Data roundup, we&amp;rsquo;ll start with some M&amp;amp;A news insightsoftware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Turning data into a strategic asset industries with an overview of the use of Big Data in business and how &amp;hellip; Big data revenue to jump 50pc to $187bn Big data and business analytics revenues will grow from nearly $122 billion in 2015 to over $187 billion in 2019, an increase of more than 50 per cent, &amp;hellip; EXCLUSIVE - High Performance Computing resources and big data visualisation OpenGov Asia That&amp;rsquo;s a problem we haven&amp;rsquo;t had to deal with before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
This Week in Hadoop and More: Strata NYC 2016 Edition This Week in Hadoop and More: Strata NYC 2016 Edition &amp;hellip; Websocket Server is an interesting product that could be used for big data dashboards. Techonomics: Big Data Collection with Toby Ault of Cornell University Toby Ault from Cornell University about collecting and using data to &amp;hellip; Shorting Attunity Ltd Could be a Low Risk Trade Small cap Attunity Ltd is a leading provider of Big Data management &amp;hellip; a global corporation has chosen Attunity Replicate for Hadoop as a strategic &amp;hellip; Big Data Analytics in the Cloud quick and future-proof decisions and thereby provide a significant advantage &amp;hellip; #Know Your Data: The Key to Business Last week&amp;rsquo;s Strata-Hadoop conference in New York, NY was showcase of how big data is redefining business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Qantas and GE hunt for cost and carbon reduction in big data GE Aviation launched its fourth digital collaboration centre in its Digital Solutions headquarters in Austin, Texas today, with Qantas as its launch &amp;hellip; Key Capabilities for Big Data Analytics using R Big Data SQL, where users can reference Hadoop data, e.g., as stored &amp;hellip; Report Looks at the Possible State of AI in 2030 Stanford recently produced a report that looks ahead to 2030 to see how AI might impact urban life, and it is more of a discussion starter than a &amp;hellip; The coherent enforcement of fundamental rights in the age of big data personal information Big Iron Marries Big Data and Opportunity in the Mobile Chaos This intersection of &amp;lsquo;big iron&amp;rsquo; and big data simply put, the challenge is, how do we add a digital layer to GE machines so our customers know when &amp;hellip; Big Data for Pharma, Philadelphia 2016 With big data and analytics technologies re-shaping the pharmaceutical &amp;hellip; Big data processing enables worldwide bacterial analysis Archive, a public database for deposition of sequences, currently &amp;hellip; Big Data Help CIA Predict Social Unrest 5 Days Before It Begins The CIA started a new future-proof division that will enable it to predict social unrest a few days before it happens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Is Your Big Data Project a Weapon of Math Destruction? For those of us who make a living solving problems, the current deluge of big data might seem like a wonderland. Data scientists and programmers &amp;hellip; Struggling Honeybees Get Some Help From Big Data Scientists at Grand Valley State University are using new technology to track the health of honeybee hives in real time. Credit Rebecca Williams &amp;hellip; How AI, Drones and Big Data Are Reshaping The Future Of Warfare Big data and IoT are transforming how wars are being fought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Dhiraj Rajaram buys out former wife&amp;rsquo;s stake in PE-backed Big Data firm Mu VCCircle The founder of data analytics firm Mu Sigma Inc., Dhiraj Rajaram, is back as the CEO of the company after his former wife Ambiga Subramanian &amp;hellip; Big Data and business analytics a $200 billion industry Big data and business analytics are set for double digit growth, with new forecasts from industry analyst firm IDC reporting the global market to grow to &amp;hellip; Gartner warns Big Data&amp;rsquo;s bubble may burst as enterprises plot investments SiliconANGLE (blog) &amp;hellip; dozens of startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Car data could be a much bigger business than electric or driverless Business Insider &amp;hellip; in the deeply experimental phase, we might be overlooking the largest new business to emerge as cars are increasingly enmeshed with Big Data. Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Big Data &amp;amp; Analytics Platform for Data Scientists Advanced Analytics for Hadoop (ORAAH), Big Data Discovery (BDD), &amp;hellip; Weapons of math destruction: how big data and algorithms affect our lives - The Guardian In this very special episode, Ian Sample and Leigh Alexander delve into the weird and not-so-wonderful world of algorithms, uncovering how they&amp;rsquo;re &amp;hellip; Blog: Ten years on, telcos chase mindset shift It was certainly a dj vu experience at the 5G Asia conference last week when the discussion at a big data analytics panel turned to the continued &amp;hellip; How data analytics will change the risk and insurance industryand your PropertyCasualty360 The insurance industry is not immune to this rising trend, and big data has &amp;hellip; Similar leaps in big data use are expected in loss control and claims &amp;hellip; Gartner Survey Reveals Investment in Big Data Is Up but Fewer Organizations Big data investments continue to rise but are showing signs of contracting, according to a recent survey by Gartner, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Lyme disease: the promise of Big Data, companion diagnostics and precision ProHealth Lyme disease caused by the spirochete Borrelia burgdorferi has become a major worldwide epidemic. Recent studies based on Big Data registries &amp;hellip; Big Data News: The Top Insights From Strata + Hadoop World 2016 In New York Just about every player in the Big Data and analytics game was in New York last week at the Strata + Hadoop World conference, to showcase their &amp;hellip; RavenPack Expands Premium Content Coverage in Big Data Analytics by Benzinga RavenPack, the leading provider of big data analytics to financial institutions will begin processing content from The Fly, a premium digital publisher of &amp;hellip; Varsity don delivers lecture in Istanbul - Amritsar NYOOOZ &amp;hellip; in digital imaging, cryptography, colour visual cryptography, climate change, feature extraction and big data analysis, besides image reconstruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Utilise the power of enterprise Hadoop with Attunity and Hortonworks Attunity and Hortonworks solutions to meet enterprise big data challenges. The Backbone of Big Data Governance: Unified Terminology&amp;rsquo;s Role in Metadata In this article in AnalyticsWeek, several business analytics thought leaders, including Cambridge Semantics&amp;rsquo; VP of Financial Services Marty Loughlin, &amp;hellip; Disruptive Technology, Monotonous Marketing At Strata+Hadoop World O&amp;rsquo;Reilly&amp;rsquo;s New York-based Strata+Hadoop World conference is one of the largest big data conferences in the world today, featuring hundreds of &amp;hellip; Taking a Peek into the Future of Big Data Big Data can be defined as the data that is so big that it cannot be analyzed or mined for information using the traditional data processing application &amp;hellip; Small groups mine big data to feed growth A British snack start-up took a bold and unusual step this year when it asked one of the UK&amp;rsquo;s biggest supermarket groups to remove a third of its range &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Oct 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-10-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
EIT Digital: Digital transformation based on Big Data and Cloud However, exploitation of big data technologies in cloud is not easy for many companies, especially SMEs. They struggle to find a convenient and &amp;hellip; Maturing of Hadoop in the Enterprise As the big data conference season winds down for 2016, I believe that one of the key trends we can see prevalent across the board is that the Apache &amp;hellip; Hackathon examines power of Big Data to change lives Entire mountain ranges of data are growing all around, and they will either bury us or help us climb to new heights of understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Review Of &amp;lsquo;Weapons Of Math Destruction&amp;rsquo; By Cathy O&amp;rsquo;Neil &amp;hellip; a Big Data startup, to design an algorithm to distinguish buyers from mere window shoppers. O&amp;rsquo;Neil found parallels between finance and Big Data. IBM Solidified Its Business Analytics Ecosystem Project DataWorks is actually a big data analytics platform which primarily consists of two most sought-after software suites of today, which are IBM &amp;hellip; Hortonworks Accelerates Cloud Innovation for Customers with Microsoft Azure Broadway World The Forrester Wave: Big Data Hadoop Cloud Solutions, Q2 2016 report calls out that &amp;ldquo;enterprises of all types and sizes are increasingly embracing the &amp;hellip; Who is Doing Big Data: A SAGE Survey us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
From tourism to big data, Chinese province presents itself in Silicon Xinhua Photo taken on Sept. 27, 2016 shows the scene of an event to promote tourism in China&amp;rsquo;s Guizhou Province, held in San Francisco, the United States. Smarter Big Data Analytics For Distributed Semiconductor High Volume Semiconductor companies are racing to compete in the highly competitive IoT era, developing products that will collect and transmit sensor data &amp;hellip; The new dynamics of big data Mike Olson discusses the new dynamics of big data and how a renewed &amp;hellip; Doug Cutting, Tom White, and Ben Lorica explore Hadoop&amp;rsquo;s role over the &amp;hellip; $10 million in &amp;lsquo;Big Data Spokes&amp;rsquo; awards announced The National Science Foundation (NSF) announced $10 million in Big Data Spokes awards to initiate research in specific areas identified, supported &amp;hellip; NSF Backs &amp;lsquo;Big Data Spokes&amp;rsquo; with $10M in Grants Future challenges for the community involve moving neuroscience toward big data and data science and developing methods to capture, harmonize &amp;hellip; Addressing Environmental Challenges with Big Data and Artificial The NSF&amp;rsquo;s $10 million initiative was created to improve the ability to solve the nation&amp;rsquo;s most pressing challenges with the use of big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Applications Now ODPi Interoperable, Provide Increased Simplicity Yahoo Finance The ODPi Interoperable Compliance Program is an ongoing commitment between Apache Hadoop platforms, big data solution and application &amp;hellip; White House, Google, Amazon Launch Big Data Tool to Help with Climate Sustainable Brands A variety of data can already be explored on the new Partnership for Resilience &amp;amp; Preparedness (PREP) web portal, such as these large scale &amp;hellip; Five New Pentaho Data Integration Enhancements, Including SQL on Spark, New Spark and Kafka support, Metadata Injection enhancements and Hadoop security alleviate big data complexity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Heard Of &amp;lsquo;Big Data&amp;rsquo;? Here&amp;rsquo;s Why Its About To Change M&amp;rsquo;sian Businesses In malaysiandigest.com This is achieved through analysing vast amounts of data, a process known as Big Data Analytics (BDA), which uncovers useful information for &amp;hellip; Opera Solutions Closes $70 Million Financing 26, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Opera Solutions, LLC, a global leader in applied Big Data analytics and artificial intelligence (AI), has announced that it has &amp;hellip; Accuritas Global Solutions Selected as a Finalist for the 2016 Lloyd&amp;rsquo;s List PR Newswire (press release) The big data award recognizes companies that have influenced the &amp;hellip; with customized big data solutions, analytics, and business intelligence for all &amp;hellip; Big data can help get travel moving forward FILE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Podium Data wants to offer a complete data wrangling platform The founding team has broad experience within the big data industry, &amp;hellip; dataincluding legacy files and massive digital dataonto Hadoop-based &amp;hellip; Big data can help get travel moving forward IN THE field of public transport, SA is battling some unique challenges. These include the legacies of historical urban planning programmes, complex &amp;hellip; 3rd International Conference on Big Data Analysis and Data Mining September The Hudson Reporter 3rd International Conference on Big Data Analysis and Data Mining provides a perfect platform for scientists, engineers, directors of companies and &amp;hellip; BCF says Big Data is Comeback Key Super Retail Group say big data and content creation will feature heavily in transforming BCF into positive gear, with technology to play a huge role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
How big data can help the housing crisis Amazingly, Ireland still relies on connections to the electricity grid to measure new dwellings being 1 Amazingly, Ireland still relies on connections to &amp;hellip; Informatica Data Lake Package Aims to Bring Clarity to Disparate Data The rise of big data has also seen a huge demand for data scientists to help companies &amp;hellip; The big data dilemma is often compared to bodies of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Sherman To Steer Combo Product, Big Data, Patient-Centered Issues As FDA Inside Health Policy (subscription) Sherman is expected to steer efforts to overhaul combination product reviews, inject big data into regulatory decisions, adopt patient-centered &amp;hellip; CounterTack Recognized as Innovative US Army Venture-Backed Startup (Learn about CounterTack Sentinel, the industry&amp;rsquo;s only Big Data Endpoint Detection and Response solution. See how organizations can better protect &amp;hellip; Impact of Big Data on Category Management discusses how the use of Big Data and data analytics will impact the success of &amp;hellip; CenturyLink, Cloudera To Jointly Develop A Big Data-As-A-Service Solution Cloudera and CenturyLink are jointly developing a cloud-based big data &amp;hellip; is built on Apache Hadoop and the latest open source technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Get Unlimited Access to Over 130 Data Analytics Courses Every business creates a huge quantity that needs storing, and Big Data experts get the job done. You can add yourself to this elite group of tech &amp;hellip; smartTrade Technologies launches cross-asset big data analytics solution LeapRate Multi-asset electronic trading solutions provider smartTrade Technologies has announced the launch of smartAnalytics, a cross-asset big data &amp;hellip; Using BigQuery to Analyze PHP on GitHub exciting summer for Google BigQuery, with the release of Standard SQL &amp;hellip; IAB, DMA study says big data potential blocked by lack of talent, silos Marketing organizations that aren&amp;rsquo;t making the most of big data are inhibited by a lack of talent within their teams and organizational silos, according to &amp;hellip; How Machine Learning, Big Data and AI Are Changing Healthcare Forever While robots and computers will probably never completely replace doctors and nurses, machine learning/deep learning and AI are transforming the &amp;hellip; Good Things Come in Small(er) Docker Packages!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big data and public service delivery - big hype? future of public service delivery will not go unchanged by the prospect of &amp;hellip; Talent Shortage and Organizational Silos Are Obstacles in Delivering on SHOOT Online The IAB Data Center of Excellence and DMA, the largest U.S. data and marketing association, have released The Data-Centric Organization, a &amp;hellip; The Institutes creates new designation in response to big data&amp;rsquo;s impact on Insurance Business America According to The Institutes, it created the AIDA designation after it had recognized big data and business technology&amp;rsquo;s impacts on the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Deals: Learn To Master Big Data With This Training Course In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world, virtually every business relies on Big Data to make important decisions. With the Very Big Hadoop &amp;amp; Apache Big Data &amp;hellip; KT, UN Join Hands to Build Big Data-based Global Contagion Prevention BusinessKorea KT chairman Hwang Chang-gyu, center, poses for a photo with UNGC executive director Lise Kingo, left, and UNGC Foundation chairman Sir Mark &amp;hellip; 6 Problems the Internet of Things and Big Data Solve Hand in hand, Big Data and IoT are working to change the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
What&amp;rsquo;s next in big data? looking to bring big data to the forefront of everyday operations. 1. How To Scale Business Intelligence With Hadoop- Based Platforms Analyzing big data poses multiple challenges. Highly parallel distributed data architecture is one solution, but until recently it has been mostly limited &amp;hellip; Big data, mobile apps fuel surge in fintech venture funding Fueled by trends in mobile computing and big data, funding for venture-backed startups in financial technology has risen sharply in recent years, &amp;hellip; KT, UN to build big data contagion prevention system South Korean telco KT and the United Nations (UN) have signed a MOU to build a big data system that will be used for global contagion prevention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Virginia Tech and Drexel University partner for workshop on ethics in big The workshop set for Sept. 29-30 will focus on how collaboration can help meet big data challenges in complex environments. Welcome to the exciting world of open and big data! hackathon in Estonia, where data enthusiasts have a chance to build &amp;hellip; Malaysia on track to become Southeast Asian hub on big data &amp;amp; analytics KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia is making steady progress in becoming a big data and analytics (BDA) hub in Southeast Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Plenary 8 - Big Data IG Session IG Session. 3 reads. Big Data IG. Status: Recognised &amp;amp; Endorsed. Chair(s): &amp;hellip; Top 21 Presentations From Hadoop Summit Melbourne A categorized list of the best presentations from last weeks Hadoop Summit Melbourne focusing on Hive, Spark, Security, Administration and Cloud. EDPS-BEUC CONFERENCE ON BIG DATA: INDIVIDUAL RIGHTS AND SMART ENFORCEMENT EDPS-BEUC CONFERENCE ON BIG DATA: INDIVIDUAL RIGHTS AND SMART ENFORCEMENT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
The Power of Integrated Innovation in Big Data with complex and novel technology and often failing. Simplifying the &amp;hellip; Big data gives insight into appeal of services like uber Date: September 16, 2016; Source: University of Chicago; Summary: In a novel test of the benefit a company can generate for consumers, a new study &amp;hellip; Big Data: Advancing Science, Changing the World Big Data: Advancing Science, Changing the World, at the Michigan &amp;hellip; Wipro, Reltio to develop cost effective MDM solutions Wipro&amp;rsquo;s experience in global MDM implementations and machine learning coupled with Reltio&amp;rsquo;s big data technology and unique commercial graph &amp;hellip; How to Plan Your Big Data Analytics Journey with SAP HANA While it&amp;rsquo;s an intense process to purchase SAP HANA appliances, train your &amp;hellip; How to Use Machine Learning to Further Retail Analytic Capacity He is passionate about machine learning and big data, and enjoys providing enterprise retailers with the tools and knowledge needed to enhance &amp;hellip; New Broker Ratings For Attunity Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
In the Loop with Hadoop - Take Advantage of Data Locality with mongo-hadoop Spark and Hadoop jobs to run quickly. Each worker node in a Spark or Hadoop &amp;hellip; Interactive Debugging for Big Data Analytics of distributed technologies such as Hadoop and Spark, which provide simple &amp;hellip; Pursuing a big data vision: key considerations For forward-thinking businesses that are already harnessing the power of big data, the benefits are endless, enabling real-time adjustments, highly &amp;hellip; Big data approach predicts drug toxicity in humans detects toxic side effects that may disqualify drugs from human use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Classic SQL, NoSQL, New SQL, IMDBs, and IMDGs Simplified My first opportunity to dive into the big data landscape was a real eye opener. So many products suppose to have the solution to big data problems, &amp;hellip; The Disrupters: The New York Times&amp;rsquo; Steve Lohr on the future of big data American Enterprise Institute Coal, iron ore, and oil fueled the Industrial Revolution. The vital raw materials of today&amp;rsquo;s information economy are data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Fintech venture takes on hedge funds with earnings estimates derived from The Japan Times Nowcast already provides information on consumer prices in real time and will use similar technology to analyze big data, starting with retail-sales &amp;hellip; BRIEF-Zhongchang Marine to change name to ZHONGCHANG BIG DATA (The following statement was released by the rating agency) HONG KONG, September 13 (Fitch) Fitch Ratings has affirmed Chinese diesel engine &amp;hellip; BRIEF-Zhongchang Marine to change name to ZHONGCHANG BIG DATA DENVER, Sept 13 The movie theater chain that owns a Colorado cinema where 12 people were killed in a 2012 shooting spree will not pursue &amp;hellip; NIIT shines on launching Big Data with Hadoop under DigiNxt Series NIIT has launched Big Data with Hadoop a futuristic program in data analytics under the DigiNxt Series, designed to optimize data usage and leading &amp;hellip; Getting Off to a Great Start in Your Big Data Career Big data has plenty of tools to work with, so getting familiar with them should be a priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big data management platform Datorama raises $32M There are two problems facing marketers today. First, there&amp;rsquo;s more data than ever before. Second, it&amp;rsquo;s changing quickly, with different types of data, &amp;hellip; IFITT Talk in Customer Engagement &amp;amp; Big Data in Tourism IFITTTalk was structured into two major sessions each one featuring four presentations and a discussion panel provided by leading authorities and &amp;hellip; EPAM and Sinequa Partner to Solve Cognitive Search and Analytics Challenges Yahoo Sports The combination of EPAMs strong Big Data solutions practice and Sinequas unique Cognitive Search and Analytics platform offers customers the &amp;hellip; Rejlers invests in Smart Grid and Big Data There is huge potential in this for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Just not cricket: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s big data Googly declared No Ball bowled by The Register Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s attempt to re-write one of cricket&amp;rsquo;s oddest rules has been rejected by its statistical guardian. This story starts with India&amp;rsquo;s mania for cricket &amp;hellip; Meet The MIP MBA Bringing Big Data Analytics To Italy&amp;rsquo;s Bars And Clubs Alongside a full-time role at Italian IT services firm Cabel, he works every day after work to develop his big data-crunching startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data is Watching You: If predictive analytics still doesn&amp;rsquo;t creep you The biggest fad in child welfare right now is predictive analytics pushing child protective services agencies to use algorithms to decide when &amp;hellip; Live from SMM: Big data changes business model SEPTEMBER 11, 2016Unlocking big data is a key to making shipping more efficient. But securing that data is also critical. With most of the &amp;hellip; How to Fix the Problem When Big Data Fails in Digital Media Planning Natural systems have a closed loop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Western Digital/Unisplendour JV to Boost Big Data in China The venture will focus on selling storage devices as well as big data services in China. This deal will expand Western Digital&amp;rsquo;s presence in China &amp;hellip; Enterprise Big Data Startup IQLECT Set to Disrupt Business Analytic Space, PR Web (press release) Real time data analytics company IQLECT, the enterprise big data startup from &amp;hellip; In the same report Gartner says that through 2018, 70% of Hadoop &amp;hellip; The Very Big Hadoop &amp;amp; Apache Big Data Training Bundle Companies Run on Big Data: Become An In-Demand Hadoop &amp;hellip; IBM&amp;rsquo;s new servers to propel AI, Deep Learning &amp;amp; Advanced Analytics With the result, the company is now integrating the new servers into its hyperscale data center for big data workloads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Data science expert interview: Andrew Oliver Hadoop. Tags: data science, Spark, R, Hadoop, predictive analytics, Data &amp;hellip; ESA&amp;rsquo;s Justin Antonipillai to Keynote Boston Big Data Innovation Summit the Economics and Statistics Administration (ESA) will deliver the keynote &amp;hellip; Big data show K-pop stretching from Asia to US SEOUL, Sept. 8 (Yonhap) The South Korean pop culture has expanded in size and market from Asia to the North American continent, a state-run &amp;hellip; Big Data In Banking: How Citibank Delivers Real Business Benefits With Forbes The company, in recent years, has adopted a fully Big Data-driven &amp;hellip; The platform is primarily built on Hadoop and datasets are sourced from between &amp;hellip; Western Digital, Unisplendour form joint venture Unis-WDC will aim to become &amp;ldquo;the strategic partner to China&amp;rsquo;s big data industry,&amp;rdquo; said the companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big data shows K-pop stretching from Asia to US SEOUL, Sept. 8 (Yonhap) &amp;ndash; The South Korean pop culture has expanded in size and market from Asia to the North American continent, a state-run &amp;hellip; Big Data Shows K-Pop Stretching from Asia to US The most significant overseas market for K-pop turned out to be Japan, according to the report. Regarding the whole K-pop culture market, &amp;hellip; Why Big Data is a Big Deal When used correctly, big data can help business leaders better understand their companies and their customers, and ultimately help them design and &amp;hellip; ISR Analytics: Challenges for IT, Implications for Big Data, and CIOReview ISR (Intelligence, Surveillance, and Reconnaissance) systems consist of infrastructure that typically includes platforms and sensors, communications &amp;hellip; Western Digital and Unisplendour Corporation Limited Celebrate New Joint Business Wire (press release) UNIS WDC will adhere to the concept of independent innovation and international cooperation to drive new applications for big data storage in &amp;hellip; The big data balance: a man-plus-machine approach to hiring As human beings, our commonality is a precondition to choose people like us, favour similarities, and unconsciously make decisions that fit a flawed &amp;hellip; Big Data in the developing world But in the developing world, big data is being used to save lives, with researchers beginning to take full advantage of the ability of smart devices to &amp;hellip; 10 Best Practices in Big Data &amp;ndash; Cryptographic Technologies The advent of big data has heralded a revolution of sophisticated new techniques in cryptography to address the security of massive, streaming and &amp;hellip; Telenor provides big data to improve community planning Telenor has developed a way to extract anonymous data from base stations securely to discover whereabouts people travel the most in Norway &amp;hellip; Getting Airlines To Promises Of Big Data Lately, there has been a growing interest in the opportunity for aircraft maintenance to benefit from big data, the Internet of Things and increased &amp;hellip; Ex-Oracle Exec Is Now CEO of Big Data Firm MapR One year ago, high-profile Oracle executive Matt Mills jumped ship to become president and COO of big data upstart MapR Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Research Assistant, Big Data and Development (RA) to support our ongoing research and training activities on big data &amp;hellip; Z Nation Lab accelerator to invest in IoT, big data &amp;amp; more Z Nation Lab has launched an incubation and accelerator programme in Mumbai, reports Inc42. The program will focus on startups in India and the &amp;hellip; Big data, smart cities, IoT new growth avenues for firms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Aspire 3.0 Recognized as a KMWorld Trend-Setting Product of 2016 Search Technologies, the leading IT services firm specializing in the design and implementation of enterprise search and big data analytics &amp;hellip; Big Data Analytics for Prognostic Foresight engineering, a plethora of data collectors, sensors, transmission devices, &amp;hellip; Gemalto significantly expands big data security offerings With Gemalto, Hadoop users can protect their files with encryption and continue to benefit from the analytics tools that make big data implementations &amp;hellip; How Analytics, Big Data and AI Are Changing Call Centers Forever If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever had to call a customer help line or other call center, you probably experience a shiver of dread at the mere thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big data offers Jolly good route to success Ding Wei, one of the three founders and current executive president of Jolly, said big data was one of the keys to the firm&amp;rsquo;s fast growth over such a &amp;hellip; S. Korea to produce standard combat uniform using big data SEOUL, Sept. 5 (Yonhap) &amp;ndash; South Korea&amp;rsquo;s military said Monday it will produce a standard combat uniform using so-called big data collected through &amp;hellip; Big Data And A Shocking Waste Problem It&amp;rsquo;s a shocking fact that in the 21st century more than three quarters of a billion people do not have access to enough food to keep themselves healthy, &amp;hellip; Big Data, Big Opportunities, Big Privacy techniques and their uses are becoming critical in non-advertising fields such &amp;hellip; Military to Develop Standard Combat Uniform with Big Data Military to Develop Standard Combat Uniform with Big Data &amp;hellip; a study to produce standard combat uniforms based on an analysis of big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big data offers Jolly good route to success In less than four years , three entrepreneurs have developed JollyChic from a startup to one of China &amp;lsquo; s largest e-commerce clothing exporters , and &amp;hellip; Elton Stoneman Highlights Hadoop and Hive for .NET Developers When it comes to big data, it&amp;rsquo;s hard not to think immediately of Hadoop. Ask Elton Stoneman, a software architect, Pluralsight author, and Microsoft &amp;hellip; Pharma Lifecycle Plagued With Integration and Data Management Challenges A Big Data system is comprised of a number of functional blocks that &amp;hellip; is the step where data from diverse sources enters the Big Data system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Deals: Become A Big Data Professional With This Bundle Using Hadoop and MapReduce, you&amp;rsquo;ll discover how to create &amp;hellip; For a limited time, the Big Data Bundle is on sale for only $58.50 AUD [$45 USD] &amp;hellip; Why Big Data Could Also Mean Big Security Breaches for Insurance Companies Big Data has been one of the largest growing developments for insurance. Car insurance companies, for instance, used to price policies based on &amp;hellip; Photo Contest Big Data to Predict and Prevent Diabetes Photo Contest Big Data to Predict and Prevent Diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Korea to foster big data use for financial firms &amp;hellip; here to share information of their customers for big data collection purposes while maintaining privacy, the top financial regulator said on Sept. 1. Inside GHD&amp;rsquo;s drive to embrace data science &amp;hellip; including predictive analysis library and more recently with Vora, a tool that can bridge HANA and big data systems like Spark and Hadoop. Reliance Jio 4G is the big data push we needed, but Ambanis must push a bit The Indian Express Reliance Jio 4G launch: Our data requirements will only boom as the new users come in by the millions, so &amp;ldquo;data abundance&amp;rdquo; will be a big help, &amp;hellip; TPG Growth Invests in C3 IoT and Its Full-Stack Development Platform for Business Wire (press release) Founded by Silicon Valley icon Thomas Siebel, C3 IoT applies the sciences of big data, advanced analytics, and machine learning to enable a new &amp;hellip; Machine Learning: The Bigger Picture, Part I One could argue that SAGE was one of the first big data processing systems ever built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Sep 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Hottest Big Data Startup IQLECT Gears up for Series A Round, set to Launch Yahoo Finance 31, 2016 /CNW/ - Real-time data analytics company IQLECT, the hottest big data startup from Bangalore , founded by Ex-CTO of Jabong.com Sachin &amp;hellip; Build vs. buy equation changes, as open source big data tools surge The build vs. buy decision is a fluid one, as open source big data tools &amp;hellip; Today&amp;rsquo;s open source technologies, such as Hadoop and Spark, were &amp;hellip; Big data salaries set to rise in 2017 Starting salaries for big data pros will continue to rise in 2017 as companies jockey to hire skilled data professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data and Mobility: How Enterprise Resource Planning Is Being Reinvented Although both mobile apps and big data analytics have become pivotal to business operations on a broad scale, one area of software &amp;hellip; HPE Vertica: Eliminating the sucking sound from Hadoop | #SeizeTheData As day one of the HPE Big Data Conference, held at the Westin Boston Waterfront in Boston, MA, wrapped up, Dave Vellante (@dvellante) and Paul &amp;hellip; Beyond The Hype: Big Data In Drug Development And Healthcare entirely clear who invented the term Big Data [Ref: Steve Lohr, The Origins of &amp;lsquo;Big &amp;hellip; Sentiment Analysis/Opinion mining: Big Data venturing into the new breed of DATAQUEST With emerging technologies that enable analysis of Big Data at blazing speed, organizations are able to understand their customers intimately and &amp;hellip; HPE Vertica 8 - Analyse big data anywhere HPE&amp;rsquo;s new Vertica 8 Advanced Analytics has flexible deployment options across on-premise, private, and public clouds, and in Hadoop data lakes, &amp;hellip; Price action limited ahead of big data Core bonds trade ended close to unchanged as disappointing EMU eco data (EC confidence data, German CPI), comments by Fed Fischer and strong &amp;hellip; Is the Cloud Finally Ready for Big Data?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Mark Torr, a valued expert on Internet of Things and Big Data, will be On 6th of September 2016 at 12 pm, Mark Torr a valued expert and opinion leader on IoT and Big Data, will be delivering a public lecture at the IT &amp;hellip; Curing health care with a dose of big data and common sense Marschall Runge, University of Michigan. While commanding four vessels sailing between England and India in 1601, Captain James Lancaster &amp;hellip; Picking the Fashion Runway Winners With Big Data That&amp;rsquo;s according to a study provided first to WWD by Katie Smith, senior fashion and retail market analyst at fashion-focused big data firm Edited, which &amp;hellip; In The Church Of Big Data, Artistic Judgment Is Just A Data Point into our fascination with Big Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Friction, spark, innovation! The formula for&amp;hellip; The formula for breaking big data sets to impact customer experience. BY Peter Roper ON 29 August 2016 4 min read. Friction, spark, innovation! China banks starved of big data as mobile payments rise The rise of third-party mobile payments in China at the expense of credit and debit cards is threatening commercial banks&amp;rsquo; access to the customer data &amp;hellip; Big Data initiative and the need for IT resources There are many definitions of big data, in fact, every tech guru has their own definition of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Get schooled on Big Data in two upcoming workshops Big Data is now big business for companies of every size and sector as they use it to improve performance and boost their bottom line. Because of that &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Rio Olympics 2016: How It Leveraged New Age Technology Into Sports ! Olympics is the world&amp;rsquo;s most spectacular sporting event. Understandably, it saw several new-age state-of-the-art technologies such as Big Data, &amp;hellip; Advanced data analysis helping to nab Medicare cheaters When FBI and Health and Human Services investigators announced earlier this summer they had snared more than 300 people trying to bilk Medicare &amp;hellip; 5 Ways Big Data Will Change Every Industry Big data has passed the early adopter stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Innovation Summit Returns To Boston The principle challenge of the decade thus far for businesses across all industries has been how to use Big Data. Organizations now have a wealth of &amp;hellip; UTA Physicists Get $1 Million to Upgrade Titan Software His work has provided important new solutions to the problem of how to manage the worldwide production and distributed analysis of the big data &amp;hellip; Inmar shares success in Big Data/Hadoop analytics with HPE SecureData and Inmar shares success in Big Data/Hadoop analytics with HPE SecureData and FPE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Thanks Big Data! How to delight your customers using intelligent data globally. In a given month, he might fly to Mexico City, Shanghai, and Toronto, &amp;hellip; Big data can combat revenue fraud &amp;ndash; even when it&amp;rsquo;s an inside job Fifteen years on, we are well into the era of large-scale analytics using big data, and some of those businesses that were tardy in their revenue &amp;hellip; Focus on ad viewability and big data at Zee Melt 2016 After a successful first edition, Kyoorius is back with the second edition of Zee Melt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
How to Turn Dark Data from a Problem into an Advantage These files can reside far more cost-effectively in Hadoop or the cloud. &amp;hellip; updates from customer databases to big data platforms such as Hadoop, &amp;hellip; Ones &amp;amp; Zeros : How Digital Power Plants Are Leveraging Big Data and Power Engineering Magazine Italy, 1952. The war is finally over, and people are beginning to hope for the future again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big data helps police spot bad apples - if they use it The Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s investigation of Baltimore police this month rebuked the agency for an entrenched culture of discriminatory policing. SAS, Samsung SDS to supply big data analytics Samsung SDS, the IT service affiliate of Samsung Electronics, and US-based business analytics vendor SAS will offer their jointly-developed new big &amp;hellip; Garbage in, garbage out: Canada&amp;rsquo;s big data problem What we call big data analytics works by finding previously unknown patterns in the huge blocks of data that very large organizations governments &amp;hellip; dmexco is the global business and innovation platform of the digital dmexco is the global business and innovation platform of the digital economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Can big data stop bad cops? Fatal force: This article is part of an ongoing examination by The Washington Post of fatal shootings by police. In 2015, The Post began tracking cases &amp;hellip; AcadGild, IL&amp;amp;FS Skills partner for tech education to students &amp;hellip; current vocational and skill-based training programmes to tech courses like Android Developer, Big Data &amp;amp; Digital Marketing conducted by AcadGild &amp;hellip; Big data and IoT promise big changes to agriculture The State University of New York (SUNY) College of Agriculture and Technology in upstate Cobleskill, NY, is home to some 2,500 students, &amp;hellip; Fusionex Receives Special Mention in Gartner&amp;rsquo;s 2016 Magic Quadrant &amp;hellip; leading software solutions provider specializing in Big Data Analytics, the Internet of Things, &amp;hellip; such as Cloud BI, Hadoop-based data discovery, Link/graph-based data discovery, and Data-blending-centric modern BI platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 18:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Strata + Hadoop World Week rental all week $1250 queen and pullout from Javits Center This is that iconic brownstone, tree lined street you see in &amp;hellip; Roundup Of Analytics, Big Data &amp;amp; BI Forecasts And Market Estimates, 2016 Presented below are a roundup of recent analytics and big data forecasts and &amp;hellip;. The Forrester Wave: Big Data Hadoop Distributions, Q1 2016. Jibun Bank Partners with Alpaca to Build the World&amp;rsquo;s First AI Supported PR Web (press release) Alpaca brings industry-proven AI and Big Data technology to the financial trading space by building an AI engine that efficiently understands each &amp;hellip; How relevant is data analytics to businesses today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Effective marketing strategies translate Big Data to smart data, say Insurance Business America A smart digital marketing strategy won&amp;rsquo;t rely on a single method of tracking, nor will it take data at face value. What differentiates the spray-and-pray &amp;hellip; Big Data and the Met Office and theory. It requires major supercomputing infrastructure to perform &amp;hellip; Emerging economies need to harness the power of Big Data MUCH has been written about the power and potential of Big Data and predictive analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Experts Highlight Differences Between Internet Plus and Big Data Big data will bring opportunities for those who want to set up their own businesses in the next five to ten years, but only those that have developed &amp;hellip; Senior Director, Product Management, Storage (Cloud/SDS, Big Data Storage) Will be responsible for the successful management of one or a group of &amp;hellip; Big Data Top 20 Container Shipping Companies Visualized Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to wrap our brains around large numbers generated by Big Data like the relative size of shipping companies based on their &amp;hellip; Strata + Hadoop World 26 29 Sep in NYC: 20% Discount with CTOvision&amp;rsquo;s SYS-CON Media (press release) And Big Data is driving this bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Coming to an HR Department near You the advancing science of hiring based on analytics. The days of making &amp;hellip; Inside Infor&amp;rsquo;s Data Science Lab The big data revolution is impacting many aspects of our lives, including how we work and play. The technologies and techniques that the big Silicon &amp;hellip; EDTECH: Silicon Valley&amp;rsquo;s Coursera Launches Big Data Analytics Moocs With BusinessBecause However, demand for trained analytics talent has hit fever pitch, with KPMG forecasting that 36% of companies lack big data specialists, up from 24% &amp;hellip; Hadoop Solutions Architect - Hadoop, HDFS, Kafka Data Hadoop Solutions Architect with Hadoop or HDFS experience, &amp;hellip; SnapLogic Expands Library of Intelligent Connectors to Integrate Enterprise Yahoo Finance The Summer 2016 release introduces several enhancements to SnapLogic&amp;rsquo;s support for Hadoop- and Spark-based big data integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Are big data analytics are more important than the cloud? Integration of big data and analytics is quickly becoming a top priority for businesses, according to IDC Australia, while cloud integration or migration is &amp;hellip; Brazil Taps GE&amp;rsquo;s Big Data in Path to Canoeing Medal in Rio When Brazil&amp;rsquo;s Isaquias Queiroz dos Santos pulled ahead of rivals from Russia and Moldova to win a silver medal in the 1,000-meter canoe sprint, &amp;hellip; Apache Kylin for OLAP on Hadoop Hadoop has evolved from a distributed data platform with generic compute &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Apache Kylin is the best OLAP engine on Big Data so far,&amp;rdquo; said Wilson &amp;hellip; Sr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Broadcasters and the big data bonanza Thanks to big data, it has changed the face of online advertising. Today the process of media buying is automated and targeted at a specific audience &amp;hellip; In perspective: How broadcasters can ride the big data wave Media companies are rife with opportunities as big data changes the way we think about everything. Web-based video companies such as Netflix ($37 &amp;hellip; Brazil Taps GE&amp;rsquo;s Big Data in Quest for Olympic Canoeing Gold When Brazil&amp;rsquo;s Isaquias Queiroz dos Santos beat rivals from Russia and France to win his qualifying match for the 1,000-meter canoe sprint, he owed &amp;hellip; ADOPTION OF BIG DATA ON CLOUD The integration of revolutionary concepts, Big Data and Cloud has stirred new wave of IT innovation across industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Hadoop Admin/Developer/Analyst AWS SysOps/Architect/Devloper SysOps/Architect/Developer, Oracle 12c DBA, PeopleSoft 9.2 Developer/Administrator, &amp;hellip; IBM scientists say big data can be used to quickly find sources of poisoned Food Safety News The mathematics are not simple, but IBM scientists have come up with methodology for analyzing retail scanner data from grocery stores against the &amp;hellip; Hadoop Developer - New York, NY - up to $180K + bon code -Write MapReduce jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
(BD2K) Enhancing Diversity in Biomedical Data Science (R25) NIH Office of the Associate Director for Data Science intends to commit $1 &amp;hellip; You are here: Home / Big Data / HP Enterprise Buying SGI for $275M Eyeing the growing demand for ever-faster and more complex data handling and analytics, Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) yesterday announced &amp;hellip; Funding Bounty: 10 startup funding really big this week [08 August 14 knowstartup (press release) Innovaccer, the Big Data Startup raises $15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Provides Marketers With A Goldmine Of Information. enough time has passed that making decisions about what to do with all &amp;hellip; Researchers prepare to wade through an ocean of data A leading oceanographer predicts Australia is on the cusp of a dramatic increase in information on our marine environment, thanks to big data and &amp;hellip; Creativity and Critique: Gap Analysis of Support for Critical Research on We define big data as large amounts of information, collected about many people, over multiple devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
5 EBooks to Read Before Getting into A Data Science or Big Data Career technology in the Big Data family. Download this handy guide to learn all you &amp;hellip; HPE to buy big data analytics firm SGI for $275 mn Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) is set to buy SGI, a solutions provider for compute, data analytics, and data management, in a deal valued at &amp;hellip; HPE Gobbles SGI for Larger Slice of HPC-Big Data Pie Big data combined with HPC is creating new solutions, adding many new users/buyers to the HPC space, stated IDC in its June HPC market update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Big Data Startup Innovaccer Closes 15.6 Million Series A Led by Westbridge Yahoo Finance SAN FRANCISCO, Aug. 10, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Innovaccer, Silicon Valley based big data startup, today announced a 15.6 Million Series A led by &amp;hellip; Difficulties of Big Data: The Anesthesiology News Report Several experts unravel the challenges of big data. A recent meta-analysis found that neuraxial anesthesia reduces surgical site infections compared &amp;hellip; Big Data Meets Consumers: Shifting from Data Mining to Data Refining Data which features an interview with Fishbowl&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Dev Ganesan, &amp;hellip; TRADER Corporation to Bring Big Data to the Canadian Automotive Industry This advanced process will map &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; such as transactional web impressions and vehicle searches on the marketplace, to understand consumer &amp;hellip; Cloud Platform Instructor (Big Data, Machine Learning) Cloud Platform product and solution training to thousands of partners, &amp;hellip; IBM big data used for rapid diagnosis of rare leukemia case in Japan In a possible first in Japan, doctors have used artificial intelligence to diagnose a rare type of leukemia and identify life-saving therapy far faster than if &amp;hellip; [Industry 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Australia&amp;rsquo;s Future Fund leads $77 million raising in US big data startup The Australian Financial Review It provides a platform for businesses to use open source software framework Hadoop, which enables organisations to analyse huge volumes of data in &amp;hellip; Software scrapes big data for big danger But taking this a step further, ASU researchers are developing a software tool that mines big data and then maps out what&amp;rsquo;s trending on everything: &amp;hellip; Can big data studies know your thoughts and predict who will win an EconoTimes When our Big Data and Smart Analytics Lab analysed those comments on Twitter towards the end of July, it predicted that if the US Presidential &amp;hellip; Industry Urged to Continue Momentum While Safely Managing Risks in the Big ScandOil Delegates at SPE Intelligent Energy 2016 (IE16) will hear presentations urging decision-makers to accelerate the adoption of big data without losing &amp;hellip; Why Startups Need A Data Scientist Data scientists are big data wranglers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Investing in big data? It might benefit your hospital to think smaller In less than a decade, internet searches for the term &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; exploded, growing nearly 100 percent between 2011 and 2016 alone. That trend &amp;hellip; Toshiba Introduces All-Flash Big Data Real-Time Analytics Platform Toshiba America Electronic Components Inc. (TAEC) has rolled out an all-flash big data analytics platform designed to enable real-time or streaming &amp;hellip; Can big data studies know your thoughts and predict who will win an The Conversation AU Who&amp;rsquo;ll be the next president of the United States Donald Trump or Hillary Clinton?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Aug 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-08-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily Big Data news from @topdatanews.
Kronologi reboots to capture big data growth PETALING JAYA: The last time Ace Market company Kronologi Asia Bhd appeared in the news, the stories revolved around major shareholder and &amp;hellip; BlueFocus Digital to embrace big data and seek emotional link with Campaign Asia-Pacific It is no longer sufficient to be creative in providing quality content and services; rather, it is a case of developing the capabilities to handle big data and &amp;hellip; Chicken &amp;amp; Beer, a New Icon of Korean Tourism Big Data is the hottest topic in the field of information technology these days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>