<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data on Crypt0 News</title>
    <link>//crypt0.net/categories/data/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data on Crypt0 News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Dataence. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crypt0.net/categories/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techstory.in/world-human-rights-day/&#39;&gt;World Human Rights Day: Six Ways In Which Big Data Is Helping Fight Child&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Techstory Child trafficking is growing fast across the world. According to the International Labor Organization 1.2 million children are trafficked each year, often &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.medgadget.com/2016/12/innovation-on-global-population-health-management-industry-analysis-to-benefit-from-implementation-of-big-data-services.html&#39;&gt;Innovation On Global Population Health Management Industry Analysis To&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medgadget (blog) As per the research, the rising aging population and the implementation of big data are two of the major factors expected to drive the industry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.whatech.com/business-intelligence/companies/graymatter-software-services&#39;&gt;GrayMatter Software Services - Business Intelligence Consultants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Big Data, Analytics &amp;amp; Data Science Specialist, GrayMatter has &amp;hellip; and Analytics stacks like SAP BI, Pentaho, Microsoft BI, Oracle BI, Hadoop, R, SAS &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.china.org.cn/china/2016-12/10/content_39889947.htm&#39;&gt;National Postdoctoral Academic Forum kicks off in Hengqin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With thetheme of &amp;ldquo;New Type of Smart City and Global Outlook in the Era of Big Data,&amp;rdquo; this year&amp;rsquo;s forum provides a platform for academic &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.kobo.com/us/en/ebook/data-governance-tools-evaluation-criteria-big-data-governance-and-alignment-with-enterprise-data-management&#39;&gt;Data Governance Tools: Evaluation Criteria, Big Data Governance, and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read Data Governance Tools: Evaluation Criteria, Big Data Governance, &amp;hellip; governance tools interact with big data technologies, including Hadoop, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itbusinessnet.com/article/Big-Data-Market-To-Gain-From-Enhanced-Demand-In-Healthcare-And-IT-Sector-Till-2022:-Grand-View-Research-Inc-4731979&#39;&gt;Big Data Market To Gain From Enhanced Demand In Healthcare And IT Sector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT Business Net According to the report published by Grand View Research, global big data market will reach $72.38 billion by 2022, the big data market is expected to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/25627899&#39;&gt;Big data mining yields novel insights on cancer.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;large-scale biological data, but the effective mining and modeling of &amp;lsquo;big data&amp;rsquo; for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/TravelCompute-Wins-APICTA-2016-Award-for-Its-Travel-Technology-Platform-Big-Data-Solution-for-NTOs-20161210&#39;&gt;TravelCompute Wins APICTA 2016 Award for Its Travel Technology Platform &amp;amp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World Octraves also showcased its Travel Big Data Solution for National Tourism Organizations (NTOs). The platform integrates data from various public, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.kdnuggets.com/2016/12/navigating-world-big-data-analytics.html&#39;&gt;Navigating the World of Big Data Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leveraging our Agile Analytics Lab, we created reusable data processing pipelines, loaded the data into Hadoop and readied it for analysis. Once the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.jewishjournal.com/articles/item/bgu_paypal_form_partnership_in_cybersecurity_research&#39;&gt;BGU, PayPal form partnership in cybersecurity research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PayPal&amp;rsquo;s involvement in big data and machine learning technology has been supported by its significant research and development (R&amp;amp;D) activity in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/big-data/amazon-redshift-engineerings-advanced-table-design-playbook-table-data-durability/&#39;&gt;Amazon Redshift Engineering&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Table Design Playbook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playbook: Table Data Durability. by Zach Christopherson | on 08 DEC &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.tradearabia.com/news/REAL_317822.html&#39;&gt;Leveraging big data analytics in retail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information is all around us, and every business - from finance to healthcare and telecom to real estate - relies on the use of big data and analytics for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.arnnet.com.au/article/611327/big-data-now-all-about-two-speed-information-architecture/?fp=2&amp;fpid=1&#39;&gt;Big data is now all about two-speed information architecture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data and analytics capabilities have made a leap forward in recent years, according to TIBCO Asia head of pre-sales, San Zaw. For Zaw, with the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://emploi.epfl.ch/page-139964-en.html&#39;&gt;PhD position: Big data, renewable energy and built environment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;environment; Development, adaptation, and programming of Big data mining &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/16/12/p8788120/nvtc-to-host-2017-capital-data-summit&#39;&gt;NVTC to Host 2017 Capital Data Summit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panel sessions will be led by principals from world leading big data and analytics companies, financial institutions, healthcare organizations, top &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.greenbiz.com/article/insurance-companies-arent-covering-climate-risk-big-data-blame&#39;&gt;Insurance companies aren&amp;rsquo;t covering climate risk  is Big Data to blame?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data  also known as predictive analytics  is helping insurers become increasingly accurate in their ability to pinpoint the exact level of risks &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itproportal.com/features/how-uk-banks-can-prevent-fraud-using-data-science/&#39;&gt;How UK banks can prevent fraud using data science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data science is the collaborative discipline - the combination of people, data, tools, and processes - used to transform big data into actionable insights &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mdpi.com/2071-1050/8/12/1293&#39;&gt;Urban Big Data and Sustainable Development Goals: Challenges and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can be achieved by situating the application of big data innovations &amp;hellip; advancing the culture and common skill sets for applying urban big data, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.readme.lk/iit-big-data-forum/&#39;&gt;IIT Big Data Analytics Tech Forum 2016: The Essentials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data, a hot topic that has been generating a lot of interest in the global IT industry. From retail and banking to providing analysis for election &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bsminfo.com/doc/data-backup-recovery-how-big-data-has-changed-things-what-decision-makers-need-to-do-about-it-0001&#39;&gt;Data Backup &amp;amp; Recovery: How Big Data Has Changed Things &amp;amp; What&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Solutions Magazine Today, companies in all sectors have a massive demand for data. To succeed, they must be able to take in a large amount of data and process it in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.kdnuggets.com/2016/12/big-data-ecosystem-science.html&#39;&gt;The big data ecosystem for science: Physics, LHC, and Cosmology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find out how big data, machine learning, and analytics are changing not only business, but society itself at Strata + Hadoop World. Save 20% on most &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scoop.co.nz/stories/GE1612/S00057/big-data-holds-key-to-life-saving-discoveries.htm&#39;&gt;Big Data Holds Key to Life Saving Discoveries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A whitepaper released today by bioinformatics technology company Biomatters examines the critical role big data will play in enabling scientists to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thelawyer.com/kinstellar-hosts-big-data-practice-seminar-budapest/&#39;&gt;Kinstellar hosts Big Data in Practice seminar in Budapest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speakers included: Istvn Tth, mathematician and data safety expert, who delved a little deeper into what Big Data means; Zsombor Orbn, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizjournals.com/bizjournals/how-to/technology/2016/12/major-league-baseball-slides-from-moneyball-to.html&#39;&gt;Major League baseball slides from Moneyball to Techball&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data is now on the cusp of an even bigger transformation of our &amp;hellip; some teams were taking advantage of less all-inclusive big data systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3148652/analytics/how-to-get-big-data-expertise-on-a-budget.html&#39;&gt;How to get big data expertise on a budget&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes staffing a big data professional can be out of reach, but these &amp;hellip; You can enroll your employees in online Tableau Training and Hadoop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.naij.com/1076973-trump-clinton-how-big-data-scientists-helped-trump-win-election.html&#39;&gt;Trump vs. Clinton: How Big Data and scientists helped Trump win the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NAIJ.COM The term Big Data means that all actions we perform on either the Web or offline leave a digital trail. Purchasing by credit card, Google search results &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3169537&#39;&gt;Emerging Global Big Data Market Trends, Technology Advancement, to Drive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital Journal The market size and forecast in terms of value for the global big data market has been provided for the period 2014 to 2019, considering 2013 as the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://ctovision.com/tapping-centralized-talent-pools-data-analytics-cybersecurity-mission-enabling-functions-government-agencies/&#39;&gt;Tapping into centralized talent pools for data analytics, cybersecurity and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CTOvision (blog) The highlight of the 2013 Government Big Data Forum was not just the focus on Hadoop-centric platforms like Cloudera, but the exchange of lessons &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blogs.voanews.com/techtonics/2016/12/09/for-developing-world-2016-brought-education-drones-big-data/&#39;&gt;For Developing World, 2016 Brought Education, Drones, Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using data collection and big data  complex analytical and behavioral databases that allow researchers to extract social and economic trends  the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.toptechnews.com/article/index.php?story_id=021000NNHR9R&#39;&gt;Understanding Your Customer Using Data Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They say that data is the new oil, and if your business has a web presence then chances are you&amp;rsquo;re sitting on vast reserves of potential customer &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dbta.com/Editorial/News-Flashes/BlueData-Announces-General-Availability-of-BlueData-EPIC-on-AWS-115276.aspx&#39;&gt;BlueData Announces General Availability of BlueData EPIC on AWS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The platform also provides the same Docker-based application images for Hadoop, Spark, and other Big Data tools are portable across on-premises &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.apics.org/sites/apics-blog/think-supply-chain-landing-page/thinking-supply-chain/2016/12/09/using-big-data-for-improved-roi&#39;&gt;Using Big Data for Improved ROI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data that supply chain professionals should be working more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://martechtoday.com/forget-big-data-thinking-small-can-help-marketers-see-future-193182&#39;&gt;Forget big data: Why thinking small can help marketers see the future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jones explains how a combination of small data analytics, predictive analytics &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.xconomy.com/texas/2016/12/09/technium-crunches-big-data-to-match-entrepreneurs-with-researchers/&#39;&gt;Technium Crunches Big Data to Match Entrepreneurs with Researchers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DallasUniversities and other institutions are chock-full of intellectual property, but it can be difficult for entrepreneurs, interested in turning those &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/12/09/big-data-no-longer-a-big-problem/&#39;&gt;Big Data No Longer a Big Problem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;equus_logo Today&amp;rsquo;s enterprise-level organizations produce ever-increasing volumes of data each day. As employees create new documents, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2016/12/08/no-big-data-didn-t-win-the-u-s-election&#39;&gt;No, Big Data Didn&amp;rsquo;t Win the U.S. Election&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Bloomberg View) &amp;ndash; One of the most enjoyable parts of the fallout from a big political upset is the victory dance of those who claim they brought it about &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.impetus.com/content/big-data-master-class-nasscom-atc-2016&#39;&gt;Big Data Master Class  NASSCOM ATC 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;its premises. The workshop will feature a mix of hands-on technical &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/dark-side-of-wearables-tsunami-of-useless-medical-big-data/&#39;&gt;Dark side of wearables: Tsunami of useless medical big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At a recent media roundtable discussion about the future for wearables, hosted by Vivalnk, I was sitting next to two doctors who have been working in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/cochlear-to-extract-big-data-from-hearing-implants/&#39;&gt;Cochlear to extract big data from hearing implants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt; From spray-on skin for burns victims, the electronic pacemaker, the Gardasil and Cervarix cancer vaccines, or finding the medical application of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pharmiweb.com/pressreleases/pressrel.asp?ROW_ID=195138&#39;&gt;Commercial Pharmaceutical Analytics Market to Provide over USD 1.5 Billion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PharmiWeb.com (press release) The tools such as Big Data, Tablue, Hadoop, and such others actually made it possible to handle such a huge data from these industries. Big Data has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://datacenternews.asia/story/znv-cloudera-target-big-data-analytics-management-data-centers/&#39;&gt;ZNV &amp;amp; Cloudera target big data analytics management in data centers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company says this need must be addressed, so it launched WeKeeper, a big data solution that will aid data center managers in their choices &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://reliefweb.int/report/world/guide-data-innovation-development-idea-proof-concept&#39;&gt;A guide to data innovation for development: From idea to proof-of-concept&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Global Pulse has served as a big data innovation hub within the UN for the past five years, testing new approaches and designing big data pilot &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/183817/global-big-data-and-analytics-in-telecom-industry-growth-analysis-and-insight-research-report-to-2016-and-forecast-to-2021&#39;&gt;Global Big Data and Analytics in Telecom Industry Growth, Analysis, and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsMaker (press release) The Global Big Data and Analytics in Telecom Industry Industry 2016 Market Research Report is a professional and in-depth study on the current state &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thefifthestate.com.au/innovation/engineering/the-megatrends-that-will-rock-the-property-industry/87296&#39;&gt;The megatrends that will rock the property industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A number of potential disrupters were uncovered, including sustainable cities, the move to carbon zero, big data, the sharing economy, virtual reality, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/big-data/interactive-analysis-of-genomic-datasets-using-amazon-athena/&#39;&gt;Interactive Analysis of Genomic Datasets Using Amazon Athena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;running a big data system. This makes Athena an excellent complement to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://prwire.com.au/pr/64697/leveraging-big-data-analytics-in-retail&#39;&gt;Leveraging Big Data Analytics in Retail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates, December 8, 2016: With the high influx of information available, every business  from finance to healthcare, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketingtechnews.net/news/2016/dec/08/ways-turning-big-data-marketing-gold/&#39;&gt;Ways of turning big data into marketing gold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wherever we turn in the 21st century, all industries are jumping on the idea of big data; and marketing is no different. Businesses from start ups to blue &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3168802&#39;&gt;Big Data Report 2016 - Global Strategic Business Report 2014-2022 -&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital Journal DUBLIN&amp;ndash;(Business Wire)&amp;ndash;Research and Markets has announced the addition of the &amp;ldquo;Big Data - Global Strategic Business Report&amp;rdquo; report to their &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://theartnewspaper.com/market/how-big-data-is-set-to-change-the-art-market/&#39;&gt;How Big Data is set to change the art market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In late October, Sotheby&amp;rsquo;s announced it had acquired the Mei Moses Art Indices, a database of repeat auction sales that tracks value over time; shortly &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161208005017/en/Big-Data-Holds-Key-Life-Saving-Discoveries&#39;&gt;Big Data Holds Key to Life Saving Discoveries Says Biomatters Whitepaper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;A whitepaper released today by bioinformatics technology company Biomatters examines the critical &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/zoomdata-earns-the-top-ranking-in-2nd-annual-big-data-analytics-market-study-from-dresner-advisory-services/&#39;&gt;Zoomdata Earns the Top Ranking in 2nd Annual Big Data Analytics Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) SAN MATEO, CA(Marketwired  Dec 7, 2016)  Zoomdata, developers of the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest visual analytics platform for big data, today announced it &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161208005164/en/ZEPL-Announces-4.1M-Funding-Accelerate-Innovation-Adoption&#39;&gt;ZEPL Announces $4.1M Funding to Accelerate Innovation and Adoption of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) And though recent advances in Hadoop, Spark, and other compute &amp;hellip; Apache Zeppelin is fast becoming the standard big data visualization interface to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://formtek.com/blog/big-data-and-analytics-what-to-expect-in-2017/&#39;&gt;Big Data and Analytics: What to Expect in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Expect to see a big data cloud ecosystem begin to take shape. Apache Spark  An big data open source project now bigger than Hadoop that is also &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zawya.com/mena/en/story/Leveraging_big_data_analytics_in_retail-ZAWYA20161208150026/&#39;&gt;Leveraging big data analytics in retail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The future of retail also lies in big data analytics. Based on customer loyalty data, browsing patterns, social media, purchase history and demographic &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ibamag.com/us/news/breaking-news/big-data-can-provide-personalized-insurance-kpmg-41601.aspx&#39;&gt;Big data can provide personalized insurance: KPMG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data can provide personalized insurance: KPMG Data analytics is about customization when it comes to insurance = something brokers can take &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://pointofsale.com/PointofSale.com-Blog/Thanx-Secures-$17.1M-Series-B-to-Bring-Big-Data-to-Retail-Merchants.html&#39;&gt;Thanx Secures $17.1M Series B to Bring Big Data to Retail Merchants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Dec. 8, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Thanx, which empowers merchants to grow their business through deeper customer loyalty, today &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/earlysense-to-present-at-pcha-connected-health-conference-605427446.html&#39;&gt;EarlySense to Present at PCHA Connected Health Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Liat Tsoref to Discuss Use of Big Data Analytics in Identifying Health &amp;hellip; Her session, Identifying patterns in seniors&amp;rsquo; health with big data analytics, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://feedstuffs.com/story-big-data-ag-continues-expand-45-150340&#39;&gt;Big data in ag continues to expand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M AgriLife currently has more than 40 scientists involved in a UAV project that is Texas A&amp;amp;M AgriLife currently has more than 40 scientists &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.co.uk/news-releases/big-data-is-already-providing-commercial-benefits-to-pharma-companies-says-gbi-research-605452576.html&#39;&gt;Big Data is Already Providing Commercial Benefits to Pharma Companies, Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire UK (press release) Big Data simply refers to any data set which is too large to store, process or analyze using traditional database software and hardware. As technology &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/big-data-and-data-analytics-in-homeland-security-and-public-safety-is-forecast-to-reach-11b-in-2022-according-to-a-new-research-report-from-homeland-security-research-corp/&#39;&gt;Big Data and Data Analytics in Homeland Security and Public Safety is&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) Homeland Security Research Corp. forecasts that the Big Data and Data &amp;hellip; Big Data and Data Analytics technologies can increase the investigative &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/357218451/gridgain-selected-as-a-2016-red-herring-top-100-global-company&#39;&gt;GridGain Selected as a 2016 Red Herring Top 100 Global Company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In the era of big data and analytics, we have created a high performance solution &amp;ndash; and &amp;hellip; GridGain is a trademark or registered trademark of GridGain Systems, Inc. Apache, Apache Hadoop, Hadoop, Apache Ignite, and Ignite are &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/marymeehan/2016/12/08/where-data-goes-to-die-big-data-still-holds-answers-but-theyre-not-where-youre-looking-for-them/&#39;&gt;Where Data Goes To Die. Big Data Still Holds Answers, But They&amp;rsquo;re Not Where&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forbes The attention data crunching has gotten from media and pundits would make anyone think that big data is the big answer  until, of course, it isn&amp;rsquo;t. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsweek.com/big-data-financial-markets-now-getting-fintech-treatment-529629&#39;&gt;Big Data in Financial Markets Is Now Getting the &amp;lsquo;Fintech&amp;rsquo; Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within the silos of incumbent financial services, so-called fintech companies are good at picking off one thing only and doing it well. This approach is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.internethealthmanagement.com/2016/12/08/digital-health-investors-see-money-pouring-big-data/&#39;&gt;Digital health investors see more money pouring into big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a session short on talk of actual dollars, but investor money will keep flowing into digital healthcareunder certain conditions. That&amp;rsquo;s the group &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blog.executivebiz.com/2016/12/netcomm-part-of-atarc-federal-big-data-test-lab-louise-white-comments/&#39;&gt;NetComm Part of ATARC Federal Big Data Test Lab; Louise White Comments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;big-data Cloud-based data analytics provider NetComm has signed up for the Advanced Technology Academic Research Center&amp;rsquo;s Federal Big Data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://nationalacademies.org/hmd/reports/2016/big-data-and-analytics-for-infectious-disease-research-operations-and-policy-proceedings-of-a-workshop.aspx&#39;&gt;Big Data and Analytics for Infectious Disease Research, Operations, and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the amount of data in the world exploding, big data could generate significant value in the field of infectious disease. The Forum on Microbial &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidehpc.com/2016/12/optimizing-for-big-data/&#39;&gt;Optimizing Your Code for Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data applications have the potential to change many aspects of how large systems can be used. With the massive amounts of data being produced &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizjournals.com/kansascity/news/2016/12/08/bayer-animal-health-marketing-big-data-changes.html&#39;&gt;Bayer targets animal health marketing in a world &amp;lsquo;awash in data&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bayer AG uses big data to research new animal health products, but also for targeted marketing. The company, whose Bayer Animal Health unit has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2016-12-08/no-big-data-didn-t-win-the-u-s-election&#39;&gt;No, Big Data Didn&amp;rsquo;t Win the U.S. Election&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messina also held that &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; was an outdated concept and the future of political campaigning depended on what he termed &amp;ldquo;little data&amp;rdquo;: &amp;ldquo;Huge &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://itbrief.co.nz/story/machine-learning-big-disruptor-says-ovum/&#39;&gt;Machine learning: The big disruptor, says Ovum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Machine learning is tipped to be the biggest disruptor for big data analytics in 2017, according &amp;hellip; The cloud will sharpen Hadoop-Spark co-opetition.. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.tableau.com/resource/top-10-big-data-trends-2017&#39;&gt;Top 10 Big Data Trends 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to fulfill the need for analytics on Hadoop. But enterprises with complex, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dbta.com/Editorial/News-Flashes/Bridging-the-Gap-Between-Traditional-and-Big-Data-with-Data-Modeling-115268.aspx&#39;&gt;Bridging the Gap Between Traditional and Big Data with Data Modeling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As more enterprises incorporate new technologies such as Hadoop and NoSQL and new strategies like data lakes to manage fast-growing volumes of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.quickenloans.com/blog/using-big-data-find-clients-real-estate-business&#39;&gt;Using Big Data to Find Clients for Your Real Estate Business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data refers to large amounts of data that have been collected over time, specifically on the internet. Since becoming publicly available in 1991, the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.proactiveinvestors.com.au/companies/news/170210/byte-power-group-to-expand-its-big-data-offering-for-china-170210.html&#39;&gt;Byte Power Group to expand its big data offering for China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byte Power Group&amp;rsquo;s (ASX:BPG) subsidiary, subsidiary Byte Power (Hong Kong) Ltd, has signed an agreement to set up a &amp;lsquo;big data&amp;rsquo; joint venture with &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.floridatoday.com/story/money/business/2016/12/08/big-tech-news-uses-big-data/95137568/&#39;&gt;The big tech news in 2016 was the uses of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I logged into Facebook recently I was presented with a video titled Your Year in Review. The message accompanying the video read, Scott, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/16/12/p8779047/etiyas-serdoo-uses-ai-to-automate-customer-service-management&#39;&gt;Etiya&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Serdoo&amp;rsquo; uses AI to automate customer service management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etiya, the leading independent software vendor providing telco CRM, catalog-driven BSS/OSS, social CRM and big data analytics, announced the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ship-technology.com/features/featureusing-big-data-to-combat-illegal-fishing-5688984/&#39;&gt;Using big data to combat illegal fishing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The international community is desperately trying to crack down on illegal fishing and is increasingly harnessing the power of big data to achieve this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://software.intel.com/en-us/forums/intel-visual-fortran-compiler-for-windows/topic/704683&#39;&gt;subroutine in ABAQUS read big data file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;some data file and then pass is to the other subroutine &amp;lsquo;DLOAD&amp;rsquo;. The data I am &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.brighttalk.com/webcast/13073/232839?utm_medium=web&amp;utm_source=brighttalk-portal&amp;utm_campaign=all-brighttalk-upcoming&#39;&gt;Shining light on Hadoop: Wellcentive Cuts Troubleshooting from Months to&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wellcentive, a SaaS health management and data analytics company, relies on a nightly Mapreduce job to process and analyze data for their entire &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://itbrief.co.nz/story/cloudera-hadoop-changing-role-data-business/&#39;&gt;Cloudera, Hadoop and the changing role of data in business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hadoop is an eco-system of big data technologies with a very scalable database at its heart. The technology came out of Yahoo around a decade ago. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://koreabizwire.com/military-uses-big-data-for-disease-control-and-prevention/71669&#39;&gt;Military Uses Big Data for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7 (Korea Bizwire)  The Ministry of Defense is teaming up with the Ministry of Science, ICT and Future Planning for a big data research project that will &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://cds.cern.ch/journal/CERNBulletin/2016/21/Announcements/2151923?ln=zh_TW&#39;&gt;Summer School - 27 June - 6 July 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 2016. IBD4Health explores advanced topics related to big data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.shanghaidaily.com/opinion/The-Global-Search-for-Education-Would-Small-Data-Mean-Big-Change/shdaily.shtml&#39;&gt;The Global Search for Education: Would Small Data Mean Big Change?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must be mindful of potential drawbacks of big data, especially those related to data privacy and research ethics. When big data is used to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.shanghaidaily.com/metro/health-and-science/Science-authority-signs-agreement-with-leading-publisher-to-develop-big-data-database-for-talents-experts/shdaily.shtml&#39;&gt;Science authority signs agreement with leading publisher to develop big&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shanghai Daily (subscription) THE city&amp;rsquo;s science authority signed cooperation agreement with the world&amp;rsquo;s largest publisher for science, technology and medicine in the city today in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://qz.com/819245/data-scientist-cathy-oneil-on-the-cold-destructiveness-of-big-data/&#39;&gt;Data scientist Cathy O&amp;rsquo;Neil on the cold destructiveness of big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data promises fairness. With enough information about individuals and populations, we can design algorithms that will identify the best possible &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/183273/hadoop-market-analysis-size-trends-share-report-and-forecast-to-2022&#39;&gt;Hadoop Market Analysis, Size, Trends, Share, Report and Forecast to 2022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Stratistics MRC, the global hadoop market is expected to grow at a &amp;hellip; demand for big data analytics are the factors influencing the market growth. &amp;hellip; North America has the largest regional market for Hadoop led by the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scotsman.com/business/companies/tech/steve-ross-big-data-still-needs-the-human-touch-1-4311195&#39;&gt;Steve Ross: Big data still needs the human touch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data analytics failed to recognise &amp;lsquo;fake&amp;rsquo; news during the race for the White House. Picture: Ty Wright/Getty Images &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://postandparcel.info/76938/news/using-big-data-to-cut-shipping-costs/&#39;&gt;Using Big Data to cut shipping costs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers from Belgium&amp;rsquo;s Vlerick Business School have developed a Big Data analytics tool which they say will help companies substantially &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/data-science-pioneer-drew-conway-closes-25m-seed-funding-bring-machine-learning-industrial-2181338.htm&#39;&gt;Data Science Pioneer Drew Conway Closes $2.5M in Seed Funding to Bring&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) Alluvium aims to conquer one of big data&amp;rsquo;s greatest unsolved challenges for complex industrial operations with expert human operators. Alluvium&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://diginomica.com/2016/12/07/panning-right-data-gold-big-data-torrent/&#39;&gt;Panning for &amp;lsquo;right data&amp;rsquo; gold in the Big Data torrent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all know what &amp;lsquo;Big Data&amp;rsquo; means  data sets that are so large or complex, they can&amp;rsquo;t be managed with traditional data processing applications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.darkdaily.com/hoping-to-become-heavyweights-in-healthcare-big-data-ibm-watson-health-teams-up-with-siemens-radiology-and-in-vitro-diagnostics-businesses-1207&#39;&gt;Hoping to Become Heavyweights in Healthcare Big Data, IBM Watson Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DARKDaily.com - Laboratory News Big data has the potential to deliver unprecedented insight into optimizing the patient care experience and managing outcomes for healthcare &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2016/12/07/895829/0/en/JUST-Capital-and-GoodData-Announce-Partnership-to-Create-a-Big-Data-Platform-that-Supports-Corporate-Engagement-and-Their-Investor-Related-Products.html&#39;&gt;JUST Capital and GoodData Announce Partnership to Create a Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GlobeNewswire (press release) JUST Capital partners with GoodData to create the foundation and single source of truth to identify JUST companies. With multiple disparate data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/celonis-launches-the-first-enterprise-class-big-data-analytics-process-mining-platform-powered-by-artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning/&#39;&gt;Celonis Launches the First Enterprise-Class, Big Data Analytics Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) NEW YORK(BUSINESS WIRE)Celonis today announced it has launched the industry&amp;rsquo;s first enterprise-class, big data analytics process mining &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cbronline.com/news/big-data/analytics/big-data-making-cios-smarter/&#39;&gt;Is Big Data making CIOs smarter?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data  the &amp;lsquo;new oil&amp;rsquo;  is fast becoming a key role in business decision making. The key, however, is how to turn that data into intelligent information &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3967572&#39;&gt;Celonis Launches the First Enterprise-Class, Big Data Analytics Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SYS-CON Media (press release) Celonis today announced it has launched the industry&amp;rsquo;s first enterprise-class, big data analytics process mining platform fueled by artificial intelligence &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.psu.edu/story/440879/2016/12/07/research/big-data-approach-water-quality-applied-shale-drilling-sites&#39;&gt;Big data approach to water quality applied at shale drilling sites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UNIVERSITY PARK, Pa.  A computer program is diving deep into water quality data from Pennsylvania, helping scientists detect potential &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/357032650/hadoop-market-2016-share-trend-segmentation-and-forecast-to-2022&#39;&gt;Hadoop Market 2016 Share, Trend, Segmentation and Forecast to 2022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;global hadoop market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 53.7% over the forecast &amp;hellip; demand for big data analytics are the factors influencing the market growth. &amp;hellip; North America has the largest regional market for Hadoop led by the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/183504/big-data-as-a-service-2016-market-segmentationapplicationtechnology-market-analysis-research-report-to-2020&#39;&gt;Big data as a Service 2016 Market Segmentation,Application,Technology &amp;amp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsMaker (press release) This market research report presents a detailed segmentation of the global big data as a service market by application (HaaS, analytics as a service, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://rezidenciaseverka.sk/679-papers-data-pdf-analysis-big-research&#39;&gt;Big data analysis research papers pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;expensive? Split your payment apart - Big data analysis research papers pdf. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3147855/security/how-to-secure-big-data-environments-with-identity-management-and-auditing.html&#39;&gt;How to Secure Big Data Environments with Identity Management and Auditing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many organizations are deploying Hadoop to help launch their big data projects. Unfortunately, Hadoop runs in non-secure mode by default, which &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sdtimes.com/hewlett-packard-enterprise-enriches-hpe-idol-machine-learning-engine-natural-language-processing/&#39;&gt;Hewlett Packard Enterprise enriches HPE IDOL machine learning engine with&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the biggest challenges facing organizations trying to leverage Big Data is providing answers to users&amp;rsquo; questions in a natural, effective manner &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/07/hpes-big-data-solutions-add-machine-learning-natural-language-mix-hpediscover/&#39;&gt;HPE&amp;rsquo;s big data solutions add machine learning and natural language into the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SiliconANGLE (blog) Veis also discussed HPE big data solutions, including Vertica, which &amp;hellip; they get the performance of a Vertica front end with the economy of Hadoop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/random-forest-as-a-regressor-a-spark-based-solutio&#39;&gt;Random Forest as a Regressor: A Spark-based Solution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consequently, it&amp;rsquo;s a perfect algorithm for making predictive analytics on Big Data. It can handle thousands of input features and variables at a time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.aiadc.org/media-center/all-news-releases/2016/december/aia-to-advocate-for-a-balanced-approach-to-big-data-at-naic-2016-fall-meeting&#39;&gt;AIA to Advocate for a Balanced Approach to Big Data at NAIC 2016 Fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about AIA to Advocate for a Balanced Approach to Big Data at NAIC 2016 Fall Meeting at aiadc.org. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-12/ps-bda120716.php&#39;&gt;Big data approach to water quality applied at shale drilling sites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, sifting through big data is labor intensive, and complex patterns that might reveal potential problems can be difficult for humans to spot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thoughtworks.com/insights/blog/will-big-data-make-me-designosaur&#39;&gt;Will Big Data Make me a Designosaur?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;age and Big Data is automating many of the utilities in our lives. The potential of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://phys.org/news/2016-12-big-approach-quality-shale-drilling.html&#39;&gt;Big data approach to water quality applied at shale drilling sites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A computer program is diving deep into water quality data from Pennsylvania, helping scientists detect potential environmental impacts of Marcellus &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://prwire.com.au/pr/64662/queensland-brain-institute-overhauls-big-data-environment-to-advance-brain-research&#39;&gt;Queensland Brain Institute Overhauls Big Data Environment To Advance Brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PRWire (press release) As one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest dedicated facilities focused on understanding how the brain works and finding ways to prevent diseases, the Queensland &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.moneymanagement.com.au/news/financial-planning/big-data-will-boost-regulatory-monitoring&#39;&gt;Big data will boost regulatory monitoring&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advent of big data tools and the ability to access data will enable regulators of the banking and financial services sector to identify and respond to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/16/12/p8784139/aia-to-advocate-for-a-balanced-approach-to-big-data-at-naic-2016-fall-m&#39;&gt;AIA to Advocate for a Balanced Approach to Big Data at NAIC 2016 Fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Benzinga The Big Data (D) Working Group will discuss its charges and work stream for 2017. &amp;ldquo;For next year, we would encourage Working Group members to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.msn.com/en-us/money/taxes/big-data-makes-more-out-of-less-in-aerospace/vp-AAlhJPg&#39;&gt;Big data makes more out of less in aerospace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kant talk about the value that start-ups can add in the aerospace sector. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.safaribooksonline.com/live-training/courses/managing-enterprise-data-strategies-with-hadoop-spark-and-kafka/0636920065586/&#39;&gt;Managing Enterprise Data Strategies with Hadoop, Spark, and Kafka&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;failures can be time-consuming and expensive. This hands-on course &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://reliefweb.int/report/world/big-data-development-and-humanitarian-action-towards-responsible-governance-report&#39;&gt;Big data for development and humanitarian action: Towards responsible&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reliefweb In 2014, Global Pulse established a Data Privacy Advisory Group comprised of experts from public and private sector, academia and civil society from &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.ftc.gov/news-events/events-calendar/2016/12/cmr-mcsweeny-will-participant-seminar-competition-big-data&#39;&gt;Cmr. McSweeny will participate in seminar on Competition and Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and Big Data sponsored by King&amp;rsquo;s College London, Safra Lecture &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.vanillaplus.com/2016/12/06/24099-big-data-big-hype-getting-bigger-but-not-grown-up-quite-yet/&#39;&gt;Big data, big hype, getting bigger but not grown up quite yet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data, big hype, getting bigger but not grown up quite yet &amp;hellip; When it comes to big data there has certainly been plenty of hype, but not a lot of facts from &amp;hellip; from big-data-as-a-service through to full-blown platforms like Hadoop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.brecorder.com/articles-a-letters/187/110353/&#39;&gt;Big data helped Trump even after he scorned it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign - but those techniques might well have propelled him to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.arirang.co.kr/news/News_View.asp?nseq=198497&#39;&gt;Korea&amp;rsquo;s Defense Ministry to adopt Big Data analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of National Defense announced on Tuesday that it will launch a three-year big-data research program together with the Ministry of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bdva.eu/?q=node/544&#39;&gt;The Network of Big Data Centers of Excellence in Europe is up and running&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;of Excellence in Europe. The main focus of the Center of Excellence &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cso.com.au/mediareleases/28694/big-data-market-will-rule-the-future-with-rising/&#39;&gt;Big Data Market Will Rule the Future With Rising Trend of Digitalization!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Global big data market was worth US$6.3 billion in 2012 and is expected to reach US$48.3 billion by 2018, growing at a CAGR of 40.5% from 2012 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchdatacenter.techtarget.com/feature/Examine-data-collection-problems-with-big-data-IoT-in-mind&#39;&gt;Examine data collection problems with big data, IoT in mind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Networking challenges and data collection problems can occur when IT tries to deploy IoT and big data into a data center. Understand how to move &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.healthcareitnews.com/sponsored-content/leveraging-cloud-big-data-analytics&#39;&gt;Leveraging the Cloud for Big Data Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A large multinational manufacturer in the healthcare industry is analyzing big data in the cloud to efficiently drive insight across the enterprise to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/home-security-systems-wider-integration-161200834.html&#39;&gt;Home Security Systems: Wider Integration of ICT and Application of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Finance &amp;ldquo;Leveraging the Big Data generated by the Internet of Things will help improve the decision-making process and enable delivery of advanced &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://animal.agwired.com/2016/12/06/big-data-in-swine-health-measure-model-fix/&#39;&gt;Big Data in Swine Health  Measure, Model, Fix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;bivi-prrs-16-49-edited When the term &amp;lsquo;big data&amp;rsquo; is used in agriculture, we generally think crops. However, we are hearing it more and more in animal &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.universiteitleiden.nl/en/news/2016/11/collaborating-on-big-data-to-unravel-disease-processes&#39;&gt;Collaborating on big data to unravel disease processes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patients with the same illness often receive the same treatment, even if &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mbtmag.com/article/2016/12/three-key-steps-manufacturers-realize-their-big-data-age-dreams&#39;&gt;Three Key Steps For Manufacturers To Realize Their Big Data Age Dreams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that the age of big data is really here, manufacturing companies have truly game-changing opportunities to increase operating efficiency and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/dive-deep-into-deep-learning-using-h2o-1&#39;&gt;Anomaly Detection Using H2O Deep Learning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; Apache Hadoop. View an on-demand webinar now. Brought to you in partnership with Hortonworks. Topics: deep learning,data science,big data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.takepart.com/article/2016/12/06/silicon-valley-disruption-farm&#39;&gt;Silicon Valley&amp;rsquo;s Next Disruption Is on the Farm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data offers farmers worldwide more precise insights about weather and soil, allowing them to use the smallest possible amounts of water, sprays, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://chicago.suntimes.com/news/kapos-what-set-eric-lefkofsky-on-a-new-course-in-big-data/&#39;&gt;Kapos: What set Eric Lefkofsky on a new course in big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a time when Eric Lefkofsky&amp;rsquo;s legacy might have been Groupon, the $2.2 billion e-commerce company that connects customers with &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://adtmag.com/articles/2016/12/06/dev-salaries.aspx&#39;&gt;Salary Report: Mobile, Big Data Devs Lead Pack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Salary Report: Mobile, Big Data Devs Lead Pack &amp;hellip; while Microsoft SQL Server database and Hadoop skills can tack on nearly equivalent bonuses for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/391785/The-Big-Data-Market-to-grow-at-a-CAGR-of-12-over-2016-2030-Opportunities-Challenges-Strategies-Industry-Verticals-and-Forecasts.html&#39;&gt;The Big Data Market to grow at a CAGR of 12% over 2016 - 2030 -&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;openPR (press release) ResearchMoz added Latest Research Report titled &amp;ldquo; The Big Data Market: 2016 - 2030 - Opportunities, Challenges, Strategies, Industry Verticals and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.arbornetworks.com/arbor-networks-new-arbor-sp-insight-big-data-analytics-extension-to-sp-deployments-raises-the-bar-for-network-visibility&#39;&gt;Arbor Networks New Arbor SP Insight Big Data Analytics Extension to SP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arbor SP Insight adds powerful new visual analytics and a big data repository to Arbor SP while preserving Arbor&amp;rsquo;s unique flow annotations and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.attunity.com/mainframe-data-integration-with-big-data-platforms&#39;&gt;Mainframe Data Integration with Big Data Platforms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and Big Data environments, including all major Hadoop distributions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.business2community.com/blogging/improve-b2b-blogging-era-big-data-01718965&#39;&gt;How to Improve B2B Blogging In the Era of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How can big data boost your B2B blogging efforts? It has long been an influential force in many industries. For example, it has helped airlines to more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/dresner-advisory-services-publishes-2016-140000082.html&#39;&gt;Dresner Advisory Services Publishes 2016 Big Data Analytics Market Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; to and analysis of data contained and managed within the Hadoop ecosystem. According to the 2016 Big Data Analytics Market Study, high tech &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/290464/new-years-resolution-dont-let-big-data-kill-sto.html&#39;&gt;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolution: Don&amp;rsquo;t Let Big Data Kill Storytelling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As agencies, nearing the end of the year often means that our thinking moves to center around data, recapping, reporting, forecasting and P&amp;amp;L  as &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/356926497/storfirst-6-delivers-native-integration-for-netapp-ontap-and-dellemc-isilon-making-big-data-migrations-easier-safer-and-faster-for-the-automated&#39;&gt;Storfirst 6 Delivers Native Integration for NetApp ONTAP and DellEMC Isilon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EIN News (press release) Storfirst 6 Delivers Native Integration for NetApp ONTAP and DellEMC Isilon Making Big Data Migrations Easier, Safer and Faster for the Automated &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bobsguide.com/guide/news/2016/Dec/5/how-data-analytics-and-visualisation-revolutionized-aml/&#39;&gt;How data analytics and visualisation revolutionized AML&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data solutions that support evolving business and regulatory requirements by maintaining an ecosystem of large datasets will become invaluable &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bangkokpost.com/tech/world-updates/1151473/big-data-helped-trump-even-after-he-scorned-it&#39;&gt;Big data helped Trump even after he scorned it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON - Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign &amp;ndash; but those techniques might well have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://guardian.ng/technology/big-data-helped-trump-even-after-he-scorned-it/&#39;&gt;Big data helped Trump even after he scorned it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign  but those techniques might well have propelled him to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.republic-news.org/news/43894/&#39;&gt;Big Data Pharmaceutical Advertising Market Research Report Now Available at&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Republic of East Vancouver Research Corridor has published a new research study titled Big Data Pharmaceutical Advertising Market  Growth, Share, Opportunities, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.claimsjournal.com/news/national/2016/12/05/275316.htm&#39;&gt;Why Analyzing Unstructured Data Benefits Every Claims Manager&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re just catching on to the fact that big data is shaking up the insurance industry in a big way, you&amp;rsquo;re a bit behind the curve. Across all industries &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itproportal.com/news/insurers-still-slow-to-pick-up-big-data/&#39;&gt;Insurers still slow to pick up Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insurance companies are mostly reluctant to use big data analytics to rate their customers&amp;rsquo; driving habits, but the trend is slowly picking up pace, a new &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/05/glow-color-genomics-big-data/&#39;&gt;How These Startups Plan to Use Big Data to Transform Women&amp;rsquo;s Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; is revolutionizing industries like technology and advertising, there is one field that is noticeably lagging when it comes to Big Data: health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/sinequa-ekimetrics-deliver-value-data-130000912.html&#39;&gt;Sinequa and Ekimetrics to Deliver Value from Data with Cognitive Search and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Sports &amp;ldquo;Sinequa&amp;rsquo;s platform is empowering our data scientists to create an end-to-end approach of big data. Teaming up with Sinequa is enabling us to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/12/05/above-the-trend-line-your-industry-rumor-central-for-1252016/&#39;&gt;Above the Trend Line  Your Industry Rumor Central for 12/5/2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week set a record in terms of pure volume of big data industry buzz! There&amp;rsquo;s so much happening, but we&amp;rsquo;re committed to keeping pace for our &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financialexpress.com/economy/big-data-can-drive-india-from-cashful-to-cashless/464972/&#39;&gt;Big Data can drive India from &amp;lsquo;Cashful&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Cashless&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digitization and big data analytics will make it more difficult to get away with under-declaration of wealth and income, help increase tax revenues and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://infocus.emc.com/william_schmarzo/big-data-analytics-customer-holiday-experience/&#39;&gt;Big Data Driving Customers&amp;rsquo; Holiday Experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hadoop is Just the Beginning: Realizing value from big data requires &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bio-itworld.com/2016/12/5/groundbreaking-big-data-platform-can-improve-the-quality-of-cancer-care.aspx&#39;&gt;Groundbreaking Big Data Platform Can Improve The Quality Of Cancer Care&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;December 5, 2016 | I believe it is now possible to end cancer, said Vice President Joe Biden at a recent American Society of Clinical Oncology &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/nimble-storage-exhibit-predictive-flash-platform-2016-gartner-data-center-infrastructure-nyse-nmbl-2180628.htm&#39;&gt;Nimble Storage to Exhibit Predictive Flash Platform at 2016 Gartner Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) Learn how innovations around storage, big data and cloud are fundamentally disrupting datacenter infrastructure as companies embark on delivering &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/MapR-Announces-Speaker-Lineup-for-Big-Data-Everywhere-Bay-Area-and-Los-Angeles-20161205&#39;&gt;MapR Announces Speaker Lineup for Big Data Everywhere Bay Area and Los&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World Big data experts, including presenters from American Express, Qualcomm and SAP, will share their knowledge and discuss best practices related to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.insurancenetworking.com/blogs/data-analytics/assembling-a-top-notch-insurance-analytics-team-37778-1.html&#39;&gt;Assembling a Top-Notch Insurance Analytics Team&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But creating the kind of organization-wide change made possible through big data is easier said than done. A critical component of bringing about &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.sdcexec.com/article/12271216/taming-big-data-in-the-iot&#39;&gt;Taming Big Data in the IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though the story of the Internet of Things (IoT) and Big Data involves sensors and terabytes instead of wild animals, the overall theme is largely the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://technical.ly/brooklyn/2016/12/05/big-data-dark-side-art/&#39;&gt;These Brooklyn artists are exploring the dark side of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tega Brain and Surya Mattu, the creators of Unfit Bits, reveal how algorithms can reinforce social inequalities in an upcoming exhibit tour. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/05/cloud-creating-data-gravity-look-future-cloud-disruption-reinvent/&#39;&gt;Is the cloud creating its own &amp;lsquo;data gravity&amp;rsquo;? A look at the future of the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SiliconANGLE (blog) Cask.co, as Gray described it, is an open-source big data company really focused around big data applications. And a big part of leveraging that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://resources.cio.com/ccd/assets/125228/detail&#39;&gt;IBM Drives Deployment Choices with Latest Hadoop Distribution Release&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IBM is one of four vendors that continue to offer a commercial distribution of Apache Hadoop. In July, the company released its latest version of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchdatacenter.techtarget.com/feature/Challenges-of-IoT-include-big-data-data-analysis-for-enterprise&#39;&gt;Challenges of IoT include big data, data analysis for enterprise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Implementing big data and IoT is difficult for enterprise IT teams due to &amp;hellip; of data via technologies, such as Hadoop and distributed storage systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/05/clouds-role-making-big-data-accessible-reinvent/&#39;&gt;What is the cloud&amp;rsquo;s role in making big data accessible? - #reInvent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the many advantages of cloud regarding data management and analysis have received deep examination, one of the advantages brought to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2016/12/05/895246/0/en/Cloudera-Continues-Global-Momentum-in-Financial-Services-Sector.html&#39;&gt;Cloudera Continues Global Momentum in Financial Services Sector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This big data analytics platform, powered by Apache Hadoop, helps us gain customer insights to increase safety, make risk and underwriting more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/mapr-announces-speaker-lineup-for-big-data-everywhere-bay-area-and-los-angeles-2180700.htm&#39;&gt;MapR Announces Speaker Lineup for Big Data Everywhere Bay Area and Los&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) Big data experts, including presenters from American Express, Qualcomm and SAP, &amp;hellip; Big Data Everywhere (BDE) Los Angeles will be held on Thursday, &amp;hellip; development in open source technologies including Spark and Hadoop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://cornandsoybeandigest.com/technology/proagrica-s-adapt-plug-harnesses-power-big-data-ag-industry&#39;&gt;Proagrica&amp;rsquo;s ADAPT plug-in harnesses power of Big Data for ag industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Editor&amp;rsquo;s Note: Briefing Room is where we run press releases from companies unedited, for your use. Proagrica have announced that they have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.hotelsmag.com/Industry/News/Details/70340&#39;&gt;Labor costs, branding, big data&amp;rsquo;s impact on EMEA: Aethos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aethos Consulting Group Managing Directors Chris Mumford and Thomas Mielke, both based in London, share commentary regarding labor costs, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.healthdatamanagement.com/news/how-big-data-is-improving-breast-cancer-prediction-rates&#39;&gt;How big data is improving breast cancer prediction rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better predicting health outcomes through the analysis of big data are the goals of healthcare analytics. Now, a new method for differentiating between &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.independent.ie/business/media/market-researchers-embrace-the-world-of-big-data-35264501.html&#39;&gt;Market researchers embrace the world of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first Friday in December every year ushers in the beginning of Christmas for many Irish marketers. With their budgets for the following year in the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/big-data-helped-donald-trump-even-after-he-scorned-it-1633704&#39;&gt;Big Data Helped Donald Trump Even After He Scorned It&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump had developed a digital strategy even after winning the nomination. (AFP File Photo). Washington, United States: Donald Trump &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/big-data-helped-donald-trump-even-after-he-scorned-it/articleshow/55784905.cms&#39;&gt;Big data helped Donald Trump even after he scorned it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON: Donald Trump derided the use of data and technology tools for his presidential campaign &amp;ndash; but those techniques might well have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2016/12/04/national/companies-paying-pinpoint-big-data-weather-forecasts/&#39;&gt;More companies paying to pinpoint big-data weather forecasts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A growing number of construction companies, farmers and railways are benefitting from area-specific weather forecasts based on supercomputer &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.desotoedge.com/stocks/attunity-ltd-attu-reviewed-by-analysts-2/194472&#39;&gt;Attunity Ltd. (ATTU) Reviewed By Analysts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attunity Ltd (Attunity) is a provider of Big Data management software &amp;hellip; such as data warehousing, Hadoop, business intelligence (BI) and Big Data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.indrastra.com/2016/12/ST-Privacy-and-Security-concerns-in-Big-Data-002-12-2016-0005.html&#39;&gt;S&amp;amp;T - Privacy and Security concerns in Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Privacy and security in terms of big data is an important issue. &amp;hellip; Prehadoop process validation This step does the representation of the data loading &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financialexpress.com/lifestyle/science/researchers-create-new-method-to-improve-predictions/463831/&#39;&gt;Researchers create new method to improve predictions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers has created a new method to analyse big data that better predicts outcomes in health care, politics and other fields. In an effort &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.hellenicshippingnews.com/big-data-reveals-the-real-picture-of-chinas-economy-but-can-it-survive/&#39;&gt;Big Data Reveals the Real Picture of China&amp;rsquo;s Economy, but Can It Survive?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wu Haishan was at Princeton studying how schools of fish swim together when the crowd behavior of a much bigger group grabbed his attention: his &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://bentleywp.com/398-research-big-2016-papers-data-camaro&#39;&gt;Big data research papers 2016 camaro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;expensive? Split your payment apart - Big data research papers 2016 camaro. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://tech.economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/internet/david-eden-on-the-many-facets-of-ai/55765612&#39;&gt;David Eden on the many facets of AI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The behind-the-scenes algorithms process big data to make our lives more predictable. Big Data offers such insights and often, this is because of an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blogs.oracle.com/bigdataspatialgraph/entry/oracle_big_data_spatial_and3&#39;&gt;Oracle Big Data Spatial and Graph&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;create two Hadoop Configuration object to access the vertices and edges &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itbusinessnet.com/article/Global-Big-Data-Market-2015-2020-4721151&#39;&gt;Global Big Data Market 2015-2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; NOVONOUS estimates that Global Big Data market will &amp;hellip; Technologies such as NoSQL databases and MapReduce/Hadoop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.socialsciencespace.com/2016/12/will-big-data-affect-evolution-social-science/&#39;&gt;How Will Big Data Affect Evolution of Social Science?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and opportunities big data creates? How can we bring down barriers to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/for-machines-analogies-are-just-math&#39;&gt;For Machines, Analogies Are Just Math&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting machines to understand the ins and outs of human communication is still an unmastered science. But see how one aspect of language, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pr.com/press-release/697222&#39;&gt;BlazeClan Achieves Premier Consulting Partner Designation with the AWS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;pr.com (press release) In addition to AWS Premier Consulting Partner recognition, BlazeClan has also achieved the status of AWS Managed Service Partner, AWS Big Data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.broadcom.com/applications/enterprise-storage/big-data-rack-architecture&#39;&gt;Breaking Down Big Data to Drive Data Flow Architecture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;lowering costs, and scaling as needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/12/03/mapr-expands-big-data-innovations-with-new-mapr-ecosystem-pack/&#39;&gt;MapR Expands Big Data Innovations with New MapR Ecosystem Pack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MapR Logo - New 2014_FEATURE MapR Technologies, Inc., provider of the industry&amp;rsquo;s Converged Data Platform, announced the next major release &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio-today.com/story.xhtml?story_id=0030008ZH1U3&#39;&gt;Apple Wants To Fly Rings Around Google Maps with Drones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Maps has the advantage of being around a lot longer than Apple Maps (11 years versus 4). Indeed, it was the default web mapping service for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://gigaom.com/2016/12/01/xavient_2017/&#39;&gt;Big Data Poised to Get Much Bigger in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data is only going to get much bigger, so big in fact that companies attempting to deal with massive and more complex data sets are going to find it &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenbrozak/2016/12/01/siemens-and-northwell-challenge-healthcare-by-planningto-standardize-it/&#39;&gt;Siemens And Northwell Announce Alliance, Enter Big Data Arms Race&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I am at the Forbes Healthcare Summit where Northwell Health and Siemens Healthineers announced a major collaboration to utilize big data in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://customerthink.com/4-gotchas-in-risk-analysis-for-big-data-initiatives/&#39;&gt;4 Gotcha&amp;rsquo;s in Risk Analysis for Big Data Initiatives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Evaluating risk vs. return of a big data initiative can be tricky, especially &amp;hellip; to your new big data solution, new BI tools for Hadoop, or additional Hadoop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-12-01/big-data-reveals-the-real-picture-of-china-s-economy-but-can-it-survive&#39;&gt;Big Data Reveals the Real Picture of China&amp;rsquo;s Economy, but Can It Survive?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big-data gurus such as Wu are providing a sharper picture of China&amp;rsquo;s economy than government statistics, which can be twisted to fit the state&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://ipolitics.ca/2016/12/01/the-future-of-big-data-an-ipolitics-live-event/&#39;&gt;The future of Big Data  an iPolitics live event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data can help individuals make decisions, help businesses offer better services, help governments  and private companies  cut costs. It&amp;rsquo;s an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/02/global-hadoop-market-will-grow-at-a-cagr-of-59-37-during-the-period-2016-2020/&#39;&gt;Global Hadoop Market Will Grow At A CAGR Of 59.37% During The Period&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) Researchmoz added Most up-to-date research on Global Hadoop Market 2016-2020 to its huge collection of research reports. The increased &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.techrepublic.com/article/the-cloud-war-moves-to-machine-learning-does-google-have-an-edge/&#39;&gt;The cloud war moves to machine learning: Does Google have an edge?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In such a world, Google, given its deep experience with big data, has a &amp;hellip; Not that AWS is sitting still, waiting to be big data&amp;rsquo;ed out of existence. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.liaison.com/2016/12/02/pollsters-wrong-big-data-implications/&#39;&gt;The Pollsters Were Wrong: What Are the Big Data Implications?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though polling data indicated a tight race in the final weeks of the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.telecompaper.com/news/combis-presents-big-data-solution-for-financial-industry--1174364&#39;&gt;Combis presents Big Data solution for financial industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Croatian IT services provider Combis has presented a version of its Big Data solution Husky intended for the financial industry during the Trustech &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thehansindia.com/posts/index/Education-&amp;-Careers/2016-12-02/5-day-certificate-course-in-business-analytics-at-UoH/266630&#39;&gt;5-day certificate course in business analytics at UoH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hyderabad: Most of the leading organisations are using business analytics/big data analytics to compete and thrive. But there is a severe shortage of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.ipsos.com/event-connection-between-big-data-behavioural-economics&#39;&gt;[EVENT] The Connection Between Big Data &amp;amp; Behavioural Economics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behavioral Economics. During this webinar, Colin will show how online &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/big-data-week-in-review-integrated-features-rule/&#39;&gt;Big Data week in review: Integrated features rule&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week was full of Big Data news, including new releases, a brand new product, a new acquisition and an update to one of the major Hadoop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://healthitanalytics.com/news/big-data-spokes-tackle-population-health-with-iot-informatics&#39;&gt;Big Data Spokes Tackle Population Health with IoT, Informatics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Academic institutions across the nation are collaborating on big data analytics projects that leverage informatics and the Internet of Things to address &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.citmagazine.com/article/1417554/big-data-helpful-headache&#39;&gt;BIG DATA - helpful or a headache?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data sits high on the agenda for many planners, who are looking at new ways to be personal and relevant, and extend the shelf-life of an event &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3964947&#39;&gt;ZE PowerGroup: Bringing Energy Expertise to Real-Time Big Data Management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SYS-CON Media (press release) But it&amp;rsquo;s challenging to understand all the options  from IaaS and PaaS to newer services like HaaS (Hadoop as a Service) and BDaaS (Big Data as a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.b2becommerceworld.com/2016/12/02/workday-eyes-supply-chains-it-grows-q3-revenue-34&#39;&gt;Workday eyes supply chains and big data as it grows Q3 revenue 34%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Workday eyes supply chains and big data as it grows Q3 revenue 34%. Paul Demery By Paul Demery Managing Editor, B2B E-Commerce. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://gulftoday.ae/portal/f73a3563-b5a7-4761-aada-1c1ec1fdeac2.aspx&#39;&gt;Satyajit Das: A desire for magical solutions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data uses inductive statistics and nonlinear system tools on large data sets to measure and establish relationships, dependencies and identify &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://europeanmovement.eu/event/college-of-europe-panel-debate-on-eu-big-data-regulation/&#39;&gt;College of Europe: Panel Debate on &amp;lsquo;EU Big Data Regulation&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;on &amp;lsquo;EU Big Data Regulation&amp;rsquo;. The event will take place on 12 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/big-data-in-global-retail-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-35-300370998.html&#39;&gt;Big Data in Global Retail market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 35%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data in Retail Industry controls the 9% market share in terms of revenue in &amp;hellip; Technologies such as NoSQL databases and MapReduce/Hadoop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://app.secure.griffith.edu.au/news/2016/11/30/big-data-analytics-nostradamus-of-the-21st-century/&#39;&gt;Big Data analytics  Nostradamus of the 21st century&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;data, according to a Griffith University researcher who correctly predicted &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/telecom-industry-big-data-analytics-adoption--usage-trends-2016-2018-300371030.html&#39;&gt;Telecom Industry: Big Data Analytics Adoption / Usage Trends 2016-2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pyramid Research&amp;rsquo;s Big Data Analytics Adoption / Usage Trends 2016-2018 report examines the overall spend on BDA, market opportunities &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://m.crn.com/news/cloud/300082989/aws-delivers-more-ai-analytics-partnerships-and-a-big-rig-for-moving-big-data.htm&#39;&gt;AWS Delivers More AI, Analytics, Partnerships And A Big Rig For Moving Big&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CRN Amazon Web Services (AWS) showcased several artificial intelligence and data services Wednesday for partners to use in building applications that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/176870/hadoop-industry-major-key-players-active-networks-are-ibm-dell-inc-cisco-systems-inc-hewlettpackard-zettaset-inc-amazon-web-services-analysis-forecast-2022&#39;&gt;Hadoop Industry Major Key Players (Active networks) are IBM, Dell, Inc.,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsMaker (press release) Hadoop Industry Major Key Players (Active networks) are IBM, Dell, Inc., Cisco &amp;hellip; global hadoop market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 53.7% over the &amp;hellip; demand for big data analytics are the factors influencing the market growth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/bernardmarr/2016/12/01/how-big-data-is-used-to-fight-cyber-crime-and-hackers-fascinating-use-case-from-bt/&#39;&gt;How Big Data Is Used To Fight Cyber Crime And Hackers: Fascinating Use Case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forbes Lately Big Data has been put to use in the ongoing battle to stay one step ahead of the hackers and malicious actors  who could be anyone from &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.politico.eu/article/france-struggles-to-balance-privacy-with-big-data/&#39;&gt;France struggles to balance privacy with big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For some, big data is Big Brother, Health Minister Marisol Touraine said earlier this year as she unveiled a related five-year e-health plan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/using-ai-to-clean-up-big-data&#39;&gt;Using AI to Clean Up Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adi Gaskell talks about the challenge of cleansing data and how software, like ActiveClean, uses prediction models that are used with the cleaning &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.hellenicshippingnews.com/big-data-can-ensure-global-enforcement-of-the-imos-requirements-for-sulphur-emissions/&#39;&gt;Big data can ensure global enforcement of the IMO&amp;rsquo;s requirements for&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hellenic Shipping News Worldwide In the wake of the IMO&amp;rsquo;s requirements for a substantial reduction in sulphur emissions from shipping, there is still a big question mark over how the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.saksoft.com/so-how-big-is-big-data/&#39;&gt;So how big is big data?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More data does not mean robust data or better results. But the ability to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businessinsider.in/Reinvent-your-business-with-Big-Data-insights/articleshow/55725234.cms&#39;&gt;Reinvent your business with Big Data insights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has been 15 years since the term big data became mainstream and about six years since it went viral. Still, C-suite executives struggle with &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/log-aggregation-capabilities-and-performance&#39;&gt;Log Aggregation Capabilities and Performance: Part I&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a very in-depth comparison of Log Aggregation comparing using a parallel disk-based message queue like Kafka vs an in-memory data store &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techstory.in/world-aids-day/&#39;&gt;World Aids Day: Time to tap into Big Data for Aids Research !&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A major problem faced by Aids researchers is that there is a data tsunami, which is often leaves the possibility of essential information getting missed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.roberthalf.com/finance/blog/increase-your-worth-with-these-6-big-data-skills&#39;&gt;Increase Your Worth With These 6 Big Data Skills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;professionals need to know about the most essential big data skills. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-11/bu-nwu112916.php&#39;&gt;New website uses big data to address underrepresentation of women in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EurekAlert (press release) BINGHAMTON, NY - A new website created by faculty and students at Binghamton University, State University of New York ranks university &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/A-panel-of-leaders-to-discuss-Assessing-the-Value-of-Your-Big-Data-Investment-20161129&#39;&gt;A panel of leaders to discuss, &amp;lsquo;Assessing the Value of Your Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World CHICAGO, Nov. 29, 2016 /PRNewswire/ Investments in big data analytics continues to rise. Due to today&amp;rsquo;s technology, business leaders now have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/2nd-watch-earns-aws-financial-220104892.html&#39;&gt;2nd Watch Earns AWS Financial Services Competency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2nd Watch has previously earned AWS competencies in Migration, DevOps, Big Data, Marketing and Commerce, Life Sciences and SharePoint and is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://english.anhuinews.com/system/2016/11/30/007516566.shtml&#39;&gt;How Big Data Reveal Your Behavior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thirty-five billion words are exchanged by more than 700 million internet users in China each day, according to a new report examining the behaviour &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/telecom-structured-data-big-data-and-analytics-business-case-market-analysis-and-forecasts-2016---2020-300370272.html&#39;&gt;Telecom Structured Data, Big Data, and Analytics: Business Case, Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire (press release) Communication Service Providers (CSP) acquire and maintain substantial structured and unstructured (Big) data. CSP are working diligently to better &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techstory.in/demonetization-black-money/&#39;&gt;Demonetization: Five ways in which Big Data Analytics can trace Black Money&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Techstory However, modern technologies such as Big Data Analytics can make it possible to trace black money painlessly and unearth the trail in five simple &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.toptechnews.com/article/index.php?story_id=13100AWD0GBD&#39;&gt;HPE Demos &amp;lsquo;The Machine&amp;rsquo; Next-Gen Memory-Driven Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; making it an ideal foundation for a wide range of emerging high-performance compute and data intensive workloads, including big data analytics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/panel-leaders-discuss-assessing-value-223700589.html&#39;&gt;A panel of leaders to discuss, Assessing the Value of Your Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Finance 29, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Investments in big data analytics continues to rise. Due to today&amp;rsquo;s technology, business leaders now have access to data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.sas.com/en_my/insights/articles/big-data/analytic-simulations-using-big-data-to-protect-tiniest-patients.html&#39;&gt;Analytic simulations: Using big data to protect the tiniest patients&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;in the NICU, saving lives (and millions of dollars). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://thefinancialbrand.com/62426/bank-customer-big-data-insights-analytics/&#39;&gt;Banks Don&amp;rsquo;t Know Their Customers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the banking industry responds to the &amp;ldquo;Age of the Individual&amp;rdquo;, big data and advanced analytics will define the winners from the losers. It is more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2016/sap-bnp-paribas-pwc-corporate-treasury-management-fintech-innovation-disruption-blockchain-real-time-payments-big-data-cybersecurity/&#39;&gt;Top Treasury Players Break Down The FinTech Disruption&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shape of treasury management is changing today, thanks to the rise of disruptive technologies, like blockchain, real-time payments and Big Data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cso.com.au/mediareleases/28638/dimension-data-publishes-it-predictions-for-2017/&#39;&gt;Dimension Data Publishes IT Predictions for 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things is delivering on the promise of big data IoT will deliver on the promise of big data. Increasingly, big data projects are going &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.linkedin.com/learning/transitioning-from-data-warehousing-to-big-data/?trk=publicProfile-public_profile_v3_desktop-learningFeedm014%3Aa001--385663_learning&#39;&gt;Transitioning from Data Warehousing to Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and build on what you already know to plan a roadmap to a better big data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://realmoney.thestreet.com/articles/11/30/2016/splunk-can-big-data-produce-big-rally&#39;&gt;Splunk: Can Big Data Produce a Big Rally?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Splunk SPLK is rallying ahead of the opening Wednesday. Does it have the right stuff to break out over resistance and start a new up-leg? Let&amp;rsquo;s visit &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.paymentssource.com/news/fis-starts-drilling-into-banks-big-data-for-payments&#39;&gt;FIS starts drilling into banks&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;big data&amp;rsquo; for payments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data was supposed to unleash a lot of powerful insights for banks, but many financial institutions still haven&amp;rsquo;t found a way to harness their own data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/11/30/two-must-attend-events-by-mapr/&#39;&gt;Big Data Events by MapR Coming to So Cal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MapR, the company behind the Converged Data Platform, is hosting two very timely upcoming big data events in Southern California. If you find &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://security.itbusinessnet.com/article/2016-Phoenix-Data-Conference---Showcasing-Emerging-Trends-in-Big-Data-4715606&#39;&gt;2016 Phoenix Data Conference - Showcasing Emerging Trends in Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 3rd Annual Phoenix Data Conference, one of the largest big data &amp;hellip; use cases clearly showed that the Hadoop environment is now mainstream &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/clearlake-capital-backed-syncsort-acquires-130400256.html&#39;&gt;Clearlake Capital-Backed Syncsort Acquires Trillium Software&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;With most large enterprises making significant investments in Big Data for &amp;hellip; while leading the industry in delivering them for Hadoop and Spark. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bbva.com/en/us/news/current-news/todays-number-big-data/&#39;&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s number is about big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;integrated big data technologies by 2018 and 48 % will have invested in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://phys.org/news/2016-11-big-analyticsnostradamus-21st-century.html&#39;&gt;Big data analyticsNostradamus of the 21st century&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In a public address on big data the day before I even correctly identified all main states that Trump would win (including Florida, North Carolina and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.universityherald.com/articles/52725/20161130/big-data.htm&#39;&gt;The Do&amp;rsquo;s And Don&amp;rsquo;ts Of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data Do&amp;rsquo;s And Dont&amp;rsquo;s Microsoft Research Senior Developer Dave Brown uses a large touch screen to demonstrate the NUIGraph visualization and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.techrepublic.com/article/amazon-goes-all-in-on-ai-and-big-data-at-aws-reinvent-2016/&#39;&gt;Amazon goes all-in on AI and big data at AWS re:Invent 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This significantly lowers the bar for everyday IT to utilize big data analytics to glean insights. To go along with these new services, Jassy also &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-management.com/white_papers/scaling-data-integration-to-handle-big-data-10030381-1.html&#39;&gt;Scaling data integration to handle big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s competitive on-line world, the speed of change in customer behaviour is increasing. In addition, in industries such as retail banking, car &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://rapidminer.com/taming-complexity-hadoop-analytics/&#39;&gt;Taming the Complexity of Hadoop Analytics: RapidMiner Radoop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Analytics and configuring it just got EASIER! Learn Now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://icrunchdata.com/federal-cloud-big-data-spending-poised-double-next-5-years/&#39;&gt;Federal Cloud and Big Data Spending Poised to Double in Next 5 Years&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cloud computing and big data represent areas of future growth within federal agencies&amp;rsquo; budgets, according to a new market analysis and report from &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.economiccalendar.com/2016/11/30/big-data-company-splunk-splk-gains-on-solid-q3-financials/&#39;&gt;Big Data Company Splunk (SPLK) Gains on Solid Q3 Financials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Splunk Inc (NASDAQ:SPLK) released its fiscal 2017 third-quarter financial results after the market close yesterday, and the big data software &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://talkincloud.com/cloud-computing/hpe-demonstrates-its-futuristic-vision-big-data-processing&#39;&gt;HPE Demonstrates its Futuristic Vision of Big Data Processing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Machine is an ominous, post-apocalyptic sounding name for a massive HPE research project, but it&amp;rsquo;s one that&amp;rsquo;s generating a lot of buzz. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/zoomdata-now-integrated-amazon-services-194311732.html&#39;&gt;Zoomdata Now Integrated in Amazon Web Services Support Portal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LAS VEGAS, NV&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - Nov 30, 2016) - AWS re:Invent - Zoomdata, developers of a visual analytics platform for big data, today announced at &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://ipolitics.ca/2016/11/30/the-future-of-big-data-an-ipolitics-live-event/&#39;&gt;The future of Big Data  an iPolitics live event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data enthusiasts gathered at the Westin in Ottawa Wednesday morning for a series of panel sessions on &amp;lsquo;big data&amp;rsquo; and innovation. Anthony &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://apex.aero/2016/11/30/big-data-aviation-industry-case-becoming-data-driven&#39;&gt;Big Data in the Aviation Industry: The Case for Becoming Data-Driven&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;APEX Insight: During the CAPA Asia Summit in Singapore earlier this month, airline and travel industry IT experts discussed big data and how to use it &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/sparse-versus-dense-document-values-with-apache-lu&#39;&gt;Sparse vs Dense Document Values with Apache Lucene&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently Elastic has made some big changes to Apache Lucene around how doc values are indexed and searched, including new nightly &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theactuary.com/opinion/2016/12/big-data-in-practice-how-45-successful-companies-used-big-data-analytics-to-deliver-extraordinary-results/&#39;&gt;Big Data In Practice: How 45 successful companies used big data analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Actuary It presents case studies of diverse companies embracing the use of big data analytics, leading to gaining valuable insights that are used to enhance &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bandt.com.au/media/seven-west-media-deploys-big-data-solution-deliver-innovation-audience-engagement&#39;&gt;Seven West Media Deploys Big Data Solution To Deliver Innovation In&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;B&amp;amp;T Seven West Media Deploys Big Data Solution To Deliver Innovation In &amp;hellip; of secure data management and analytics platform built on Apache Hadoop, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/356126161/how-to-simplify-the-science-of-big-data-analytics&#39;&gt;How to simplify the science of big data analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We dedicated to make advanced big data analytics more accessible and approachable, while allowing people to discover actioanable insights in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-29/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://inter.viewcentral.com/events/cust/default.aspx?cid=arcsight&amp;pid=1&amp;lid=5&amp;bu_id=7,10&#39;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=http://techblog.netflix.com/search/label/big%2520data&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYASoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNEYMlTikWjHydYhiWHLAX4xr_beMw&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=http://techblog.netflix.com/search/label/big%2520data&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYASoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNEYMlTikWjHydYhiWHLAX4xr_beMw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.fusionex-international.com/strataconf2016&#39;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://ssrn.com/abstract%3D2394683&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYAyoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNH3PJGIUPui1aksxWCQkhKz5wH6cA&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://ssrn.com/abstract%3D2394683&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYAyoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNH3PJGIUPui1aksxWCQkhKz5wH6cA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strata Hadoop Conference 2016 Strata + Hadoop World Conference &amp;hellip; Fusionex Big Data Analytics helps you make the best decisions possible; and who knows, you might even &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://docs.oracle.com/en/cloud/paas/big-data-prep-cloud/index.html&#39;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://www.imi.europa.eu/sites/default/files/uploads/documents/Events/SF%25202015/BigData_Concept_29May2015.pdf&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYBSoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHnyxc5O4rn2f7VUcIsCR1JF3jkQw&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://www.imi.europa.eu/sites/default/files/uploads/documents/Events/SF%25202015/BigData_Concept_29May2015.pdf&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYBSoTMTQxMjgyMTM0MDcwNjY3MzA5NTIaNTQyYWJhYzcwYzAwMzI1ZTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNHnyxc5O4rn2f7VUcIsCR1JF3jkQw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oracle Big Data Preparation Cloud Service Oracle Big Data Preparation Cloud Service is a managed Platform as a Service (PaaS) cloud-based offering that enables you to rapidly ingest, repair, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2016/11/28/503035862/big-data-coming-in-faster-than-biomedical-researchers-can-process-it&#39;&gt;Big Data Coming In Faster Than Biomedical Researchers Can Process It&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biomedical research is going big-time: Megaprojects that collect vast stores of data are proliferating rapidly. But scientists&amp;rsquo; ability to make sense of all &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/kimberlywhitler/2016/11/27/are-big-data-predictive-analytics-and-social-media-getting-in-the-way-of-basic-marketing/&#39;&gt;Are Big Data, Predictive Analytics And Social Media Getting In The Way Of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forbes Is it possible that all of the emphasis on newer marketingcoping with big data, social media, digital, and sophisticated analyticsis preventing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bostonglobe.com/opinion/2016/11/23/big-data-big-election-fail/LdCiWMhbqpVeOSu9LdAgnK/story.html&#39;&gt;Big data&amp;rsquo;s big election fail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The season of computer-assisted consumption is hard upon us and, as shoppers, we are fairly sanguine by now about the data sweeps that infest our &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://origin-nyi.thehill.com/blogs/pundits-blog/presidential-campaign/307303-did-big-data-get-trumped-in-election-2016&#39;&gt;Did Big Data get &amp;lsquo;Trumped&amp;rsquo; in Election 2016?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Trump&amp;rsquo;s big data gamble didn&amp;rsquo;t last, it never defined his operation. Late in the campaign Trump did expand his data team but it almost certainly &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.ft.com/content/1b614d10-9a03-11e6-8f9b-70e3cabccfae&#39;&gt;Big data promise exponential change in healthcare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a top Formula One team is using pit stop data-gathering technology to help a drugmaker improve the way it makes ventilators for asthma &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-management.com/news/big-data-analytics/big-data-robotics-having-a-big-impact-on-mining-industry-10030365-1.html&#39;&gt;Big Data, Robotics Having a Big Impact On Mining Industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The growing use of big data analytics, machine-to-machine (M2M) and Internet of Things (IoT) technologies is having a huge impact on many sectors, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/2016-phoenix-data-conference---showcasing-emerging-trends-in-big-data-603547176.html&#39;&gt;2016 Phoenix Data Conference - Showcasing Emerging Trends in Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discussions around data ingestion, new developments in big data, security, predictive analytics, IOT, leveraging Hadoop and Spark, machine learning &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.smartdatacollective.com/philip-piletic/450954/how-big-data-helps-boost-marketing-conversion-rates&#39;&gt;How Big Data Helps Boost Marketing Conversion Rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data is one of these developments, and it has the potential to transform the manner in which advertising is approached. Problems like price &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/zettaset-announces-advanced-encryption-platform-for-big-data-in-the-cloud-2178992.htm&#39;&gt;Zettaset Announces Advanced Encryption Platform for Big Data in the Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - Nov 29, 2016) - Zettaset, the leader in Big Data security, today announced availability of its advanced data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techseen.com/2016/11/29/big-data-trends-tableau/&#39;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s in stock for Big Data in 2017; Tableau predicts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the focus on big data analytics skills will continue to grow as it &amp;hellip; With Hadoop, they can process lots of data, but the data isn&amp;rsquo;t generally &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.motorship.com/news101/industry-news/maersk-drilling-targets-big-data-maintenance-savings&#39;&gt;Maersk Drilling targets big data maintenance savings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maersk Drilling is collaborating with GE on a pilot project that aims to harness data analytics to increase the productivity of drilling vessels and reduce &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.opengovasia.com/blogs/5-opengov-expert-opinion/post/7242-gaining-big-data-insights-with-spatial-temporal-analytics&#39;&gt;Gaining Big Data Insights with Spatial-Temporal Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leonard is a techno-commercial leader, with over 20 years of experience, spanning Consulting Services, Solution Development, Industry Lead, Sales &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://ascent.atos.net/big-data-advanced-analytics-lasting-investment/&#39;&gt;Big Data and Advanced Analytics: A Lasting Investment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;of Big Data and Advanced Analytics. Whatever their size, whatever their &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.yahoo.com/tech/federal-cloud-big-data-spending-poised-nearly-double-140000584.html&#39;&gt;Federal Cloud and Big Data Spending Poised to Nearly Double between 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo News HERNDON, Va., Nov. 29, 2016 /PRNewswire-USNewswire/ &amp;ndash; According to Deltek&amp;rsquo;s new GovWin IQ report Federal Priorities: Cloud, Big Data, Mobility, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nzherald.co.nz/technology/news/article.cfm?c_id=5&amp;objectid=11757150&#39;&gt;How insurers could use &amp;lsquo;big data&amp;rsquo; to charge you more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;British financial regulator, FCA, has warned that insurance companies could start charging higher premiums to customers who are less likely to switch &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dabcc.com/democratizing-big-data-analytics-for-the-masses/&#39;&gt;Democratizing Big Data Analytics for the Masses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone in the private and public sector is eager to employ Big Data Analytics to glean better understanding from the ecosystem around them in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://thehill.com/blogs/congress-blog/economy-budget/307850-sec-radically-changes-its-approach-to-investigating&#39;&gt;SEC radically changes its approach to investigating insider trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, armed and emboldened with an internal analytics platform and powerful data mining tools, the SEC is aggressively analyzing &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; to first &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161129005560/en/Axtria%C2%AE-Announces-Strategic-Agreement-Improve-Productivity-Effectiveness&#39;&gt;Axtria Inc. Announces a Strategic Agreement to Improve Productivity &amp;amp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) BERKELEY HEIGHTS, N.J.&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Axtria, a global big data analytics company, is pleased to announce a strategic agreement with &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blog.revolutionanalytics.com/2016/11/edx-microsoft-r.html&#39;&gt;Free online course: Analyzing big data with Microsoft R Server&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;performance problems when attempting to analyze large data sets, you might &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.generali.com/media/press-releases/all/2016/Generali-receives-the-Big-Data-Innovation-Award-from-Politecnico-di-Milano.html&#39;&gt;Generali receives the Big Data Innovation Award from Politecnico di Milano&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Politecnico di Milano in the Innovative governance model for the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://hbr.org/2016/11/the-promise-and-challenge-of-big-data-for-pharma&#39;&gt;The Promise and Challenge of Big Data for Pharma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The emergence of big data, as well as advancements in data science approaches and technology, is providing pharmaceutical companies with an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://phys.org/news/2016-11-website-big-underrepresentation-women-philosophy.html&#39;&gt;New website uses big data to address underrepresentation of women in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phys.Org A new website created by faculty and students at Binghamton University, State University of New York ranks university philosophy departments and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3962377&#39;&gt;Blackbaud&amp;rsquo;s Big Data #GivingTuesday Update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Nov. 29, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Blackbaud, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading cloud software company powering social good who processes a majority &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://wunc.org/post/big-data-coming-faster-biomedical-researchers-can-process-it&#39;&gt;Big Data Coming In Faster Than Biomedical Researchers Can Process It&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biomedical research is going big-time: Megaprojects that collect vast stores of data are proliferating rapidly. But scientists&amp;rsquo; ability to make sense all that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://gcn.com/articles/2016/11/29/kentucky-intelligent-transportation.aspx&#39;&gt;Kentucky plows through big data on winter roadways&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kentucky plows through big data on winter roadways &amp;hellip; The open source Hadoop and Spark technologies were game changers, Kumar &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cfoinnovation.com/story/12249/cybersecurity-big-data-culture-are-key-priorities-internal-auditors&#39;&gt;Cybersecurity, Big Data, Culture Are Key Priorities for Internal Auditors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, nearly half of the organizations surveyed have made investments to effectively manage big data, and culture remains an underlying cause &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3962500&#39;&gt;A panel of leaders to discuss, Assessing the Value of Your Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SYS-CON Media (press release) CHICAGO, Nov. 29, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Investments in big data analytics continues to rise. Due to today&amp;rsquo;s technology, business leaders now have &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.evolutionnews.org/2016/11/in_election_201103321.html&#39;&gt;In Election 2016, Why Big Data Took a Tumble&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Presidential election results threw Silicon Valley off in more ways than one. Not only did the favored candidate fail to get elected, the surprise &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com.au/news/seven-west-media-taps-cloudera-and-contexti-for-big-data-solution-for-rio-olympics-442954&#39;&gt;Seven West Media taps Cloudera and Contexti for big data solution for Rio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CRN Australia Seven West Media  parent of Channel 7, Pacific Magazines and The West Australian  has enlisted Sydney-based Contexti to deploy a big data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blogs.oracle.com/datawarehousing/entry/big_data_sql_quick_start15&#39;&gt;Big Data SQL Quick Start. Big Data SQL over complex data types in Oracle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data SQL over complex data types in Oracle NoSQL. &amp;hellip; In this example we are going to show you how to use Oracle Big Data SQL over these &amp;hellip; .oracle.com/cd/NOSQL/html/examples/hadoop/hive/table/package-summary.html# &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.nbr.co.nz/article/david-leach-appointed-ceo-spark-ventures-big-data-division-qrious-b-197003&#39;&gt;David Leach appointed boss of Spark Ventures&amp;rsquo; big data division Qrious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;David Leach, the former senior vice-president at Orion Health, has been appointed chief executive of Spark&amp;rsquo;s big data venture Qrious. Qrious, which &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-11-22/big-data-is-a-big-mess-for-hedge-funds-hunting-for-trade-signals&#39;&gt;Big Data Is a Big Mess for Hedge Funds Hunting for Trade Signals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was big data&amp;rsquo;s big moment. The most unfathomable U.S. presidential race in memory gave Predata, a startup firm backed by hedge fund manager &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizcommunity.com/Article/196/379/154129.html&#39;&gt;Big Data and the power of cross-industry data sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data is prolific; it&amp;rsquo;s ubiquitous and pertains to virtually every aspect of life and its ability to offer additional value to customers - and, in turn, the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketingtechnews.net/news/2016/nov/22/big-data-really-future-marketing/&#39;&gt;Is big data really the future of marketing?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketing data is evolving: from the generic to the specific; from market trends to individual habits and from historic actions to real-time engagement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.neopost.com/en/newsroom/blog/how-big-data-can-create-value-for-customers&#39;&gt;How Big Data can Create Value for Customers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not Just Target Them&amp;rdquo; by Niraj Dawar explains that: &amp;ldquo;The questions that need &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizcommunity.com/Article/196/78/154172.html&#39;&gt;Big data is like sex, everyone talks about it but no one has it - this and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bizcommunity.com The big digital topics globally are the same that we see in South Africa: programmatic, big data, video, location and attribution. One major issue being &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mondovisione.com/media-and-resources/news/the-challenges-for-insurance-and-regulators-in-a-big-data-world-speech-by-and/&#39;&gt;Enter your email address to receive regular updates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am going to start with what is often known as Big Data. My comments draw on the FCA&amp;rsquo;s recent paper on Big Data though I don&amp;rsquo;t do justice to the full &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://allafrica.com/stories/201611220221.html&#39;&gt;East Africa: #WTIS16 - Itu to Launch Measuring the Information Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AllAfrica.com As in the last year, WTIS-16 will also dedicate a session on the topic of big data, where ITU has developed a number of concrete projects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://federalnewsradio.com/big-data/2016/11/agencies-use-big-data-improve-health-security-save-money/&#39;&gt;How agencies use big data to improve health, security, save money&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for using it, others have been using data to improve their services for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-management.com/news/big-data-analytics/to-achieve-advanced-analytics-start-with-big-data-integration-10030322-1.html&#39;&gt;To Achieve Advanced Analytics, Start with Big Data Integration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The promise of big data is virtually unlimited. Employing advanced analytics throughout an enterprise can deliver huge competitive advantages &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scoop.co.nz/stories/BU1611/S00874/new-ceo-of-spark-ventures-big-data-division-qrious.htm&#39;&gt;New CEO of Spark Ventures big data division Qrious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nov. 22 (BusinessDesk) - David Leach, the former senior vice president at Orion Health, has been appointed chief executive of Spark&amp;rsquo;s big data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/Internet-Infrastructure-Service-Provider-SinoBBD-Reshapes-the-Big-Data-Industry-with-the-Power-of-Integration-20161122&#39;&gt;Internet Infrastructure Service Provider SinoBBD Reshapes the Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World During the event, Internet Infrastructure Provider Beijing Big Data Group (&amp;ldquo;SinoBBD&amp;rdquo;) held a press conference toannounce their strategy to build an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.whatech.com/market-research/it/230298-detailed-examination-of-the-global-hadoop-market-that-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-53-7-from-2015-to-2022&#39;&gt;Detailed examination of the Global hadoop market that is expected to grow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WhaTech &amp;hellip; demand for big data analytics are the factors influencing the market growth. &amp;hellip; Hadoop application software has the dominant share in global market and is &amp;hellip; North America has the largest regional market for Hadoop led by the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.talend.com/blog/2016/11/22/catch-the-big-data-wave-talend-named-leader-in-forrester-wave%E2%84%A2-big-data-fabric-q4&#39;&gt;Catch the Big Data Wave - Talend Named Leader in Forrester Wave&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;them in a big data platform technology, such as Hadoop and Apache Spark, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://spacenews.com/big-data-a-big-market-for-small-satellites/&#39;&gt;Big data a big market for small satellites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Planet Labs Doves ISS Planet is one of a number of companies developing small satellite constellations to provide imagery or other data of the Earth &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.healthcare-informatics.com/article/analytics/asco-s-cancerlinq-harnessing-big-data-build-learning-health-system&#39;&gt;ASCO&amp;rsquo;s CancerLinQ is Harnessing Big Data to Build a Learning Health System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two years ago, the American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO) announced the launch of an initiative to build a big data platform, called &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.healthdatamanagement.com/news/why-big-data-is-key-for-better-infectious-disease-surveillance-modeling&#39;&gt;Why big data is key for better infectious disease surveillance, modeling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead, big data drawn from electronic health records, social media, the Internet and other digital data are emerging as potentially more timely and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://chippewa.com/dunnconnect/news/opinion/editorial/other-view-beating-the-odds-why-big-data-isn-t/article_a808ec8d-6e2d-54bd-bc80-28de8431682b.html&#39;&gt;Other view: Beating the odds: Why Big Data isn&amp;rsquo;t destiny&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this Oct. 15, 2013, file photo, Chuck Goolsbee, site director for Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Prineville data centers, shows the computer servers that store users&amp;rsquo; &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.insurancebusinessonline.com.au/au/news/breaking-news/competition-to-drive-big-data-uptake-227330.aspx&#39;&gt;Competition to drive big data uptake&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Competition to drive big data uptake Increased competition within the industry will mean firms have to invest in big data, with one expert believing it &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.infoq.com/presentations/big-data-georgia-aquarium&#39;&gt;How Predictive Analytics Boosts the Customer Experience at the Georgia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InfoQ.com Managing Big Data has become a major competitive advantage for many organizations and hence maintaining a proper analytics platform is vital for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.ft.com/content/ac04817c-abf9-11e6-ba7d-76378e4fef24&#39;&gt;Managers push back against the certainties of big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clay Christensen tells a good joke about a tour of heaven. How come there&amp;rsquo;s no data here? the Harvard professor asks his celestial guide. Because &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://financefeeds.com/tradency-ceo-lior-nabat-true-proponent-entrepreneurs/&#39;&gt;Tradency CEO Lior Nabat is a true proponent of entrepreneurs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under the leadership of Lior Nabat, Tradency has gathered a tremendous amount of big data, which led to the development of the company&amp;rsquo;s RoboX &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.hitcentral.eu/healthtech-wire/%E2%80%98you%E2%80%99ve-got-keep-it-simple-make-it-work-make-it-think%E2%80%99&#39;&gt;&amp;lsquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve got to keep it simple; make it work; make it think.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data and genomic technologies help to improve diagnosis, prognosis and treatment of patients. Have you messages that will inspire our readers, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.rcrwireless.com/20161121/opinion/reader-forum-3-levels-big-data-success-telecom-market-tag10&#39;&gt;Reader Forum: 3 levels of big data success for the telecom market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks Apache Hadoop, it is possible to store and compute massive amounts of disparate structured, unstructured or semistructured data sources at a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/384698/Hadoop-Market-is-to-Cross-US-50-0-Billion-by-2020.html&#39;&gt;Hadoop Market is to Cross US$ 50.0 Billion by 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hadoop is open source technology used for storing and organizing data in a bunch of commodity hardware. Hadoop gives very big amount of data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://military-technologies.net/2016/11/21/big-data-enabled-market-by-manufacturerstypesregions-and-applications-research-report-forecast-to-2019/&#39;&gt;Big Data Enabled Market by Manufacturers,Types,Regions and Applications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Military Technologies Com Publish a New Market Research Report On  Big Data Enabled &amp;hellip; with knowledge of handling the data in Hadoop and other big data related &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.hitcentral.eu/healthtech-wire/s%C3%A3o-jo%C3%A3o-hospital-center-portugal-recognised-inaugural-european-awards-ceremony&#39;&gt;So Joo Hospital Center in Portugal recognised at inaugural European&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Health IT Central This winning project from the So Joo Hospital Center named is HVITAL: Transforming Hospital Big Data into real insights that empower clinical &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-management.com/news/big-data-analytics/operations-vs-insights-how-to-make-sense-of-the-right-data-10030315-1.html&#39;&gt;Operations vs. Insights: How to Make Sense of the Right Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be successful, companies need automation processes together with the right strategies that allow data teams to focus on big data insights, not &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.timeshighereducation.com/blog/using-big-data-and-predictive-analytics-recruit-international-students&#39;&gt;Using big data and predictive analytics to recruit international students&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year, several articles and conference presentations have been made on big data and predictive analytics and the impact on several aspects of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/11/21/at-the-speed-of-big-data-revolutionizing-shipping-and-logistics/&#39;&gt;At the Speed of Big Data  Revolutionizing Shipping and Logistics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;shannon-vaillancourt In this special guest feature, Shannon Vaillancourt, president and founder of RateLinx, discusses how big data is helping the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.medicalplasticsnews.com/news/medical-devices/how-pharma-can-benefit-from-big-data-and-asthma-intelligence/&#39;&gt;How big data is benefitting asthma devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pharmaceutical companies are set to benefit from intelligence on asthma as Aerobit, provider of a smart respiratory device, teams with artificial &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://business.financialpost.com/entrepreneur/growth-strategies/how-the-rise-of-mobile-and-big-data-are-a-blessing-for-gis-technology&#39;&gt;How the rise of mobile and big data are a blessing for one GIS-based&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Financial Post Handout/Esri Canada Alex Miller, founder of Esri Canada, says in part he is driven by what GIS can do to help make the world more sustainable by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://pulse.ng/events/digitech-conference-inaugural-edition-on-data-driven-innovation-for-businesses-holding-this-november-id5789962.html&#39;&gt;Digitech Conference Inaugural Edition on data-driven innovation for&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pulse Nigeria The Digitech Conference is a series of Conversations on Big Data and its Emerging possibilities, bringing together the top minds in various information &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.channelweb.co.uk/crn-uk/news/2477918/arrow-finds-out-how-happy-london-is-in-bid-to-help-partners&#39;&gt;Arrow finds out how happy London is in bid to help partners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arrow has launched a big data project to find out how happy London is in a bid to help channel partners explain the technology to their customers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/press-releases/blockchain-set-greatest-impact-banking-next-decade/&#39;&gt;Why Blockchain Is Set To Have The Greatest Impact On Banking Over The Next&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoinDesk Innovation Enterprise hosts the Big Data &amp;amp; Analytics for Banking Summit at the Crowne Plaza Times Square on December 7 &amp;amp; 8. Unite with over 150 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.out-law.com/en/articles/2016/november/merkel-calls-for-balanced-approach-to-data-protection/&#39;&gt;Merkel calls for balanced approach to data protection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Germany has traditionally been cautious over data collection, but if countries are too restrictive then &amp;ldquo;big data management will not be possible&amp;rdquo;, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/11/21/alluxio-revolutionizes-enterprise-big-data-launches-industrys-first-solution-to-unify-data-at-memory-speed/&#39;&gt;Alluxio Revolutionizes Enterprise Big Data, Launches Industry&amp;rsquo;s First&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;insideBIGDATA Alluxio provides a unified view of enterprise data that spans disparate storage systems, locations and clouds, allowing any big data compute &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.enterprisetech.com/solution_content/hpe/health-life-sciences/bill-mannel-vice-president-general-manager-hpc-big-data-iot-solutions-hpe-servers-hewlett-packard-enterprise/&#39;&gt;Bill Mannel, Vice President &amp;amp; General Manager  HPC, Big Data &amp;amp; IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EnterpriseTech Genomic sequencing has progressed so rapidly that researchers can now analyze the genetic profiles of healthy individuals to uncover mutations that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://healthitanalytics.com/news/prioritizing-preventive-value-based-care-with-big-data-analytics&#39;&gt;Prioritizing Preventive Value-Based Care with Big Data Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Success in the value-based care environment requires a familiarity with big data analytics that can fuel population health management efforts and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.educationdive.com/news/students-expect-big-data-to-aid-persistence-performance/430851/&#39;&gt;Students expect big data to aid persistence, performance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to eCampus News, sentiment is growing among college students for data cultivation and analytics to play a larger role in their personal &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2016/11/21/big_data_dev_risks/&#39;&gt;Even big data devs make big data security gaffes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apache Big Data Europe Big data application programmers routinely download and execute unverified code, opening the door to information-stealing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/11/21/above-the-trend-line-your-industry-rumor-central-for-11212016/&#39;&gt;Above the Trend Line  Your Industry Rumor Central for 11/21/2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve had a very active week here at insideBIGDATA with big data moving forward at a frenetic pace. We&amp;rsquo;ll start our weekly roundup with new &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.computerdealernews.com/blog/trump-victory-bad-for-big-data/51617&#39;&gt;Trump victory bad for big data?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the over-arching narratives in the big data movement is that data can provide the necessary insights for businesses to make good decisions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3151126&#39;&gt;Big Data Market Estimated to reach $72B USD by 2021 with a CAGR of 20.8%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OrbisResearch.com has published The Big Data Market: Business Case, Market Analysis and Forecasts 2016-2021 market report to its research &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.insurancenetworking.com/news/innovation/the-hanover-names-big-data-entrepreneur-to-lead-strategy-37744-1.html&#39;&gt;The Hanover Names Big Data Entrepreneur to Lead Strategy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keim&amp;rsquo;s last job was as the co-founder of HealthReveal, a big data and analytics company targeting healthcare. He also has insurance strategy &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://macaudailytimes.com.mo/macao-big-data-forum-2016-computer-engineers-voice-opinions-smart-city-development.html&#39;&gt;Macao Big Data Forum 2016 - Computer engineers voice opinions on smart city&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Macau Daily Times Three experts on data management were invited to the University of Macau, to participate in the Macao Big Data Forum 2016, last week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizjournals.com/portland/news/2016/11/21/portlands-corios-brings-big-data-to-executives.html&#39;&gt;Portland&amp;rsquo;s Corios brings big data to executives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technology Association of Oregon president Skip Newberry talks big data with &amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s much more exciting to talk about big data than, say, statistics and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Nov 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-11-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://newsok.com/article/5527338&#39;&gt;Big debate about Shakespeare finally settled by big data: Marlowe gets his&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsOK.com Now, for the first time and with a bit of help from computers and big data, the Oxford University Press will add Christopher Marlowe as a co-author in all &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.vnews.com/Consumer-Confidential-Medical-privacy-threatened-by--big-data--5370836&#39;&gt;Consumer Confidential: Medical Privacy Threatened By &amp;lsquo;Big Data&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the most prominent example of how public and private insurers are spending millions of dollars on big data  using advanced technology to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://thetechnews.com/2016/11/20/predictive-world-can-forecast-your-future-using-big-data/&#39;&gt;Predictive World can forecast your future using big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day, internet users leave associated data series of over 2.5 gigabytes. With this incredible amount of information, it&amp;rsquo;s quite possible to tell a lot &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.science20.com/news_articles/storytelling_deconstructed_vonnegut_was_right_about_just_six_emotional_story_lines_says_big_data-180676&#39;&gt;Storytelling Deconstructed: Vonnegut Was Right About Just Six Emotional&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science 2.0 Our most beloved works of fiction hide well-trodden narratives - people want them, people expects them by now - and big data analysis can determine &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://itnewsafrica.com/iot/&#39;&gt;Internet of Things Forum Africa - 31 May 2017,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things (IoT) represents one of the most transformative technological phenomena to emerge in the 21st century. Its impact will be far &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.jsonline.com/story/opinion/contributors/2016/11/20/keith-personal-data-trumps-big-data/94151600/&#39;&gt;Keith: Personal data trumps big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Democrats relied on the classical 20th century big data of anonymous surveys, better known as polling. The Republicans relied on micro-targeting &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/10-big-data-trends-for-2017&#39;&gt;10 Big Data Trends for 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More and more organizations will be adopting Hadoop and other big data stores, in turn, vendors will rapidly introduce new, innovative Hadoop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>