<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Things on Crypt0 News</title>
    <link>//crypt0.net/categories/things/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Things on Crypt0 News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Dataence. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 09:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crypt0.net/categories/things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Companies boost spends on cyber security</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/companies-boost-spends-on-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 09:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/companies-boost-spends-on-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Dhanya Thakkar, MD and VP-APAC at Trend Micro, says, &amp;ldquo;Ransomware has been around a long time, but how quickly it spread this time from machine to machine is new.&amp;rdquo; Ransomware are malicious software that are designed to block access to a computer system, typically by encryption. The attackers &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT startup Moeco raises $5 million from blockchain firm Bitfury</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/iot-startup-moeco-raises-5-million-from-blockchain-firm-bitfury/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 09:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/iot-startup-moeco-raises-5-million-from-blockchain-firm-bitfury/</guid>
      <description>blockchain company Bitfury. Moeco uses the blockchain to build its IoT data routing platform and will now be implementing Bitfury&amp;rsquo;s Exonum protocol. Moeco is a service platform that enables customers to deploy citywide IoT &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet of Things coming to South Australia after French firm Sigfox</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/the-internet-of-things-coming-to-south-australia-after-french-firm-sigfox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 09:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/the-internet-of-things-coming-to-south-australia-after-french-firm-sigfox/</guid>
      <description>The Advertiser The Internet of Things, which is widely considered to be the next digital revolution, is still a mystery to many South Australians. However, SA will be the first state with complete access to a cheap way to connect millions of devices. French company Sigfox has signed a Memorandum of Understanding with &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WISeKey and OISTE.ORG announce a unique new Global RoT for IoT designed to</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/wisekey-and-oisteorg-announce-a-unique-new-global-rot-for-iot-designed-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 07:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/wisekey-and-oisteorg-announce-a-unique-new-global-rot-for-iot-designed-to/</guid>
      <description>GlobeNewswire (press release) WISeKey provides a full suite of secure microcontrollers, such as VaultIC and MicroXsafe, that act as secure elements in an IoT device. WISeKey&amp;rsquo;s chips are designed to protect critical device operations like secure boot, code signing, firmware update validations, protect the device identity and &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet of Things to drive the digital transformation of government and</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/internet-of-things-to-drive-the-digital-transformation-of-government-and/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 06:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/internet-of-things-to-drive-the-digital-transformation-of-government-and/</guid>
      <description>Markets Insider We are Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s leading organizer of Machine-to-Machine (M2M) and Internet of Things (IoT) conferences and exhibitions. We work with local and global businesses, as well as public sector bodies and associations who are looking to expand their reach in Asian markets. We provide the best &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Power Brings New Smart Home Service to Australian Consumers With</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/people-power-brings-new-smart-home-service-to-australian-consumers-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 06:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/people-power-brings-new-smart-home-service-to-australian-consumers-with/</guid>
      <description>Power Engineering Magazine PALO ALTO, CA&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - Nov 20, 2017) - Internet of Things (IoT) software company providing bot-enabled artificial intelligence (AI) for energy, security and care solutions, People Power announces today commercial availability of Home HQ from Origin Energy ( ASX : ORG ), a smart home service &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireless Interoperability Fuels the Industrial Internet of Things</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/wireless-interoperability-fuels-the-industrial-internet-of-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 06:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/wireless-interoperability-fuels-the-industrial-internet-of-things/</guid>
      <description>As we move toward industrial things being digital and connected, putting in place the right communications infrastructure is a critical piece of the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) equation. Connectivity is required to ensure that data is meaningful and actionable. Industrial things come from a variety of &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;The next decade belongs to India, do things differently&#39;</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/the-next-decade-belongs-to-india-do-things-differently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 05:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/the-next-decade-belongs-to-india-do-things-differently/</guid>
      <description>As for the changes which he envisioned, one is, IOT (Internet of Things) and automation will take over a large part of how we live, work, commute and &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Ways to Boost Your Campaigns With Blockchain</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/4-ways-to-boost-your-campaigns-with-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/4-ways-to-boost-your-campaigns-with-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard about it yet, you will. It&amp;rsquo;s the ingenious technology underlying the success of bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. Not only that, but it&amp;rsquo;s now poised to be a game changer for industries across the spectrum. Internet advertising stands to gain massively from blockchain &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 companies dead-set on &#39;shaking up&#39; the world of blockchain</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/5-companies-deadset-on-shaking-up-the-world-of-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/5-companies-deadset-on-shaking-up-the-world-of-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>The information that&amp;rsquo;s stored in these ledgers is saved in verifiable chunks, which are known as blocks. Blocks are chained together to form blockchains. This technology is completely revolutionary, but it&amp;rsquo;s yet to go mainstream. That being said, blockchain technology is already proving successful for a &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Echo and Google Home patched against BlueBorne threat</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/amazon-echo-and-google-home-patched-against-blueborne-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/amazon-echo-and-google-home-patched-against-blueborne-threat/</guid>
      <description>The Amazon Echo and Google Home are being marketed to the world as the smart speakers to put helpful, voice-assisted Internet of Things (IoT) AI into people&amp;rsquo;s homes. This week we had wearying confirmation that they also, less helpfully, distribute the same security failings into people&amp;rsquo;s homes as &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aussie Government Backs Blockchain For &#39;Smart&#39; Water And Power Grids</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/aussie-government-backs-blockchain-for-smart-water-and-power-grids/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/aussie-government-backs-blockchain-for-smart-water-and-power-grids/</guid>
      <description>The project&amp;rsquo;s goal is to use a blockchain-based platform to reduce the carbon footprints of cities. Data analytics will be leveraged in conjunction with distributed energy grids and water systems to provide a backbone for interconnected cities of the future; the potential result would be a veritable blueprint &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big banks&#39; blockchain specialists are flocking to cryptocurrency firms in</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/big-banks-blockchain-specialists-are-flocking-to-cryptocurrency-firms-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/big-banks-blockchain-specialists-are-flocking-to-cryptocurrency-firms-in/</guid>
      <description>Quartz Executives tasked with exploring blockchain tech for banks and consulting firms are finding it harder and harder to resist going full crypto. Case in point: three executives at BNY Mellon, Deutsche Bank, and PWC well known for leading blockchain work at their firms have left to pursue their own &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin and Blockchain Aren&#39;t Investible Yet, Canada Pension Says</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/bitcoin-and-blockchain-arent-investible-yet-canada-pension-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/bitcoin-and-blockchain-arent-investible-yet-canada-pension-says/</guid>
      <description>He said his views were more aligned with Lloyd Blankfein, CEO of Goldman Sachs Group Inc., than with Jamie Dimon, CEO of JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. when it comes to bitcoin and blockchain. Dimon has famously called bitcoin a fraud while Blankfein said he is not ready to dismiss the digital currency &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Could Be the Future of the Apparel Supply Chain</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-could-be-the-future-of-the-apparel-supply-chain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-could-be-the-future-of-the-apparel-supply-chain/</guid>
      <description>If you try to stay up to date on technological or economic trends, chances are you&amp;rsquo;ve either read about or at least seen references to blockchain. Though vague and catchy, the term is no mere buzzword. While plenty of hype and speculation still surround blockchain, all that I&amp;rsquo;ve read about it so far points &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Investment Services: What Small Business Owners Should Know</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-investment-services-what-small-business-owners-should-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-investment-services-what-small-business-owners-should-know/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago, companies began creating blockchain walletsthink of a digital bank account where crypto assets are storedthat automatically converted cryptocurrencies into fiat currencies. This cut out the manual labor side of crypto coin transactions. Users no longer had to convert the currencies &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Startup EthereCash Announce Peerless Crypto-Platform Set to Take</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-startup-etherecash-announce-peerless-cryptoplatform-set-to-take/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-startup-etherecash-announce-peerless-cryptoplatform-set-to-take/</guid>
      <description>The Merkle Etherecash, a Blockchain technology start-up, have developed a platform for sending, spending and lending money through mutual terms, secured by a Ethereum smart contract and backed by the platform users&amp;rsquo; crypto assets.With their crypto debit card, Etherecash offers a world-first in a card that can &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Support Phone Number-1(844)</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-support-phone-number1844/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-support-phone-number1844/</guid>
      <description>number Blockchain support number Blockchain support number Blockchain support number Blockchain support number Blockchain support number Blockchain support number Blockchain support number more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain gets a Wall Street win: `we know the thing works now&#39;</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-gets-a-wall-street-win-we-know-the-thing-works-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-gets-a-wall-street-win-we-know-the-thing-works-now/</guid>
      <description>The prospect of blockchain technology remaking financial services just moved a step closer to reality after banks including Goldman Sachs Group Inc. and JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. completed a successful six-month test in the $2.8 trillion equity swaps market. The program, managed by blockchain startup &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain likely to replace bankers and lawyers</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-likely-to-replace-bankers-and-lawyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-likely-to-replace-bankers-and-lawyers/</guid>
      <description>A report by ICAEW, titled Blockchain and the Future of Accountancy, argued that smart contacts using blockchain could disrupt financial systems and threaten central authorities like banks, clearing-houses and lawyers. However, it added that this could save firms the cost and effort of doing business with &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain project to link Aussie water and power</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-project-to-link-aussie-water-and-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-project-to-link-aussie-water-and-power/</guid>
      <description>A blockchain project in Australia is to receive more than $8 million (4.6m) of funding to integrate a range of energy and water systems. The City of Freemantle will receive $2.6 million (1.5m) from the government and $5.7 million (3.3m) through project partners. It will trial how cities can use blockchain &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain&#39;s Vertical Takeoff As Flying Cars Become Reality</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchains-vertical-takeoff-as-flying-cars-become-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchains-vertical-takeoff-as-flying-cars-become-reality/</guid>
      <description>You remember the pictures of techy, geeky, out-of-this worldly future in any sci-fi movie like &amp;lsquo;The Fifth Element&amp;rsquo; to date: tall buildings, strange clothes, and, of course, flying cars running invisible highways stacking up all the way to the endless sky. And I am most sure you&amp;rsquo;d say: That&amp;rsquo;s too far ahead to &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build IoT apps the easy way</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/build-iot-apps-the-easy-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/build-iot-apps-the-easy-way/</guid>
      <description>Many organisations can benefit from rolling out internet of things (IoT) applications. Manufacturers managing customer equipment, from fitness-trackers to aeroplanes; transport and utility companies monitoring for performance metrics and faults; healthcare companies checking on patient wellbeing via &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CWRU, CSU partner to evaluate how West Side manufacturers could use</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/cwru-csu-partner-to-evaluate-how-west-side-manufacturers-could-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/cwru-csu-partner-to-evaluate-how-west-side-manufacturers-could-use/</guid>
      <description>CWRU, CSU working to tackle technology in manufacturing. Crain&amp;rsquo;s Business Cleveland: Case Western Reserve University and Cleveland State University partnered on a Smart &amp;amp; Connected Communities grant to evaluate how small and mid-sized manufacturers on Cleveland&amp;rsquo;s West Side could use &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control and Rewards: The Two Fundamental Benefits of the Blockchain</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/control-and-rewards-the-two-fundamental-benefits-of-the-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/control-and-rewards-the-two-fundamental-benefits-of-the-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>One of the fundamental benefits of Blockchain technology is the provision of alternatives in the ways that users can retain control over their assets and revenue generation across within their fields of endeavor. All over the technological ecosystem, anywhere Blockchain is implemented, whether explored &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossing borders: Blockchain&#39;s role in smoothing trade</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/crossing-borders-blockchains-role-in-smoothing-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/crossing-borders-blockchains-role-in-smoothing-trade/</guid>
      <description>IBM and Maersk are working together to create a new blockchain related solution to this situation built over the Hyperledger Fabric platform. The solution, they believe, could vastly reduce the complications involved and also expedite the transit process. This approach tries enveloping the complete &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity: The Focal Point of 2018</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/cybersecurity-the-focal-point-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/cybersecurity-the-focal-point-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>As the world grows increasingly connected, moving towards both the Internet of Things and the 4 Industrial Revolution, greater cybersecurity is needed. In recent years, cyber attacks against companies have been increasing in sophistication, with their damage ranging from brand damage to irreparably &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining and securing the Internet of Things: ENISA publishes a study on</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/defining-and-securing-the-internet-of-things-enisa-publishes-a-study-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/defining-and-securing-the-internet-of-things-enisa-publishes-a-study-on/</guid>
      <description>The study which is titled &amp;lsquo;Baseline Security Recommendations for Internet of Things in the context of critical information infrastructures&amp;rsquo;, aims to set the scene for IoT security in Europe. It serves as a reference point in this field and as a foundation for relevant forthcoming initiatives and developments. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIME Expands Global Presence with Office Opening in Dubai</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/fime-expands-global-presence-with-office-opening-in-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/fime-expands-global-presence-with-office-opening-in-dubai/</guid>
      <description>It supports a range of technologies including contact, contactless, EMV chip, near field communication (NFC), host card emulation (HCE), tokenization, secure element (SE), machine to machine (M2M), internet of things (IoT) and trusted execution environment (TEE). Partnering with the international and &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Ways Blockchain Can Impact The Real Estate Market For The Better</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/five-ways-blockchain-can-impact-the-real-estate-market-for-the-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/five-ways-blockchain-can-impact-the-real-estate-market-for-the-better/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain is one such technology that could make an impact in the real estate market by offering real-time data that can help secure financial transactions. According to TechCrunch, the advantages of using blockchain in the real estate market have been mostly ignored, even though the technology has &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forget Sierra Wireless, Skyworks Solutions is the Better Internet of Things</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/forget-sierra-wireless-skyworks-solutions-is-the-better-internet-of-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/forget-sierra-wireless-skyworks-solutions-is-the-better-internet-of-things/</guid>
      <description>Madison.com Forget Sierra Wireless, Skyworks Solutions is the Better Internet of Things Stock. newsfeedback@fool.com (Leo Sun); 31 min &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things (IoT), which connects various devices to each other and the cloud, is widely expected to be the &amp;ldquo;next big trend&amp;rdquo; in technology. Research firm IDC expects &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Industries Ripe for Blockchain Disruption</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/four-industries-ripe-for-blockchain-disruption/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/four-industries-ripe-for-blockchain-disruption/</guid>
      <description>businesses operate. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future picture: Why India will need Internet of Things to bring in major</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/future-picture-why-india-will-need-internet-of-things-to-bring-in-major/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/future-picture-why-india-will-need-internet-of-things-to-bring-in-major/</guid>
      <description>ETTelecom.com Future picture: Why India will need Internet of Things to bring in major transformation NEW DELHI: Internet of Things (IoT) may further take up years to proliferate in India and globally, however there are cases where it is being currently used by consumers and industries extensively. While IoT will touch &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghana: Can Ghana Attain Blockchain Economy Status?</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/ghana-can-ghana-attain-blockchain-economy-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/ghana-can-ghana-attain-blockchain-economy-status/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain thus has the potential for profound impact, bringing wholesale change to organizations and local and national economies. Technology industry experts have recently opined that blockchain technology will do for transactions what the internet did for information &amp;ndash; and in the relatively near &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hartford, state aim to build bridges with Israel&#39;s tech economy</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/hartford-state-aim-to-build-bridges-with-israels-tech-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/hartford-state-aim-to-build-bridges-with-israels-tech-economy/</guid>
      <description>AmNet Pro Company is developing electronic hardware for Internet-of-Things and machine-to-machine applications. Matt Pilon. Nearly two dozen Israeli startup executives and government officials, fresh off visits to New York and Philadelphia, made one last stop on their East Coast road show this &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How blockchain encryption works: It&#39;s all about math</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/how-blockchain-encryption-works-its-all-about-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/how-blockchain-encryption-works-its-all-about-math/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain encryption prevents sensitive information from getting into the wrong hands, and being misused or forged. Riot Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s CEO John O&amp;rsquo;Rourke explains how this encryption works. The blockchain ledger records every transaction that has ever taken place on that blockchain. That transaction &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Internet of Things will reshape future production systems</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/how-the-internet-of-things-will-reshape-future-production-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/how-the-internet-of-things-will-reshape-future-production-systems/</guid>
      <description>20, 2017 | Insights. For decades, many of the world&amp;rsquo;s best companies have used their production systems as a source of sustainable competitive advantage. But such a system isn&amp;rsquo;t just about doing things well, with fast, efficient &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation in Mining and the Internet of Things (IoT)</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/innovation-in-mining-and-the-internet-of-things-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/innovation-in-mining-and-the-internet-of-things-iot/</guid>
      <description>embracing innovation to advance operations and refine customer solutions. The Internet of Things (IoT) is an emerging technology that offers positive change in the mining industry and will change the way miners operate over the &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inseego Corp. (INSG) Receiving Somewhat Favorable Media Coverage, Analysis</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/inseego-corp-insg-receiving-somewhat-favorable-media-coverage-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/inseego-corp-insg-receiving-somewhat-favorable-media-coverage-analysis/</guid>
      <description>StockNewsTimes Inseego Corp. logo News articles about Inseego Corp. (NASDAQ:INSG) have trended somewhat positive recently, according to Accern. The research group rates the sentiment of news coverage by monitoring more than 20 million blog and news sources. Accern ranks coverage of publicly-traded &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside SAP&#39;s blockchain as a service strategy  an SAP TechEd analysis</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/inside-saps-blockchain-as-a-service-strategy--an-sap-teched-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/inside-saps-blockchain-as-a-service-strategy--an-sap-teched-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Several candid meetings at SAP TechEd Barcelona brought clarity to SAP&amp;rsquo;s blockchain direction. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I learned from SAPs Torsten Zube and &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intergrating Internet of Things based on semantic description for</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/intergrating-internet-of-things-based-on-semantic-description-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/intergrating-internet-of-things-based-on-semantic-description-for/</guid>
      <description>Intergrating Internet of Things based on semantic description for Business-to Business supply chain monitoring and tracking &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT needs to be secured by the network</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/iot-needs-to-be-secured-by-the-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/iot-needs-to-be-secured-by-the-network/</guid>
      <description>Everyone who has a stake in the internet of things, from device manufacturers to network service providers to implementers to customers themselves, makes important contributions to the security or lack thereof in enterprise IoT, attendees at Security of Things World were told. The key to all [IoT devices] &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Blockchain Technology Really the New Internet?</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/is-blockchain-technology-really-the-new-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/is-blockchain-technology-really-the-new-internet/</guid>
      <description>IoT (Internet of Things) technology, of course, has been managing electronic devices on the Internet and through smart contracts. In the same way, the next phase of innovation in manufacturing (XLI) or any other industry could be driven by tech based on blockchain technology. The way even stock &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Las Vegas a Smart City</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/making-las-vegas-a-smart-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/making-las-vegas-a-smart-city/</guid>
      <description>This week on The Internet of Things Podcast, host Stacey Higginbotham speaks with Michael Sherwood, Director of Technology and Innovation City of Las Vegas, about plans for a traffic light that detects pollution and can send cars along before it builds up, and what it really means to build a smart city. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ModusLink Recognized in Gartner&#39;s Competitive Landscape</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/moduslink-recognized-in-gartners-competitive-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/moduslink-recognized-in-gartners-competitive-landscape/</guid>
      <description>more than 30 billion connected devices, which will result in a 20 percent increase in potential revenue generated from manufacturers running software on smart things in IoT. To stay competitive and maximize on the opportunity for &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NB-IoT and LTE CAT-M1 field measurements and SLA verification</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/nbiot-and-lte-catm1-field-measurements-and-sla-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/nbiot-and-lte-catm1-field-measurements-and-sla-verification/</guid>
      <description>Internet of Things (IoT) is today&amp;rsquo;s megatrend in wireless communication industry. Machine to machine wireless connectivity is being adopted in various verticals at increasing pace. Number of IoT devices deployed by 2020 is expected to increase to ~20 Billion. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narrowband Internet-of-Things (IoT) Chipset Market Growth and Analysis-</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/narrowband-internetofthings-iot-chipset-market-growth-and-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/narrowband-internetofthings-iot-chipset-market-growth-and-analysis/</guid>
      <description>MilTech Narrowband Internet-of-Things (IoT) Chipset Market analysis is provided for global market including development trends by regions, competitive analysis of the Narrowband Internet-of-Things (IoT) Chipset market. Narrowband Internet-of-Things (IoT) Chipset Industry report focuses on the major drivers &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Entries and Money Flow into Bitcoin/ Blockchain Market Creating New</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/new-entries-and-money-flow-into-bitcoin-blockchain-market-creating-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/new-entries-and-money-flow-into-bitcoin-blockchain-market-creating-new/</guid>
      <description>Markets Insider Big money is flowing into the sector with HIVE Blockchain announcing closing &amp;ldquo;$34.5 Million Bought Deal Financing and Expands Production of Newly &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packaging and Processing OEMs Continue on Digital Path</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/packaging-and-processing-oems-continue-on-digital-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/packaging-and-processing-oems-continue-on-digital-path/</guid>
      <description>Advancements in Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) technologies will provide machine-to-machine (M2M) connection as well as machine-to-people. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Rolls-Royce, TCS seeks more IoT deals to scale now</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/post-rollsroyce-tcs-seeks-more-iot-deals-to-scale-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/post-rollsroyce-tcs-seeks-more-iot-deals-to-scale-now/</guid>
      <description>BENGALURU: Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) is working on several larger Internet-of-Things-based deals after securing Rolls-Royce as a marquee IoT client. Many of these deals are in the exploratory phase as the technology begins to gain traction, the head of the IoT business told ET. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposal  IBM blockchain to manage marijuana supply chain in British</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/proposal--ibm-blockchain-to-manage-marijuana-supply-chain-in-british/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/proposal--ibm-blockchain-to-manage-marijuana-supply-chain-in-british/</guid>
      <description>Diginomica Blockchain is rapidly becoming a world leading technology enabling the assured exchange of value in both digital and tangible assets, while protecting privacy and eliminating fraud. Blockchain offers a shared ledger that is updated and validated in real time with each network participant. It enables &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recognized in Gartner&#39;s Competitive Landscape: License and Entitlement</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/recognized-in-gartners-competitive-landscape-license-and-entitlement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/recognized-in-gartners-competitive-landscape-license-and-entitlement/</guid>
      <description>Business Wire (press release) Gartner predicts that, by 2020, the Internet of Things (IoT) will connect more than 30 billion connected devices, which will result in a 20 percent increase in potential revenue generated from manufacturers running software on smart &amp;ldquo;things&amp;rdquo; in IoT. To stay competitive and maximize on the opportunity for &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBI to use blockchain for smart contracts by next month</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/sbi-to-use-blockchain-for-smart-contracts-by-next-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/sbi-to-use-blockchain-for-smart-contracts-by-next-month/</guid>
      <description>Country&amp;rsquo;s largest lender State Bank of India (SBI) is set to launch beta versions of blockchain-enabled smart contracts by next month. It will be followed by blockchain-enabled Know Your Customer (KYC), according to an ET report. Smart contracts are ones which deploys blockchain technology, &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego-Based LiFi Innovator Firefly Wireless Networks Receives Visit</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/san-diegobased-lifi-innovator-firefly-wireless-networks-receives-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/san-diegobased-lifi-innovator-firefly-wireless-networks-receives-visit/</guid>
      <description>Business Wire (press release) San Diego-Based LiFi Innovator Firefly Wireless Networks Receives Visit from the Mayor of Dresden, Germany to Discuss Internet of Things (IoT) and LiFi Development. Mayor Dirk Hilbert and the Office of Economic Development discussed continued synergy on technology development, leveraging &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senegal Subscribes to the IMF&#39;s Special Data Dissemination Standard</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/senegal-subscribes-to-the-imfs-special-data-dissemination-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/senegal-subscribes-to-the-imfs-special-data-dissemination-standard/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip; and by funding from the African Development Bank to build and maintain the open data platform that allows machine-to-machine data transmission. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopin Places First in Blockchain Startup Competition - 2017 CoinAgenda</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/shopin-places-first-in-blockchain-startup-competition--2017-coinagenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/shopin-places-first-in-blockchain-startup-competition--2017-coinagenda/</guid>
      <description>Markets Insider NEW YORK, Nov. 20, 2017 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Out of more than 40 competitors, Shopin was named the winner in the 2017 CoinAgenda Global blockchain startup competition by a panel of investors. Shopin is a blockchain technology startup that is uniting the open ecommerce web and retail into a &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Dubai Office Bags Award for Blockchain Initiative</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/smart-dubai-office-bags-award-for-blockchain-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/smart-dubai-office-bags-award-for-blockchain-initiative/</guid>
      <description>The Smart Dubai Office (SDO) has won an award for its Dubai Blockchain Strategy initiative. Announced during the Smart Cities Expo and World Congress that took place in Barcelona last week, the City Project Award recognizes the most &amp;ldquo;innovative and successful&amp;rdquo; projects being implemented in an &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Dubai Office Scoops Major Award for Blockchain City Initiative</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/smart-dubai-office-scoops-major-award-for-blockchain-city-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/smart-dubai-office-scoops-major-award-for-blockchain-city-initiative/</guid>
      <description>The Smart Dubai Office has bagged an award for its Dubai Blockchain Strategy at the Smart Cities Expo and World Congress in Barcelona, beating competition from 308 other projects from 58 countries. Launched in 2016, the Dubai Blockchain Strategy sees the Dubai government aim among many &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Somewhat Favorable Press Coverage Somewhat Unlikely to Impact CalAmp Corp.</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/somewhat-favorable-press-coverage-somewhat-unlikely-to-impact-calamp-corp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/somewhat-favorable-press-coverage-somewhat-unlikely-to-impact-calamp-corp/</guid>
      <description>Dispatch Tribunal The Company&amp;rsquo;s Wireless DataCom segment offers solutions for mobile resource management (MRM) applications, the machine-to-machine (M2M) communications space and other markets that require connectivity anytime and anywhere. Insider Buying and Selling by Quarter for CalAmp Corp. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State Bank of India to Beta Test Blockchain Smart Contracts Next Month</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/state-bank-of-india-to-beta-test-blockchain-smart-contracts-next-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/state-bank-of-india-to-beta-test-blockchain-smart-contracts-next-month/</guid>
      <description>The State Bank of India (SBI) is planning a beta launch of smart contracts by next month, with blockchain-based know-your-customer (KYC) processes soon after. According to Sudin Baraokar, head of innovation at SBI, the systems have been developed by Bankchain a consortium of 27 banks that was &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blockchain Might Scare the Gig Economy to Death</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/the-blockchain-might-scare-the-gig-economy-to-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/the-blockchain-might-scare-the-gig-economy-to-death/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Skedaddle, an &amp;lsquo;Uber-for-buses&amp;rsquo; startup, is launching a blockchain project that aims to completely eliminate tipping,&amp;rdquo; is the first sentence here, and then somehow &amp;ldquo;Users can rate any interaction with a service worker, which also functions as a tip, and follows a worker from job to job,&amp;rdquo; is the second, and by &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brokerages Set CalAmp Corp. (CAMP) Target Price at $19.00</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/the-brokerages-set-calamp-corp-camp-target-price-at-1900/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/the-brokerages-set-calamp-corp-camp-target-price-at-1900/</guid>
      <description>A number of analysts have recently issued reports on the company. Zacks Investment Research cut CalAmp Corp. from a hold rating to a sell rating in a research report on Thursday, April 20th. Benchmark Co. initiated coverage on CalAmp Corp. in a research note on Tuesday, April 25th. They issued &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Machine Identity Crisis:The Security of Machine-to-machine</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/the-machine-identity-crisisthe-security-of-machinetomachine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/the-machine-identity-crisisthe-security-of-machinetomachine/</guid>
      <description>BankInfoSecurity.com Our increased dependence on machines is so profound that even the definition of machine is undergoing radical change. The number and type of physical devices on enterprise networks has been rising rapidly, but this is outstripped by the number of applications and services they host. At the same &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The average AI job commands six figureshere are the top 15 companies</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/the-average-ai-job-commands-six-figureshere-are-the-top-15-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/the-average-ai-job-commands-six-figureshere-are-the-top-15-companies/</guid>
      <description>CNBC From Mark Cuban to Bill Gates, top thought leaders have confirmed that the future of work revolves around artificial intelligence. Tech hubs, both in and out of Silicon Valley, are now in a race to perfect AI and these companies are seeking top talent to do so. As competition stiffens among HR teams, &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The rise of IoT-based Hivenets</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/the-rise-of-iotbased-hivenets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/the-rise-of-iotbased-hivenets/</guid>
      <description>It is the Internet of Things, but with an enterprise angle. Take that to mean industry vertical applications, development ecosystems, product design, hardware, deployment and more. Latest Blog Posts. Smart building security: Cyber-resilience must be built in Investing in the internet of things IoT&amp;rsquo;s biggest &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel seeks ways to adopt blockchain</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/travel-seeks-ways-to-adopt-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/travel-seeks-ways-to-adopt-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>from one point to another in a highly secure manner. As Norm Rose, senior technology and corporate market analyst at Phocuswright wrote in a recent paper for Phocuswright titled &amp;ldquo;How and Why Blockchain Can Transform the &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPS Steers Into Blockchain Trucking Alliance</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/ups-steers-into-blockchain-trucking-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/ups-steers-into-blockchain-trucking-alliance/</guid>
      <description>Since the concept of blockchain technology was first released in 2009 as the technology fabric supporting Bitcoin, numerous applications have been &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wave kicks off live blockchain pilots for paperless trade solution</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/wave-kicks-off-live-blockchain-pilots-for-paperless-trade-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/wave-kicks-off-live-blockchain-pilots-for-paperless-trade-solution/</guid>
      <description>Wave, the fintech startup that last year completed the world&amp;rsquo;s first live blockchain trade transaction with Barclays, has now taken the next step towards releasing a commercial blockchain-powered product for paperless trade. Together with Israeli shipping company ZIM and Hong Kong-based logistics firm &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will 3D Graphics and Head-Up Displays Be In Your Next Vehicle?</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/will-3d-graphics-and-headup-displays-be-in-your-next-vehicle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/will-3d-graphics-and-headup-displays-be-in-your-next-vehicle/</guid>
      <description>Cypress Semiconductor reported record sales during its third quarter 2017 report, driven by strong growth in its connected Internet of Things and MCU business. Automotive has become an important part of that picture, with 30% of revenues during the last quarter coming from that industry alone. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wipro, Cisco ally for smart lighting</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/wipro-cisco-ally-for-smart-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/wipro-cisco-ally-for-smart-lighting/</guid>
      <description>With the emergence of the IoT (Internet of Things) and big data, smart and connected digital lighting is the way forward, said Anuj Dhir, vice president and business head, Wipro Lighting, in a statement. Wipro said lighting makes up approximately 40% of a building&amp;rsquo;s electricity bill. This, it said, coupled &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xinhuanet marks 20th anniversary in Beijing</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/xinhuanet-marks-20th-anniversary-in-beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/xinhuanet-marks-20th-anniversary-in-beijing/</guid>
      <description>China Mobile will cooperate with Xinhuanet in fields such as 5G content and application, new media technology and Internet of things, he noted. Through 20 years of development, Xinhuanet has evolved into a comprehensive news portal, releasing around 20,000 pieces of all-media news and &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zebra Technologies Participates in Senate Hearing on Advancement of</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/zebra-technologies-participates-in-senate-hearing-on-advancement-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/zebra-technologies-participates-in-senate-hearing-on-advancement-of/</guid>
      <description>Business Wire (press release) 7 Senate hearing on advancing the Internet of Things (IoT) in rural communities before the Communications, Technology, Innovation and Internet Subcommittee. Mike Terzich, Chief Administrative Officer of Zebra Technologies, discussed how Zebra is a global leader in bringing enterprise IoT solutions &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zipit Recognized with Strategic Product Award at AT&amp;T Partner Exchange</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/zipit-recognized-with-strategic-product-award-at-att-partner-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/zipit-recognized-with-strategic-product-award-at-att-partner-exchange/</guid>
      <description>Markets Insider Zipit was presented with a Strategic Product Award for its work in developing IoT solutions, and was noted as being the top performing IoT solution provider in the AT&amp;amp;T Partner Exchange channel. During their keynote presentation, executives from AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things division also highlighted Zipit&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ePlus inc. (PLUS) versus USA Technologies (USAT) Head-To-Head Review</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/eplus-inc-plus-versus-usa-technologies-usat-headtohead-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/eplus-inc-plus-versus-usa-technologies-usat-headtohead-review/</guid>
      <description>It has designed and marketed systems and solutions that facilitate electronic payment options, as well as telemetry and machine-to-machine (M2M) &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AIA Hong Kong announces blockchain solution for bancassurance operations</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/aia-hong-kong-announces-blockchain-solution-for-bancassurance-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/aia-hong-kong-announces-blockchain-solution-for-bancassurance-operations/</guid>
      <description>AIA Hong Kong, a subsidiary of Asian insurance giant AIA, has announced a blockchain solution that will improve the efficiency of its bancassurance &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APAC Tops the Global Home Broadband Wi-Fi Devices Market - Technavio</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/apac-tops-the-global-home-broadband-wifi-devices-market--technavio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/apac-tops-the-global-home-broadband-wifi-devices-market--technavio/</guid>
      <description>According to Jujhar Singh, a lead analyst at Technavio for research on machine to machine (M2M) and connected devices, &amp;ldquo;The licensing of 4G and the ongoing launch of 4G services across Asia have provided the fundamental platform for growth in wireless broadband services. 4G has also offered &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlockEx, OpenText Partner on Blockchain-Based Supply Chain Finance Solution</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockex-opentext-partner-on-blockchainbased-supply-chain-finance-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockex-opentext-partner-on-blockchainbased-supply-chain-finance-solution/</guid>
      <description>Digital asset platform BlockEx has teamed with business network OpenText to explore how blockchain can make supply chain finance more efficient. more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Tech May Allow Developing World to Leapfrog Developed World:</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-tech-may-allow-developing-world-to-leapfrog-developed-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-tech-may-allow-developing-world-to-leapfrog-developed-world/</guid>
      <description>Cointelegraph (Bitcoin, Cryptocurrency and Blockchain News) Brock Pierce is a US entrepreneur, investor and a public speaker, co-founder of Blockchain Capital, chairman of Bitcoin Foundation. He&amp;rsquo;s also a &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain: a natural partner for 21st century power grids</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-a-natural-partner-for-21st-century-power-grids/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/blockchain-a-natural-partner-for-21st-century-power-grids/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain: a natural partner for 21st century power grids &amp;hellip; Take blockchain, for example, a distributed database system that is swiftly becoming a &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Central New Mexico Community College to Offer Digital Diplomas Using</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/central-new-mexico-community-college-to-offer-digital-diplomas-using/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/central-new-mexico-community-college-to-offer-digital-diplomas-using/</guid>
      <description>BlockTribune Central New Mexico Community College (CNM) will start issuing digital diplomas using blockchain technology. 21 students graduating on December 15 from CNM Ingenuity&amp;rsquo;s Deep Dive Coding bootcamps will receive the first digital credentials. CNM, formerly Albuquerque Technical Vocational Institute, &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India&#39;s Largest Bank Confirms Blockchain Rollout in December</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/indias-largest-bank-confirms-blockchain-rollout-in-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/indias-largest-bank-confirms-blockchain-rollout-in-december/</guid>
      <description>The State Bank of India will launch two blockchain production-ready beta solutions next month, ready for use to 27 major Indian banks of the &amp;lsquo;BankChain&amp;rsquo; consortium. Government-owned State Bank of India (SBI) is India&amp;rsquo;s largest banking corporation with assets over $460 billion amid a foothold in just &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infographic: How is Technology Enhancing Supply Chain Management?</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/infographic-how-is-technology-enhancing-supply-chain-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/infographic-how-is-technology-enhancing-supply-chain-management/</guid>
      <description>The Internet of Things (IoT) is all about connecting devices over the internet, allowing for the interlinking of data and communication between us, our devices and applications. In Britain, it is most commonly found in home heating and energy use, where the temperature of your house can be controlled &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number of DDoS Attacks Have Doubled in Six Months As Criminals Leverage</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/number-of-ddos-attacks-have-doubled-in-six-months-as-criminals-leverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/number-of-ddos-attacks-have-doubled-in-six-months-as-criminals-leverage/</guid>
      <description>Business Wire (press release) Corero attributes this increase in frequency to the growing availability of DDoS-for-hire services, and the proliferation of unsecured Internet of Things (IoT) devices. For example, the &amp;lsquo;Reaper&amp;rsquo; botnet is known to have already infected thousands of devices, and is believed to be particularly dangerous due &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Network Automation for Blockchain Developers</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/social-network-automation-for-blockchain-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/social-network-automation-for-blockchain-developers/</guid>
      <description>A platform that allows any blockchain enterprise to communicate, get information, analyze and monitor social networks launches its ICO beginning of December. Using Social Ether, entrepreneurs will be able to achieve real social media reach, without losing blockchain benefits. Sether will enable &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Health-tech Korea] MediBloc eyes blockchain for patient-centered medical</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/post/healthtech-korea-medibloc-eyes-blockchain-for-patientcentered-medical/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 04:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/post/healthtech-korea-medibloc-eyes-blockchain-for-patientcentered-medical/</guid>
      <description>The Korea Herald The Korea Herald is publishing a series of articles highlighting South Korea&amp;rsquo;s promising startups in the emerging sectors of digital health care and &amp;hellip; more.
@surgethings</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>