<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dailies on CloudFeed</title>
    <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dailies on CloudFeed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>CloudFeed. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//cloudfeed.net/daily/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.kdnuggets.com/2016/12/navigating-world-big-data-analytics.html&#39;&gt;Navigating the World of Big Data Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leveraging our Agile Analytics Lab, we created reusable data processing pipelines, loaded the data into Hadoop and readied it for analysis. Once the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.jewishjournal.com/articles/item/bgu_paypal_form_partnership_in_cybersecurity_research&#39;&gt;BGU, PayPal form partnership in cybersecurity research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PayPal&amp;rsquo;s involvement in big data and machine learning technology has been supported by its significant research and development (R&amp;amp;D) activity in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/big-data/amazon-redshift-engineerings-advanced-table-design-playbook-table-data-durability/&#39;&gt;Amazon Redshift Engineering&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Table Design Playbook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playbook: Table Data Durability. by Zach Christopherson | on 08 DEC &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.tradearabia.com/news/REAL_317822.html&#39;&gt;Leveraging big data analytics in retail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Information is all around us, and every business - from finance to healthcare and telecom to real estate - relies on the use of big data and analytics for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.arnnet.com.au/article/611327/big-data-now-all-about-two-speed-information-architecture/?fp=2&amp;fpid=1&#39;&gt;Big data is now all about two-speed information architecture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data and analytics capabilities have made a leap forward in recent years, according to TIBCO Asia head of pre-sales, San Zaw. For Zaw, with the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://emploi.epfl.ch/page-139964-en.html&#39;&gt;PhD position: Big data, renewable energy and built environment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;environment; Development, adaptation, and programming of Big data mining &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/16/12/p8788120/nvtc-to-host-2017-capital-data-summit&#39;&gt;NVTC to Host 2017 Capital Data Summit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Panel sessions will be led by principals from world leading big data and analytics companies, financial institutions, healthcare organizations, top &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.greenbiz.com/article/insurance-companies-arent-covering-climate-risk-big-data-blame&#39;&gt;Insurance companies aren&amp;rsquo;t covering climate risk  is Big Data to blame?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data  also known as predictive analytics  is helping insurers become increasingly accurate in their ability to pinpoint the exact level of risks &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itproportal.com/features/how-uk-banks-can-prevent-fraud-using-data-science/&#39;&gt;How UK banks can prevent fraud using data science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data science is the collaborative discipline - the combination of people, data, tools, and processes - used to transform big data into actionable insights &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mdpi.com/2071-1050/8/12/1293&#39;&gt;Urban Big Data and Sustainable Development Goals: Challenges and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can be achieved by situating the application of big data innovations &amp;hellip; advancing the culture and common skill sets for applying urban big data, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.readme.lk/iit-big-data-forum/&#39;&gt;IIT Big Data Analytics Tech Forum 2016: The Essentials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data, a hot topic that has been generating a lot of interest in the global IT industry. From retail and banking to providing analysis for election &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bsminfo.com/doc/data-backup-recovery-how-big-data-has-changed-things-what-decision-makers-need-to-do-about-it-0001&#39;&gt;Data Backup &amp;amp; Recovery: How Big Data Has Changed Things &amp;amp; What&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Solutions Magazine Today, companies in all sectors have a massive demand for data. To succeed, they must be able to take in a large amount of data and process it in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.kdnuggets.com/2016/12/big-data-ecosystem-science.html&#39;&gt;The big data ecosystem for science: Physics, LHC, and Cosmology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find out how big data, machine learning, and analytics are changing not only business, but society itself at Strata + Hadoop World. Save 20% on most &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scoop.co.nz/stories/GE1612/S00057/big-data-holds-key-to-life-saving-discoveries.htm&#39;&gt;Big Data Holds Key to Life Saving Discoveries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A whitepaper released today by bioinformatics technology company Biomatters examines the critical role big data will play in enabling scientists to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thelawyer.com/kinstellar-hosts-big-data-practice-seminar-budapest/&#39;&gt;Kinstellar hosts Big Data in Practice seminar in Budapest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speakers included: Istvn Tth, mathematician and data safety expert, who delved a little deeper into what Big Data means; Zsombor Orbn, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizjournals.com/bizjournals/how-to/technology/2016/12/major-league-baseball-slides-from-moneyball-to.html&#39;&gt;Major League baseball slides from Moneyball to Techball&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data is now on the cusp of an even bigger transformation of our &amp;hellip; some teams were taking advantage of less all-inclusive big data systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3148652/analytics/how-to-get-big-data-expertise-on-a-budget.html&#39;&gt;How to get big data expertise on a budget&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes staffing a big data professional can be out of reach, but these &amp;hellip; You can enroll your employees in online Tableau Training and Hadoop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.naij.com/1076973-trump-clinton-how-big-data-scientists-helped-trump-win-election.html&#39;&gt;Trump vs. Clinton: How Big Data and scientists helped Trump win the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NAIJ.COM The term Big Data means that all actions we perform on either the Web or offline leave a digital trail. Purchasing by credit card, Google search results &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3169537&#39;&gt;Emerging Global Big Data Market Trends, Technology Advancement, to Drive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital Journal The market size and forecast in terms of value for the global big data market has been provided for the period 2014 to 2019, considering 2013 as the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://ctovision.com/tapping-centralized-talent-pools-data-analytics-cybersecurity-mission-enabling-functions-government-agencies/&#39;&gt;Tapping into centralized talent pools for data analytics, cybersecurity and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CTOvision (blog) The highlight of the 2013 Government Big Data Forum was not just the focus on Hadoop-centric platforms like Cloudera, but the exchange of lessons &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blogs.voanews.com/techtonics/2016/12/09/for-developing-world-2016-brought-education-drones-big-data/&#39;&gt;For Developing World, 2016 Brought Education, Drones, Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using data collection and big data  complex analytical and behavioral databases that allow researchers to extract social and economic trends  the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.toptechnews.com/article/index.php?story_id=021000NNHR9R&#39;&gt;Understanding Your Customer Using Data Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They say that data is the new oil, and if your business has a web presence then chances are you&amp;rsquo;re sitting on vast reserves of potential customer &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dbta.com/Editorial/News-Flashes/BlueData-Announces-General-Availability-of-BlueData-EPIC-on-AWS-115276.aspx&#39;&gt;BlueData Announces General Availability of BlueData EPIC on AWS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The platform also provides the same Docker-based application images for Hadoop, Spark, and other Big Data tools are portable across on-premises &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.apics.org/sites/apics-blog/think-supply-chain-landing-page/thinking-supply-chain/2016/12/09/using-big-data-for-improved-roi&#39;&gt;Using Big Data for Improved ROI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data that supply chain professionals should be working more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://martechtoday.com/forget-big-data-thinking-small-can-help-marketers-see-future-193182&#39;&gt;Forget big data: Why thinking small can help marketers see the future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jones explains how a combination of small data analytics, predictive analytics &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.xconomy.com/texas/2016/12/09/technium-crunches-big-data-to-match-entrepreneurs-with-researchers/&#39;&gt;Technium Crunches Big Data to Match Entrepreneurs with Researchers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DallasUniversities and other institutions are chock-full of intellectual property, but it can be difficult for entrepreneurs, interested in turning those &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidebigdata.com/2016/12/09/big-data-no-longer-a-big-problem/&#39;&gt;Big Data No Longer a Big Problem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;equus_logo Today&amp;rsquo;s enterprise-level organizations produce ever-increasing volumes of data each day. As employees create new documents, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2016/12/08/no-big-data-didn-t-win-the-u-s-election&#39;&gt;No, Big Data Didn&amp;rsquo;t Win the U.S. Election&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Bloomberg View) &amp;ndash; One of the most enjoyable parts of the fallout from a big political upset is the victory dance of those who claim they brought it about &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.impetus.com/content/big-data-master-class-nasscom-atc-2016&#39;&gt;Big Data Master Class  NASSCOM ATC 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;its premises. The workshop will feature a mix of hands-on technical &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/dark-side-of-wearables-tsunami-of-useless-medical-big-data/&#39;&gt;Dark side of wearables: Tsunami of useless medical big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At a recent media roundtable discussion about the future for wearables, hosted by Vivalnk, I was sitting next to two doctors who have been working in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/cochlear-to-extract-big-data-from-hearing-implants/&#39;&gt;Cochlear to extract big data from hearing implants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt; From spray-on skin for burns victims, the electronic pacemaker, the Gardasil and Cervarix cancer vaccines, or finding the medical application of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Cloud Computing News from @cloudfeednet - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Cloud Computing news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#34;&gt;@cloudfeednet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://virtualizationreview.com/articles/2016/12/08/passthrough-authentication-preview-added-to-azure-ad.aspx&#39;&gt;Pass-Through Authentication Preview Added to Azure AD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shops that want the benefits of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure public cloud, but still want to maintain local control of authentication, will soon have a new option. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchaws.techtarget.com/news/450404343/AWS-Blox-puzzles-fans-of-containers-in-cloud-computing&#39;&gt;AWS Blox puzzles fans of containers in cloud computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The advantage that Amazon has right now &amp;hellip; is that there&amp;rsquo;s no really credible open source equivalent to Lambda or Google Cloud Functions or &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://tech.firstpost.com/news-analysis/microsoft-corporation-announces-new-cloud-console-for-azure-portal-351991.html&#39;&gt;Microsoft Corporation announces new cloud console for Azure portal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new Microsoft Azure Cloud Console comes with an integrated workflow, that allows users to build applications on Azure using graphical interface &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nasdaq.com/article/google-partners-slack-to-dive-deeper-into-workplace-market-cm718474&#39;&gt;Google Partners Slack to Dive Deeper into Workplace Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alphabet GOOGL isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly giving up the cloud space. To make Google cloud services more attractive to all its customers, the company has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com.au/feature/salmat-it-leader-turned-to-google-partner-cloud-sherpas-to-move-office-into-the-cloud-444132&#39;&gt;Salmat IT leader turned to Google partner Cloud Sherpas to move office into&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CRN Australia Salmat is a leading Australian marketing services business. Its CTO, Dave Glover, is guiding the company as it looks to transform its office &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.openstack.org/videos/barcelona-2016/on-building-an-auto-healing-resource-cluster-using-senlin&#39;&gt;On Building an Auto-healing Resource Cluster using Senlin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;environment. How to accurately detect failures happen in different layers; how to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.enterprisetimes.co.uk/2016/12/09/openstack-mitaka-uk-public-sector/&#39;&gt;OpenStack Mitaka for UK public sector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UKCloud has announced that it is the first UK public sector cloud provider to support OpenStack Mitaka. The company calls this a major upgrade to its &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.infotechlead.com/cloud/microsoft-launches-azure-blockchain-as-a-service-in-india-44382&#39;&gt;Microsoft launches Azure Blockchain as a Service in India&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain-Logo Eyeing on the emerging market opportunity for Blockchain, Microsoft has launched Microsoft Azure Blockchain as a Service (BaaS) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.news18.com/news/tech/microsoft-unveils-azure-blockchain-as-service-1321115.html&#39;&gt;Microsoft Unveils Azure Blockchain as Service&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has launched Azure Blockchain as a Service (BaaS) that provides a rapid, low-cost and low-risk platform for organisations to collaborate &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.daijiworld.com/news/news_disp.asp?n_id=426947&#39;&gt;Red Hat launches OpenShift Dedicated solution on Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The enterprise customers can use Red Hat&amp;rsquo;s platform to build, launch and manage applications on &amp;ldquo;OpenShift Dedicated&amp;rdquo; with Google Cloud Platform &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.infoworld.com/article/3148815/cloud-computing/microsoft-brings-f-to-jupyter-notebooks-on-azure.html&#39;&gt;Microsoft brings F# to Jupyter Notebooks on Azure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure Notebooks cloud service is adding support for F#, the Microsoft-developed &amp;ldquo;functional-first&amp;rdquo; language. Azure Notebooks, a free &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dabcc.com/public-review-of-microsoft-intune-on-azure/&#39;&gt;Public Review of Microsoft Intune on Azure!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get ready for a whole new Intune experience. In early 2017 we will begin migrating our Intune admin experience onto the Azure portal, allowing for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.redhat.com/en/about/events/openstack-nfv-sr-iov-and-ovs-dpdk-integrated-deployment&#39;&gt;OpenStack NFV: SR-IOV and OVS-DPDK integrated deployment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;awareness support to optimize OpenStack orchestration and use of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://streetwisereport.com/stocks-aim-to-attain-street-attentions-wells-fargo-company-nysewfc-endurance-international-group-nasdaqeigi/3424800/&#39;&gt;Stocks Aim To Attain Street Attentions: Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company (NYSE:WFC),&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Street Wise Report (press release) (blog) This venture extends Google Cloud&amp;rsquo;s G Suite apps availability to small businesses through sub-resellers around the world.Consumers are now able to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://securitymiddleeast.com/2016/12/09/infoblox-brings-network-control-security-microsoft-azure/&#39;&gt;Infoblox brings network control and security to Microsoft Azure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Infoblox Inc., which provides DNS, DHCP, and IP address management (DDI), introduced Infoblox DDI for Microsoft Azure, a virtual appliance that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://thenextweb.com/insider/2016/12/09/pokemon-taught-cloud/&#39;&gt;What Pokmon taught me about the cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Niantic hasn&amp;rsquo;t said how it serves up its games, but rumor has it that the company is using Google&amp;rsquo;s cloud. If they are indeed using Google&amp;rsquo;s cloud, there &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://thenextweb.com/insider/2016/12/09/pokemon-taught-cloud/&#39;&gt;What Pokmon taught me about the cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When more storage is needed, a company just contacts Amazon Web Services (AWS), Google Cloud, IBM Azure, or the others, and takes on more &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/microsoft-launches-azure-blockchain-service-india/&#39;&gt;Microsoft Launches Azure Blockchain Service in India&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technology giant Microsoft has launched its Blockchain as a Service (BaaS) offering to provide blockchain solutions to customers over its Azure cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cloudpro.co.uk/leadership/cloud-essentials/6511/red-hat-and-google-join-forces-on-containers&#39;&gt;Red Hat and Google join forces on containers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Hat and Google are set to offer enterprise customers a managed OpenShift service hosted on Google&amp;rsquo;s cloud to make the build, launch and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/how-seattle-became-cloud-computing-city-amazon-microsoft-are-leading-tech-revolution/&#39;&gt;How Seattle became &amp;lsquo;Cloud City&amp;rsquo;: Amazon and Microsoft are leading a tech&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Seattle Times The goal: tapping in to Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure, the software maker&amp;rsquo;s network of on-demand computing power, to build a new generation of software. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.elegantthemes.com/blog/tips-tricks/how-to-install-wordpress-on-google-cloud-and-why-thats-awesome&#39;&gt;How to Install WordPress on Google Cloud (And Why That&amp;rsquo;s Awesome)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;we&amp;rsquo;ll show how to install WordPress on Google Cloud in a few quick steps! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.episerver.com/legal/episerver-trial-agreement-for-microsoft-azure-marketplace/&#39;&gt;(DXC) Services  Trial Agreement for Microsoft Azure Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Azure Marketplace. EPISERVER DXC SERVICES  TRIAL &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/how-seattle-became-cloud-computing-city-amazon-microsoft-are-leading-tech-revolution/&#39;&gt;How Seattle became &amp;lsquo;Cloud City&amp;rsquo;: Amazon and Microsoft are leading a tech&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Seattle Times In 2006 the company launched Amazon Web Services (AWS), which at first amounted to a big, web-accessed hard drive where other businesses &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thehindu.com/sci-tech/technology/Microsoft-unveils-Azure-Blockchain-as-Service/article16785197.ece&#39;&gt;Microsoft unveils Azure Blockchain as Service&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft on Friday launched Azure Blockchain as a Service (BaaS) that provides a rapid, low-cost and low-risk platform for organisations to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://intabloid.com/tech/microsoft-brings-new-cloud-console-for-azure-portal/010418&#39;&gt;Microsoft Brings New Cloud Console for Azure Portal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tech Giant, Microsoft has confirmed that they are launching a new cloud console for their own cloud service, Microsoft Azure. Cloud computing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financialexpress.com/industry/red-hat-launches-openshift-dedicated-on-google-cloud-platform/469567/&#39;&gt;Red Hat launches &amp;lsquo;OpenShift&amp;rsquo; dedicated on Google Cloud Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;World&amp;rsquo;s leading provider of open source solutions Red Hat has announced the general availability of OpenShift Dedicated on Google Cloud Platform. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://mobilesyrup.com/2016/12/09/amazon-web-services-launch-two-more-availability-zones-in-canada-region/&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services launch two more availability zones in Canada region&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services recently announced the launch of AWS Canada (Central) Region, and will offer two more availability zones at launch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newseveryday.com/articles/58977/20161209/google-slack-partnership-poses-threat-to-microsoft-companies-to-integrate-team-collaboration-products.htm&#39;&gt;Google, Slack Partnership Poses Threat To Microsoft; Companies To Integrate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;News Every day In a blog post, Head of Global Technology Partners of Google Cloud Nan Boden shares that &amp;ldquo;Google and Slack share the same vision for the future of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://realmoney.thestreet.com/articles/12/09/2016/how-amazons-stock-could-triple-next-five-years&#39;&gt;How Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Stock Could Triple in the Next Five Years&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, if Amazon Web Services can continue to grow at a 40% annual clip through 2021, it would be a $65 billion business by then. Working in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-age.com/5-collaboration-communication-predictions-2017-123463542/&#39;&gt;Top 5 collaboration and communication predictions for 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; surprise then that Google, Amazon and Microsoft are investing so heavily into cloud service delivery platforms like AWS, Azure and Google Cloud. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itbusinessnet.com/article/UKCloud-becomes-first-UK-public-sector-cloud-provider-to-support-OpenStack-Mitaka-4729740&#39;&gt;UKCloud becomes first UK public sector cloud provider to support OpenStack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT Business Net UKCloud, the easy to adopt, easy to use and easy to leave assured cloud services company, has announced a major upgrade to its entire Cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://mspoweruser.com/azure-media-indexer-2-preview-now-supports-japanese-language-models/&#39;&gt;Azure Media Indexer 2 Preview Now Supports Japanese Language Models&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft recently announced new improvements to the Azure Media Indexer 2 Preview which will improve the quality of the transcripts generated by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dbta.com/Editorial/News-Flashes/BlueData-Announces-General-Availability-of-BlueData-EPIC-on-AWS-115276.aspx&#39;&gt;BlueData Announces General Availability of BlueData EPIC on AWS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BlueData is announcing the general availability of its BlueData EPIC software on Amazon Web Services (AWS). We hardened the product and now &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://security.itbusinessnet.com/article/Endurance-Collaborates-with-Google-to-Empower-Small-Businesses-Globally-with-Professional-Intelligent-Apps-from-G-Suite-4730057&#39;&gt;Endurance Collaborates with Google to Empower Small Businesses Globally&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT Business Net BURLINGTON, Mass., Dec. 8, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash;Endurance International Group(NASDAQ:EIGI) today announced it has worked with Google &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://msdynamicsworld.com/story/microsoft-rolls-out-new-cloud-training-next-gen-tech-pros&#39;&gt;Microsoft Rolls Out New Cloud Training for Next-Gen Tech Pros&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has launched new free Azure training courses to help address the need for highly skilled cloud techs across a variety of industries &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://topexaminer.com/2016/12/09/amazon-web-services-go-local-for-canadian-customers/&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services go local for Canadian customers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon has revealed that its Canadian customers can now avail Amazon Web Services (AWS) Cloud through locally available data centers. This step &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dabcc.com/microsoft-creating-your-first-data-model-in-azure-analysis-services/&#39;&gt;Microsoft: Creating your first data model in Azure Analysis Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Azure Analysis Services is a new preview service in Microsoft Azure where you can host semantic data models. Users in your organization can then &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3171031&#39;&gt;Western Computer: Taking Business Apps to the Next Level with Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital Journal The new Microsoft Dynamics 365 software runs on the Microsoft Azure cloud platform. One aspect of the software is Customer Insights, which is a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cartt.ca/article/data-centres-amazon-web-services-comes-north-wants-partner-telcos&#39;&gt;DATA CENTRES: Amazon Web Services comes north, wants to partner with telcos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TORONTO  Amazon Web Services (AWS) has been setting up data centres around the world offering a wide range of compute and analytics services &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.infotechlead.com/cloud/dell-technologies-quiver-hit-cloud-market-44392&#39;&gt;What does Dell Technologies have in its quiver to hit cloud market?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; Technologies highlighted VMware partnerships with IBM and AWS, and expanded Pivotal Cloud Foundry partnerships with Google Cloud Platform &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.quest.com/community/products/active-administrator/f/forum/20273/keep-it-simple-manage-users-and-groups-in-microsoft-azure-active-directory-from-a-single-console&#39;&gt;Keep IT Simple: Manage Users and Groups in Microsoft Azure Active Directory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Share; More; Cancel. Related. Keep IT Simple: Manage Users and Groups in Microsoft Azure Active Directory from a Single Console! Read Blog. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cartt.ca/article/data-centres-amazon-web-services-comes-north-wants-partner-telcos&#39;&gt;DATA CENTRES: Amazon Web Services comes north, wants to partner with telcos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;ve been partnering big time with Microsoft [Azure], that&amp;rsquo;s the preferred partner at this point just because of the large partner network they &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.gurufocus.com/news/462858/amazons-innovations-make-it-a-buy&#39;&gt;Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Innovations Make It a Buy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the third quarter, Amazon Web Services (AWS) produced $3.2 billion of total revenue, setting the business at a yearly run rate of more than $10 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.montrealinternational.com/en/news/2016/12/amazon-web-services-cloud-now-available-to-customers-from-data-centers-in-canada/&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services Cloud Now Available to Customers from Data Centers in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SEATTLE  December 8, 2016  (NASDAQ:AMZN)  Amazon Web Services, Inc. (AWS), an Amazon.com company, today announced the launch of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://gcn.com/articles/2016/12/09/encrypted-gmail.aspx&#39;&gt;Client-side encryption enables Gmail for state users&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maryland has moved more state employees&amp;rsquo; email to Google Cloud after adding a platform that secures sensitive data in the cloud while leaving data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://marketrealist.com/2016/12/amazon-slammed-oracles-claim-competitiveness-cloud/&#39;&gt;Did Amazon Just Top Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Claim of Competitiveness in the Cloud?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At AWS&amp;rsquo;s Re-Invent 2016 conference, Amazon Web Services CEO Andy Jassy announced X-ray vision. According to Business Insider, Jassy &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://marketrealist.com/2016/12/amazon-empowers-aws-ongoing-artificial-intelligence-wave/&#39;&gt;Oracle Competitor Amazon Empowers AWS for Ongoing AI Wave&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oracle (ORCL) has become a competitive player in the billion-dollar cloud space, where Amazon.com (AMZN), with its market share of 30%, still &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.sdxcentral.com/articles/news/red-hats-container-platform-lands-on-google-cloud/2016/12/&#39;&gt;Red Hat&amp;rsquo;s Container Platform Lands on Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Google Cloud version of OpenShift Dedicated comes with 100 GB of flash-based persistent storage and nine nodes of computing, among other &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.eweek.com/video/microsoft-closes-26-billion-linkedin-social-network-buyout.html&#39;&gt;Mirosoft, LinkedIn Close Their $26 Billion Social Network Deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DAILY BRIEFING: Microsoft completes $26 Billion LinkedIn social network &amp;hellip; DAILY VIDEO: Microsoft Azure flaw posed RHEL hacking risk; Google &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily IoT/Blockchain news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://windowsitpro.com/security/secure-iot-through-oversight-open-source-and-open-standards&#39;&gt;Secure IoT Through Oversight, Open Source and Open Standards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My idea is that to secure the Internet of things, we need to take a three pronged approach that includes oversight, open source and open standards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nanalyze.com/2016/12/m2m-machine-to-machine-communication/&#39;&gt;Is Machine to Machine Communication (M2M) Dead?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;M2Mi or Machine-to-Machine Intelligence Corporation was founded in 2006 to enable organizations to create value and monetize their connected &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://iapp.org/news/a/startup-addresses-financial-institutions-blockchain-privacy-concerns/&#39;&gt;Startup addresses financial institutions&amp;rsquo; blockchain privacy concerns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;trusted parties will be able to decrypt their meaning. Our view is that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.pingidentity.com/en/blog/2016/12/07/authentication_in_the_iot_challenge_or_opportunity.html&#39;&gt;Authentication in the IoT: Challenge or Opportunity?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;recurring theme that it won&amp;rsquo;t reach its full potential if it&amp;rsquo;s not secure. The point is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://hackerboards.com/guest-column-a-guide-to-open-source-in-iot/&#39;&gt;Maximizing the benefits of open source in IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the dawn of the Internet of Things, software is making its way into every product, into every industry. And along with software come developers, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://themerkle.com/ethereum-based-projects-received-prizes-from-blockchain-startup-contest/&#39;&gt;Ethereum-based Projects Received Prizes from Blockchain Startup Contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The year 2016 has been kind for Blockchain startups, as the rise of Ethereum and the advancement of other protocols have resulted in the inception of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://nxter.org/referral-foundation-brings-blockchain-technology-to-referral-marketing-industry/&#39;&gt;Referral Foundation Brings Blockchain Technology to Referral Marketing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Referral Foundation is on a mission to upgrade the industry by introducing it to blockchain technology. It also provides early insights into the adoption &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/how-the-cyber-kangaroo-can-help-defend-the-internet-of-things/&#39;&gt;How the Cyber Kangaroo can help defend the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are Australia&amp;rsquo;s policy options for responding to the internet threats of 2022? This question was explored in the 360 Cyber Game conducted &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/BitGive-launches-blockchain-based-real-time-donation-tracking-system-GiveTrack-442788&#39;&gt;BitGive launches blockchain-based real-time donation tracking system&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes BitGive, the first Bitcoin 501&amp;copy;(3) nonprofit, has announced the launch of GiveTrack  a revolutionary blockchain-based donation platform. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2016/12/09/bluetooth_50_emerges_fancies_snacking_on_the_internet_of_things/&#39;&gt;Bluetooth 5.0 emerges, ready to chew on the internet of things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which will come in handy for things on the internet of things. Range can now hit 200m under the right circumstances. 8 x data refers to message size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.design-reuse.com/news/41065/unh-iol-iot-interoperability.html&#39;&gt;UNH-IOL Shines Spotlight on Internet of Things Interoperability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DURHAM, N.H., DECEMBER 8, 2016  The University of New Hampshire InterOperability Laboratory (UNH-IOL), an independent provider of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/PayCommerce-expands-global-footprint-to-drive-blockchain-and-AI-innovations-442803&#39;&gt;PayCommerce expands global footprint to drive blockchain and AI innovations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PayCommerce, open cross-border payments network and banking consortium, has announced the expansion of its global footprint with the opening of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.design-reuse.com/news/41065/unh-iol-iot-interoperability.html?&#39;&gt;UNH-IOL Shines Spotlight on Internet of Things Interoperability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UNH-IOL Shines Spotlight on Internet of Things Interoperability &amp;hellip; today announced the launch of the Internet of Things (IoT) IP Testing Services. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://telecom.economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/modi-govts-efforts-to-increase-internet-penetration-driving-iot-adoption-6wresearch/55890223&#39;&gt;Modi govt&amp;rsquo;s efforts to increase internet penetration driving IoT adoption:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ETTelecom.com India&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things (IoT) market is likely to grow at a CAGR of 28.2% during 2016-22, driven by industrial vertical, according to 6Wresearch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://home.bt.com/tech-gadgets/future-tech/bt-huawei-5g-mobile-technology-partnership-11364119667641&#39;&gt;BT and Huawei embark on pioneering 5G research partnership&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; network resources to specific services; machine-to-machine communications in Internet of Things (IoT) applications; and security technologies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Cubichain-Technologies-deploys-blockchain-for-3D-printing-and-Additive-Manufacturing-industry-442934&#39;&gt;Cubichain Technologies deploys blockchain for 3D printing and Additive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes California-based startup Cubichain Technologies along with CalRAM LLC. announced the successful demonstration of deployment of a blockchain &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcquest.com/can-iot-ease-our-demonetisation-pain/&#39;&gt;Can IoT Ease Our Demonetisation Pain?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Machine-to-Machine interactions in IoT-empowered devices allow collection and transfer of large volumes of user-specific information using various &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/ibm-blockchain-ecosystem/&#39;&gt;IBM to Launch Blockchain Ecosystem While Rapidly Expanding Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CryptoCoinsNews Blockchain has the potential to transform the way industries conduct business transactions, writes IBM in their most recent press release. This will &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/67381/everledger-secures-the-first-bottle-of-wine-on-the-blockchain&#39;&gt;Everledger secures the first bottle of wine on the blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emerging technology firm Everledger is the first organisation to secure a bottle of wine&amp;rsquo;s provenance on the blockchain. The bottle, a 2001 Margaux, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://readwrite.com/2016/12/08/uks-bristol-wins-laurels-smart-city-leadership-cl4/&#39;&gt;UK&amp;rsquo;s Bristol wins laurels for its programmable city initiative&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Globe Newswire said that the southwest U.K. city recently won the Smart City Award at the World Communications Awards &amp;amp; Internet of Things Awards &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://ibsintelligence.com/ibs-journal/ibs-news/everledger-secures-a-bottle-of-wine-on-the-blockchain/&#39;&gt;Everledger secures a bottle of wine on the blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everledger has become the first financial organisation to secure a bottle of wine&amp;rsquo;s provenance on the blockchain. Yes, you have read that correctly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/ARK-blockchain-ecosystem-to-launch-public-testnest-mobile-and-desktop-clients-442718&#39;&gt;ARK blockchain ecosystem to launch public testnest mobile and desktop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes The ARK blockchain ecosystem has announced the first publically available test network along with mobile and desktop clients, while the platform is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161209005022/en/Internet-Market-Expected-Reach-500-Million-2020&#39;&gt;The Internet of Things Market Is Expected to Reach $500 Million in 2020,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) BOULDER, Colo.&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;A recent slide-based report from Navigant Research explores the US market for the Internet of Things (IoT), &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itbusinessnet.com/article/Boost-for-IoT-interoperability-as-open-source-foundations-and-projects-use-oneM2M-standards-4729598&#39;&gt;Boost for IoT interoperability as open source foundations and projects use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT Business Net oneM2M, the global standards partnership for Machine-to-Machine (M2M) communications and the Internet of Things (IoT), has revealed its standards &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prolificnorth.co.uk/2016/12/manchester-agency-involved-in-internet-of-things-heritage-project/&#39;&gt;Manchester agency involved in Internet of Things heritage project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manchester agency involved in Internet of Things heritage project. mellor. Stephen Chapman. By Stephen Chapman  9 December 2016. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/microsoft-launches-azure-blockchain-service-india/&#39;&gt;Microsoft Launches Azure Blockchain Service in India&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technology giant Microsoft has launched its Blockchain as a Service (BaaS) offering to provide blockchain solutions to customers over its Azure cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/357292859/one-stop-media-now-offers-blockchain-and-chatbot-solutions-to-australian-businesses&#39;&gt;One Stop Media Now Offers Blockchain and Chatbot Solutions to Australian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EIN News (press release) At One Stop Media, we are passionate about learning new technologies and can now Offer Our Clients the latest in Blockchain and Chatbot Solutions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.computerweekly.com/news/450404392/Blackberry-changes-tack-to-secure-enterprise-internet-of-things&#39;&gt;Blackberry changes tack to secure enterprise internet of things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry has moved beyond mobile device management with a platform targeting the emerging world of the internet of things (IoT) in the enterprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nasdaq.com/article/3-tech-stocks-to-buy-in-december-cm719108&#39;&gt;3 Tech Stocks to Buy in December&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big improvements in network speed and data capacity are needed to accommodate the machine-to-machine communication boom, and Verizon is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.fool.com/investing/2016/12/09/why-calamp-corp-stock-popped-125-in-november.aspx&#39;&gt;Why CalAmp Corp. Stock Popped 12.5% in November&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The machine-to-machine communications company has all but recovered from a disappointing quarter. Here&amp;rsquo;s what investors need to know. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/12/09/bitgive-foundation-launches-givetrack-blockchain-fund-tracking-platform/&#39;&gt;BitGive Foundation Launches GiveTrack Blockchain Fund-tracking Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s underlying blockchain technology is known for transparency, something which the non-profit sector is in dire need of. BitGive Foundation, the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/sovereign-blockchains-will-change-monetary-policy-bank-paper-argues/&#39;&gt;&amp;lsquo;Sovereign&amp;rsquo; Blockchains Will Change Monetary Policy, Bank Paper Argues&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new research paper published by South Africa&amp;rsquo;s FirstRand Bank explores the world of central banks and blockchains, suggesting that the technology &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.finsmes.com/2016/12/blockchain-fintech-startup-setl-received-investment-from-deloitte.html&#39;&gt;Blockchain Fintech Startup Setl Received Investment from Deloitte&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Setl, a London, UK-based startup providing blockchain solutions for post-trade activity in financial services, received an investment from Deloitte. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://invezz.com/news/equities/24870-BT-share-price-Group-inks-5G-research-deal-with-Huawei&#39;&gt;BT share price: Group inks 5G research deal with Huawei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; the UK to explore various aspects of 5G, including network architecture, machine-to-machine communications in Internet of Things (IoT) applications &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://techcrunch.com/2016/12/09/vesper-grabs-15m-to-build-a-durable-low-power-mic-that-listens-forever/&#39;&gt;Vesper grabs $15M to build a durable low-power mic that listens forever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; hearables, Vesper is also looking at applications for their specialized MEMS microphones within the Internet of Things and connected car markets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.chicagotribune.com/bluesky/originals/ct-glance-smart-mirror-bsi-20161209-story.html&#39;&gt;Glance wants to put a smart mirror in your house, your gym, your hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trio of software engineers and Internet of Things developers founded Glance in February at tech hub 1871. McQuown is president and chief &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://nextbillion.net/news/stellar-partners-icici-bank-enables-blockchain-money-transfers-in-india-africa-and-philippines/&#39;&gt;Stellar Partners ICICI Bank, Enables Blockchain Money Transfers in India,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stellar, the open blockchain platform and non-profit payment protocol has unveiled a slew of new partners including, notably, India&amp;rsquo;s largest private &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://boingboing.net/2016/12/09/company-town-internet-of-thi.html&#39;&gt;Company town + Internet of Things + Drones = total surveillance of remote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boing Boing Rio Tinto is a giant UK/Australian mining corporation that operates many facilities in Australia&amp;rsquo;s remotest reaches, where there is no housing for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/241911/blackberry-unveils-enterprise-of-things-with-mobile-security&#39;&gt;BlackBerry Unveils Enterprise of Things with Mobile Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry Limited (BBRY - Free Report) launched its mobile security platform which is primarily designed for Enterprise of Things (EoT). The move &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cointelegraph.com/news/fintech-30-blockchain-overrated-bitcoin-underrated&#39;&gt;FinTech 3.0: Blockchain Overrated, Bitcoin Underrated&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This conference claims to explore FinTech 3.0, including Blockchain technology and other decentralized solutions for financial processes, and its &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nasdaq.com/article/how-blockchain-is-shaking-things-up-bestselling-author-alex-tapscott-looks-ahead-cm719122&#39;&gt;How Blockchain Is Shaking Things Up: Bestselling Author Alex Tapscott Looks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nasdaq 2016 has been a year of significant advancement for blockchain technology, a globally distributed ledger with digital application for industries ranging &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.fxpips.com/blockchain-gambling-platform-vdice-to-complete-ico-next-week/&#39;&gt;Blockchain Gambling Platform vDice to Complete ICO next week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;vDice only offers traditional dice gambling over the blockchain for now, but hopes to further develop vDice.io after the successful completion of the IPO. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.fundstrategy.co.uk/blockchain-fund-settlement-services-feature-investment-market-review/&#39;&gt;Blockchain and fund settlement services feature in investment market review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain and fund settlement services feature in investment market review. By Jessica Tasman-Jones 8th December 2016 4:44 pm 8th December &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/Permissioned-Blockchain-Configuration-Could-Help-Eliminate-Threat-Of-Hackers-In-Digital-Voting-Propose-Winners-Of-Kaspersky-Labs-Cybersecurity-Case-Study-Competition-H-20161208&#39;&gt;Permissioned Blockchain Configuration Could Help Eliminate Threat Of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World First place was awarded to the team from New York University, which proposed the usage of a &amp;ldquo;permissioned blockchain&amp;rdquo; configuration, in which a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lexology.com/library/detail.aspx?g=4ee7622c-03ae-466c-a432-58f6ea87e815&#39;&gt;US Agencies Release Guidance for Securing the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things continues to draw broad interest from policymakers and regulators around the globe. Following on the heels of a major &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.rcrwireless.com/20161209/asia-pacific/huawei-bt-partner-5g-research-tag23&#39;&gt;Huawei, BT partner on 5G research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; a new air interface between devices and base stations; network slicing; machine-to-machine communications in Internet of Things (IoT) applications; &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.medgadget.com/2016/12/global-m2m-connected-healthcare-market-forward-looking-perspective-on-different-factors-driving-or-restraining-market-growth.html&#39;&gt;Global M2M Connected Healthcare Market: Forward looking perspective on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medgadget (blog) Over the past few years, the healthcare industry has been witnessing increasing adoption of machine to machine (M2M) technology in order to reduce &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://threatpost.com/nyu-students-apply-blockchain-solution-to-electronic-voting-security/122382/&#39;&gt;NYU Students Apply Blockchain Solution to Electronic Voting Security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A team of engineering and policy students at New York University took a stab at a solution that applies blockchain to the problem. The students, Kevin &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/peterjreilly/2016/12/09/irs-coinbase-summons-what-are-you-going-to-do-when-they-come-for-you/&#39;&gt;IRS Coinbase Summons What Are You Going To Do When They Come For You ?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thing I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus on is the blockchain. The blockchain is like a really thorough version of the website Where&amp;rsquo;s George which allows people &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/sufian-farrukh/how-internet-of-things-wi_b_13485040.html&#39;&gt;How Internet Of Things Will Revolutionise The Supply Chain?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When someone refers to the Internet of Things (IoT), most of us relate it to electronics or wearables - perhaps the type of technologies that are driving &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/vesper-raises-15m-series-drive-110000496.html&#39;&gt;Vesper Raises $15M Series A to Drive Pervasive Voice Interfaces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These products include smartphones, smart cities, smart speakers, Internet of Things (IoT) devices and connected cars. Vesper is funded by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/tjmccue/2016/12/08/celebrity-security-hacks-are-not-the-only-hacks-protecting-your-business/&#39;&gt;Celebrity Security Hacks Are Not The Only Hacks: Protecting Your Business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forbes &amp;hellip; yourself, your business, your smartphone, and your home network with its internet of things connected lights or security cams that is also at risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.programmableweb.com/news/understanding-requirements-and-standards-behind-green-button-api-initiative/analysis/2016/12/09&#39;&gt;Understanding The Requirements and Standards Behind The Green Button API&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ProgrammableWeb Implement a high degree of security in machine-to-machine web services. Modern communications must protect the confidentiality, integrity, and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/a16z-usv-invest-10-million-blockchain-token-trading-polychain-capital/&#39;&gt;A16z, USV Invest $10 Million in Blockchain Token Trading Firm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A startup that specializes in the trading of blockchain-based assets has raised a $10m fund backed by Andreessen Horowitz (A16z) and Union Square &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://bravenewcoin.com/news/berlins-esmt-becomes-latest-university-to-accept-bitcoins-for-tuition/&#39;&gt;Berlin&amp;rsquo;s ESMT becomes latest university to accept bitcoins for tuition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Christoph Burger, a senior associate dean for the ESMT executive education program is also the university&amp;rsquo;s blockchain expert, according to the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/us-regulators-discuss-difficulties-of-smart-contract-oversight/&#39;&gt;Smart Contract Issues Set Off &amp;lsquo;Alarm Bells&amp;rsquo;, Says US Regulator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, CFTC commissioner Christopher Giancarlo said blockchain could be &amp;ldquo;the biggest technological innovation in the financial services &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://boingboing.net/2016/12/09/the-mirai-worm-is-gnawing-its.html&#39;&gt;The Mirai worm is gnawing its way through the Internet of Things and will&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boing Boing Lily Hay Newman&amp;rsquo;s Wired article on Mirai provides some much-needed context into Mirai&amp;rsquo;s past and future, and makes a persuasive case that IoT &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cointelegraph.com/press-releases/byteball-to-give-away-its-new-cryptocurrency-for-free-to-bitcoin-holders-on-christmas-day&#39;&gt;Byteball to Give Away Its New Cryptocurrency for Free to Bitcoin Holders on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoinTelegraph Byteball, the cryptocurrency platform for decentralized storage and transfer of value, is built on Directed Acyclic Graph (DAG) instead of blockchain like &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://arstechnica.co.uk/tech-policy/2016/12/maker-of-internet-of-things-connected-vibrator-will-settle-privacy-suit/&#39;&gt;Maker of Internet of Things-connected vibrator will settle privacy suit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few months back, we reported on the collision of the Internet of Things and sex toys. The maker of an Internet-connected, remote-controlled vibrator &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/09/vesper-raises-15m-bring-always-microphones-internet-things/&#39;&gt;Vesper raises $15M to bring always-on microphones to the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vesper Technologies, Inc. said today it has closed a $15 million Series A funding round to advance its tiny microphones for use in almost any device. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitalmusicnews.com/2016/12/09/blockchain-bitcoin-save-music-industry/&#39;&gt;Why Blockchain Won&amp;rsquo;t Save the Music Industry (at Least Not Yet)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge with using the blockchain for music isn&amp;rsquo;t a technological one. It&amp;rsquo;s a set of interlocking business problems that have been around since &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.moneycontrol.com/news/sme/how-crypto-currencies-will-revolutionise-our-worldfuture_8091761.html&#39;&gt;How crypto currencies will revolutionise our world in future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buterin who conceptualised Ethereum, a blockchain based distributed &amp;hellip; contract which is a computer program that you can upload on the BlockChain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.himss.org/getinvolved/hidden-menace-body-healthcare-internet-things&#39;&gt;The Hidden Menace in the Body of the HealthCare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Source: The Hidden Menace in the Body of the HealthCare Internet of Things. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/us-commerce-department-weighs-blockchain-washington-event/&#39;&gt;US Commerce Department Weighs Blockchain at Washington Event&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Held in Washington, DC, the event drew a mix of regulators, business representatives and members of the startup world, including blockchain firm &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.readitquik.com/news/fintech/ibm-introduces-blockchain-ecosystem-for-collaboration/&#39;&gt;IBM Introduces Blockchain Ecosystem for Collaboration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IBM has announced a new blockchain ecosystem, which will provide enterprises the tools and resources to develop their own blockchain applications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.biztechmagazine.com/article/2016/12/internet-things-creates-business-opportunities-and-challenges&#39;&gt;The Internet of Things Creates Business Opportunities and Challenges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IoT can drive new revenue and efficiencies, but the technology requires high levels of interoperability, portability and management  all of which &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.engadget.com/2016/12/09/bluetooth-inventor-jaap-haartsen-interview/&#39;&gt;The inventor of Bluetooth on where wireless is going next&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, 5G, but we also talk about the Internet of Things. We&amp;rsquo;ll have millions of devices within a square kilometer, and we&amp;rsquo;ll have to think about how &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.news.com.au/technology/gadgets/think-twice-before-buying-these-kids-toys-this-christmas/news-story/00056c526ddd7d5e047da3294250cdcc&#39;&gt;Think twice before buying these kids toys this Christmas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With internet technology now on many more products than just our laptops and phones (the &amp;lsquo;internet of things&amp;rsquo;), consumers face unprecedented levels &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/spells-of-genesis-soft-launch-pairs-enhanced-gameplay-with-advantages-of-blockchain-tech-1481321040&#39;&gt;Spells of Genesis Soft Launch Pairs Enhanced Gameplay With Advantages of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Magazine The world of gaming is changing, with some games now integrating digital currencies into their platforms using the blockchain. One example is Spells &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2016/b2b-venture-capital-fintech-startup-deloitte-blockchain-santander-innoventures-tradeshift-investment-round-funding/&#39;&gt;High-Profile  But Secretive  Funding For B2B FinTechs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7), the funding marks Deloitte&amp;rsquo;s first public investment in a blockchain company, but again, the firms kept quiet about how much was raised. Still, the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.luxresearchinc.com/sites/default/files/LUX%20RESEARCH_Blockchain%20Report%20Excerpt_12_16.pdf&#39;&gt;beyond finance: blockchain&amp;rsquo;s impact on the power sector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; on the potentially massive opportunities for blockchain beyond finance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.osa-opn.org/home/industry/2016/december/investing_in_the_global_internet_of_things/&#39;&gt;Investing in the Global Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Transportation is one the of the many industries expected to be impacted by the &amp;ldquo;Internet of Things.&amp;rdquo; [Image: George Dement/Creative Commons]. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com/news/internet-of-things/video/300083102/new-signature-executive-how-solution-providers-can-adapt-to-fit-the-unique-iot-space.htm&#39;&gt;New Signature Executive: How Solution Providers Can &amp;lsquo;Adapt To Fit The&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CRN New Signature has tapped into the Internet of Things with a sweet solution &amp;ndash; helping The Hershey Company wire its existing production equipment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.infoworld.com/article/3148865/mobile-security/blackberry-integrates-its-enterprise-iot-and-mobile-security-portfolio.html&#39;&gt;BlackBerry integrates its enterprise IoT and mobile security portfolio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry has unveiled a comprehensive mobile-security platform for a wide variety of mobile and internet of things devices connected to enterprises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.navigantresearch.com/newsroom/the-internet-of-things-market-is-expected-to-reach-500-million-in-2020&#39;&gt;The Internet of Things Market Is Expected to Reach $500 Million in 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things is expected to transform the relationship between utilities and customers. A recent slide-based report from Navigant Research &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://gulfnewsjournal.com/stories/511018791-emirates-nbd-set-for-new-blockchain-initiative&#39;&gt;Emirates NBD set for new blockchain initiative&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I am delighted that we are the first bank in India and among few globally to set up a blockchain application, Chanda Kochhar, CEO and managing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.digitalocean.com/community/tutorials/how-to-install-and-secure-the-mosquitto-mqtt-messaging-broker-on-ubuntu-16-04&#39;&gt;How to Install and Secure the Mosquitto MQTT Messaging Broker on Ubuntu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Introduction. MQTT is a machine-to-machine messaging protocol, designed to provide lightweight publish/subscribe communication to &amp;ldquo;Internet of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.macobserver.com/news/bluetooth-5-internet-of-things/&#39;&gt;Bluetooth 5: It&amp;rsquo;s All About the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The massive range increase and lower power requirements over Bluetooth 4.2 are good news for Internet of Things, or IoT, device makers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.kykernel.com/news/lecture-series-speaks-to-the-importance-of-cybersecurity/article_e053046a-bd8f-11e6-9830-1b2496d8320c.html&#39;&gt;Lecture series speaks to the importance of cybersecurity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Murphy also discussed the idea of the large security risks with the Internet of Things (or IOT), which are household appliances that are connected to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.manufacturingglobal.com/technology/1069/The-technology-of-safety:-keep-your-facility-connected-and-secure&#39;&gt;The technology of safety: keep your facility connected and secure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But these benefits come with difficulties - cyber attackers are increasingly using poorly-defended Internet of Things (IoT) devices as the gateway to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Mobile Computing news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topmobilenews&#34;&gt;@topmobilenews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.voxy.co.nz/business/5/270827&#39;&gt;Out of date websites cost Kiwi businesses dearly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;These mobile apps, by their very nature, are designed to be responsive and their popularity only goes to prove just how popular mobile computing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com.au/feature/canberra-reseller-mit-services-prepares-for-school-byod-surge-444157&#39;&gt;Canberra reseller MIT Services prepares for school BYOD surge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being the end of financial year for most independent schools in Canberra, it&amp;rsquo;s when they start updating their laptop fleets and bring-your-own-device &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://networking.cioreview.com/cioviewpoint/the-byod-revolution-has-added-the-traditional-desk-phone-to-the-endangered-species-list-but-is-this-the-end-nid-15348-cid-9.html&#39;&gt;The BYOD revolution has added the traditional desk phone to the endangered&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CIOReview It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that ditching the desk phone is not always analogous with canceling your phone service. In most cases, an end user will still &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itproportal.com/features/byod-or-bring-your-own-device-what-businesses-need-to-know/&#39;&gt;BYOD or Bring-your-own-device: What businesses need to know&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The foremost way that businesses are tackling the BYOD security risk is by implementing mobile device management (MDM) software. The main aim &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itproportal.com/features/byod-or-bring-your-own-device-what-businesses-need-to-know/&#39;&gt;BYOD or Bring-your-own-device: What businesses need to know&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the rise of smartphone technology, bring your own device - or BYOD - certainly cannot be ignored by businesses. Whether they endorse the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mobilecomputingtoday.co.uk/4876/iphone-red-color-option/&#39;&gt;Next iPhone can have a Red Color Option&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The year 2016 is about to end very soon. It is now the time when we will see a lot of rumours floating all over the internet about the next iPhone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.computerweekly.com/news/450404392/Blackberry-changes-tack-to-secure-enterprise-internet-of-things&#39;&gt;Blackberry changes tack to secure enterprise internet of things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry has moved beyond mobile device management with a platform targeting the emerging world of the internet of things (IoT) in the enterprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://theindependentrepublic.com/2016/12/09/technology-stocks-worth-chasing-nielsen-holdings-plc-nlsn-qualcomm-incorporated-qcom/&#39;&gt;Technology Stocks Worth Chasing: Nielsen Holdings plc (NLSN), QUALCOMM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Independent Republic &amp;hellip; Windows 10 on mobile computing devices powered by next-generation Qualcomm Snapdragon processors, enabling mobile, power efficient, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161209005018/en/Pulse-Generator-%E2%80%93-Market-Drivers-Forecast-Technavio&#39;&gt;Pulse Generator  Market Drivers and Forecast by Technavio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The growth in internet bandwidth is fueled by two factors: the proliferation of mobile computing devices with new capabilities (such as smartphones, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/393832/Bring-Your-Own-Device-BYOD-Market-to-reach-USD-350-billion-To-2023.html&#39;&gt;Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) Market to reach USD 350 billion To 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MarketStudyReport.com adds Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) Market Size By End-Use (Small Businesses, Mid-To-Large Sized Businesses), &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.toptechnews.com/article/index.php?story_id=021000NNHRNR&#39;&gt;Faster Windows 10 Mobile Devices Promised by Microsoft, Qualcomm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft had previously targeted the mobile computing market with ARM-based devices running Windows RT, which launched in late 2012. However &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.trefis.com/stock/bbry/articles/390823/what-blackberry-aims-to-achieve-with-its-latest-security-offering/2016-12-09&#39;&gt;What BlackBerry Aims To Achieve With Its Latest Security Offering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry Secure will simplify BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s security offerings, by integrating its multi-platform mobile device management software BES12, now called &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.themalaymailonline.com/tech-gadgets/article/microsoft-unveils-windows-10-for-qualcomm-chips-hits-intel&#39;&gt;Microsoft unveils Windows 10 for Qualcomm chips, hits Intel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;ll also bring to Windows the Qualcomm chips that have been integral to the explosion of mobile computing, a growing business Microsoft has failed &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Security News from @trustpath - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-trust-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-trust-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Security news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/trustpath&#34;&gt;@trustpath&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thestar.com/business/2016/12/08/blackberry-unveils-new-platform-for-cyber-security-threats.html&#39;&gt;BlackBerry unveils new platform for cyber security threats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chen said the platform is aimed at easing the threat of data breaches that mount a roadblock to the potential of the Enterprise of Things, which &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.jordanlawrence.com/insights/2016/11/28/law-firm-data-breach-info&#39;&gt;Breaking Down Law Firm Data Breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and have no plan to remediate a breach. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/13445/identity-verification-in-an-era-of-data-breaches&#39;&gt;Identity verification in an era of data breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyberattacks and breaches have grown in frequency, and losses are on the rise. In 2015 the number of U.S. data breaches continued to break records &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://e27.co/2017-walks-get-ready-face-cyber-security-threats-20161209/&#39;&gt;As 2017 walks in, get yourself ready to face these cyber security threats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Forcepoint report predicts cyber security threats that we are likely to face next year. One of them being millennials. By Anisa Menur A. Maulani 09 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://metro.co.uk/2016/12/09/how-to-prevent-yourself-being-caught-out-by-a-massive-hack-6311386/&#39;&gt;How to stop hackers if you&amp;rsquo;ve been the victim of a cyber attack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;M:You&amp;rsquo;ve exposed big data breaches, such as Dropbox and xHamster, &amp;hellip; The most common method used by hackers when it comes to data breaches, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/this-highly-personalized-malware-campaign-targets-retailers-with-phony-customer-queries/&#39;&gt;This &amp;lsquo;highly personalized&amp;rsquo; malware campaign targets retailers with phony&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ZDNet &amp;hellip; containing the relatively new &amp;lsquo;August&amp;rsquo; malware (lines in the malware&amp;rsquo;s code as well as the control panel for stolen credentials all refer to the month). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.streetinsider.com/Analyst+Comments/BTIG+Starts+VASCO+Data+Security+(VDSI)+at+Buy/12328236.html&#39;&gt;BTIG Starts VASCO Data Security (VDSI) at Buy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; verticals, just as governments shift greater attention towards building national standards to hold enterprises accountable for data breaches.&amp;ldquo;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nojitter.com/post/240172187/are-you-prepared-for-a-data-breach&#39;&gt;Are You Prepared for a Data Breach?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some data breaches can take months to discover. In fact, in its fourth annual Experian-sponsored study on enterprise response to data breaches, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pandasecurity.com/mediacenter/products/panda-virus-bulletin-awards/&#39;&gt;Panda Endpoint Protection Is Given The VB100 Certificate By Virus Bulletin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;independent consultancy Virus Bulletin.See the complete report with study &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://247wallst.com/technology-3/2016/12/09/data-breaches-hit-health-care-industry-hard-could-be-worse-in-2017/&#39;&gt;Data Breaches Hit Health Care Industry Hard, Could Be Worse in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The health care industry is expected to be hackers&amp;rsquo; most heavily targeted sector in 2017, according to the latest Data Breach Industry Forecast from &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-isle-of-man-38243141&#39;&gt;Confidential data about vulnerable children stolen in Isle of Man&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Civil liberties campaigner Tristram Llewellyn Jones said data breaches, while not are not uncommon, can be even more serious on an island. &amp;ldquo;The Isle &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.readitquik.com/news/personal-security/online-security-fear-growing-among-internet-users/&#39;&gt;Online Security Fear Growing among Internet Users&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The recent passing of the Investigatory Powers Act, as well as news about new data breaches, will only bring this worry into greater focus. Businesses &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://appdevelopermagazine.com/4694/2016/12/9/Loggly-gets-AWS-DevOps-competency-status&#39;&gt;Loggly gets AWS DevOps competency status&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loggly offers a cloud-based log management service that mines vast amounts of data in real time and reveals what matters so that DevOps teams &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.darkreading.com/operations/pci-security-standards-council-publishes-supplemental-pci-dss-scoping-guidance/d/d-id/1327683&#39;&gt;PCI SECURITY STANDARDS COUNCIL PUBLISHES SUPPLEMENTAL PCI DSS SCOPING &amp;hellip;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; 9 December 2016  Incorrectly identifying where and how payment data is at risk in an organization&amp;rsquo;s systems continues to lead to data breaches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/186036/enterprise-governance-risk-and-compliance-market-expecting-worldwide-growth-by-2021&#39;&gt;Enterprise Governance, Risk and Compliance Market Expecting Worldwide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsMaker (press release) Such data breaches can destroy the confidential information and processes within seconds and can cause massive financial losses to the companies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.informationsecuritybuzz.com/study/25-organisations-can-effectively-detect-respond-data-breaches/&#39;&gt;Only 25% Of Organisations Can Effectively Detect And Respond To Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBuzz News London, UK. Tripwire, Inc., a leading global provider of security and compliance solutions for enterprises and industrial organizations, today &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Venture/Startup news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topventurenews&#34;&gt;@topventurenews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.greenbaypressgazette.com/story/money/2016/12/08/winnebago-seed-fund/95157438/&#39;&gt;New $10M fund aims to aid NE Wis. startups&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Badger Fund of Funds, a $25 million venture capital fund started by the &amp;hellip; Trotter said the seed fund&amp;rsquo;s investments should give startups enough &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techcircle.vccircle.com/2016/12/09/exclusive-fashion-e-commerce-startup-stalkbuylove-raises-funding-from-kalaari-others/&#39;&gt;Exclusive: Fashion e-commerce startup StalkBuyLove raises funding from&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VCCircle Existing investors including early-stage VC fund Singularity Ventures, Asia Venture Group, Asian E-Commerce Alliance, Kabs Ventures and FabIndia &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2016/b2b-venture-capital-fintech-startup-deloitte-blockchain-santander-innoventures-tradeshift-investment-round-funding/&#39;&gt;High-Profile  But Secretive  Funding For B2B FinTechs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For startups, 2016 wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best year in venture capital. Analysts say that investors&amp;rsquo; wallets could be opening up as we enter 2017, though. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/09/startup-layoffs/&#39;&gt;Well-Funded Startups Are Cutting Costs and Laying Off Staff&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, I predicted that many startups would go through &amp;hellip; million in venture funding from Meritech Capital Partners and Storm Ventures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pharmiweb.com/pressreleases/pressrel.asp?ROW_ID=195138&#39;&gt;Commercial Pharmaceutical Analytics Market to Provide over USD 1.5 Billion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PharmiWeb.com (press release) The tools such as Big Data, Tablue, Hadoop, and such others actually made it possible to handle such a huge data from these industries. Big Data has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://datacenternews.asia/story/znv-cloudera-target-big-data-analytics-management-data-centers/&#39;&gt;ZNV &amp;amp; Cloudera target big data analytics management in data centers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company says this need must be addressed, so it launched WeKeeper, a big data solution that will aid data center managers in their choices &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://reliefweb.int/report/world/guide-data-innovation-development-idea-proof-concept&#39;&gt;A guide to data innovation for development: From idea to proof-of-concept&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Global Pulse has served as a big data innovation hub within the UN for the past five years, testing new approaches and designing big data pilot &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/183817/global-big-data-and-analytics-in-telecom-industry-growth-analysis-and-insight-research-report-to-2016-and-forecast-to-2021&#39;&gt;Global Big Data and Analytics in Telecom Industry Growth, Analysis, and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsMaker (press release) The Global Big Data and Analytics in Telecom Industry Industry 2016 Market Research Report is a professional and in-depth study on the current state &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thefifthestate.com.au/innovation/engineering/the-megatrends-that-will-rock-the-property-industry/87296&#39;&gt;The megatrends that will rock the property industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A number of potential disrupters were uncovered, including sustainable cities, the move to carbon zero, big data, the sharing economy, virtual reality, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/big-data/interactive-analysis-of-genomic-datasets-using-amazon-athena/&#39;&gt;Interactive Analysis of Genomic Datasets Using Amazon Athena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;running a big data system. This makes Athena an excellent complement to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://prwire.com.au/pr/64697/leveraging-big-data-analytics-in-retail&#39;&gt;Leveraging Big Data Analytics in Retail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubai, United Arab Emirates, December 8, 2016: With the high influx of information available, every business  from finance to healthcare, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketingtechnews.net/news/2016/dec/08/ways-turning-big-data-marketing-gold/&#39;&gt;Ways of turning big data into marketing gold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wherever we turn in the 21st century, all industries are jumping on the idea of big data; and marketing is no different. Businesses from start ups to blue &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3168802&#39;&gt;Big Data Report 2016 - Global Strategic Business Report 2014-2022 -&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital Journal DUBLIN&amp;ndash;(Business Wire)&amp;ndash;Research and Markets has announced the addition of the &amp;ldquo;Big Data - Global Strategic Business Report&amp;rdquo; report to their &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://theartnewspaper.com/market/how-big-data-is-set-to-change-the-art-market/&#39;&gt;How Big Data is set to change the art market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In late October, Sotheby&amp;rsquo;s announced it had acquired the Mei Moses Art Indices, a database of repeat auction sales that tracks value over time; shortly &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161208005017/en/Big-Data-Holds-Key-Life-Saving-Discoveries&#39;&gt;Big Data Holds Key to Life Saving Discoveries Says Biomatters Whitepaper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;A whitepaper released today by bioinformatics technology company Biomatters examines the critical &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/zoomdata-earns-the-top-ranking-in-2nd-annual-big-data-analytics-market-study-from-dresner-advisory-services/&#39;&gt;Zoomdata Earns the Top Ranking in 2nd Annual Big Data Analytics Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) SAN MATEO, CA(Marketwired  Dec 7, 2016)  Zoomdata, developers of the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest visual analytics platform for big data, today announced it &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161208005164/en/ZEPL-Announces-4.1M-Funding-Accelerate-Innovation-Adoption&#39;&gt;ZEPL Announces $4.1M Funding to Accelerate Innovation and Adoption of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) And though recent advances in Hadoop, Spark, and other compute &amp;hellip; Apache Zeppelin is fast becoming the standard big data visualization interface to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://formtek.com/blog/big-data-and-analytics-what-to-expect-in-2017/&#39;&gt;Big Data and Analytics: What to Expect in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Expect to see a big data cloud ecosystem begin to take shape. Apache Spark  An big data open source project now bigger than Hadoop that is also &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zawya.com/mena/en/story/Leveraging_big_data_analytics_in_retail-ZAWYA20161208150026/&#39;&gt;Leveraging big data analytics in retail&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The future of retail also lies in big data analytics. Based on customer loyalty data, browsing patterns, social media, purchase history and demographic &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ibamag.com/us/news/breaking-news/big-data-can-provide-personalized-insurance-kpmg-41601.aspx&#39;&gt;Big data can provide personalized insurance: KPMG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data can provide personalized insurance: KPMG Data analytics is about customization when it comes to insurance = something brokers can take &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://pointofsale.com/PointofSale.com-Blog/Thanx-Secures-$17.1M-Series-B-to-Bring-Big-Data-to-Retail-Merchants.html&#39;&gt;Thanx Secures $17.1M Series B to Bring Big Data to Retail Merchants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO, Dec. 8, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Thanx, which empowers merchants to grow their business through deeper customer loyalty, today &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/earlysense-to-present-at-pcha-connected-health-conference-605427446.html&#39;&gt;EarlySense to Present at PCHA Connected Health Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Liat Tsoref to Discuss Use of Big Data Analytics in Identifying Health &amp;hellip; Her session, Identifying patterns in seniors&amp;rsquo; health with big data analytics, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://feedstuffs.com/story-big-data-ag-continues-expand-45-150340&#39;&gt;Big data in ag continues to expand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Texas A&amp;amp;M AgriLife currently has more than 40 scientists involved in a UAV project that is Texas A&amp;amp;M AgriLife currently has more than 40 scientists &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.co.uk/news-releases/big-data-is-already-providing-commercial-benefits-to-pharma-companies-says-gbi-research-605452576.html&#39;&gt;Big Data is Already Providing Commercial Benefits to Pharma Companies, Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire UK (press release) Big Data simply refers to any data set which is too large to store, process or analyze using traditional database software and hardware. As technology &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/big-data-and-data-analytics-in-homeland-security-and-public-safety-is-forecast-to-reach-11b-in-2022-according-to-a-new-research-report-from-homeland-security-research-corp/&#39;&gt;Big Data and Data Analytics in Homeland Security and Public Safety is&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) Homeland Security Research Corp. forecasts that the Big Data and Data &amp;hellip; Big Data and Data Analytics technologies can increase the investigative &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/357218451/gridgain-selected-as-a-2016-red-herring-top-100-global-company&#39;&gt;GridGain Selected as a 2016 Red Herring Top 100 Global Company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In the era of big data and analytics, we have created a high performance solution &amp;ndash; and &amp;hellip; GridGain is a trademark or registered trademark of GridGain Systems, Inc. Apache, Apache Hadoop, Hadoop, Apache Ignite, and Ignite are &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/marymeehan/2016/12/08/where-data-goes-to-die-big-data-still-holds-answers-but-theyre-not-where-youre-looking-for-them/&#39;&gt;Where Data Goes To Die. Big Data Still Holds Answers, But They&amp;rsquo;re Not Where&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forbes The attention data crunching has gotten from media and pundits would make anyone think that big data is the big answer  until, of course, it isn&amp;rsquo;t. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsweek.com/big-data-financial-markets-now-getting-fintech-treatment-529629&#39;&gt;Big Data in Financial Markets Is Now Getting the &amp;lsquo;Fintech&amp;rsquo; Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within the silos of incumbent financial services, so-called fintech companies are good at picking off one thing only and doing it well. This approach is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.internethealthmanagement.com/2016/12/08/digital-health-investors-see-money-pouring-big-data/&#39;&gt;Digital health investors see more money pouring into big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a session short on talk of actual dollars, but investor money will keep flowing into digital healthcareunder certain conditions. That&amp;rsquo;s the group &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blog.executivebiz.com/2016/12/netcomm-part-of-atarc-federal-big-data-test-lab-louise-white-comments/&#39;&gt;NetComm Part of ATARC Federal Big Data Test Lab; Louise White Comments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;big-data Cloud-based data analytics provider NetComm has signed up for the Advanced Technology Academic Research Center&amp;rsquo;s Federal Big Data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://nationalacademies.org/hmd/reports/2016/big-data-and-analytics-for-infectious-disease-research-operations-and-policy-proceedings-of-a-workshop.aspx&#39;&gt;Big Data and Analytics for Infectious Disease Research, Operations, and&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the amount of data in the world exploding, big data could generate significant value in the field of infectious disease. The Forum on Microbial &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidehpc.com/2016/12/optimizing-for-big-data/&#39;&gt;Optimizing Your Code for Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data applications have the potential to change many aspects of how large systems can be used. With the massive amounts of data being produced &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizjournals.com/kansascity/news/2016/12/08/bayer-animal-health-marketing-big-data-changes.html&#39;&gt;Bayer targets animal health marketing in a world &amp;lsquo;awash in data&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bayer AG uses big data to research new animal health products, but also for targeted marketing. The company, whose Bayer Animal Health unit has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2016-12-08/no-big-data-didn-t-win-the-u-s-election&#39;&gt;No, Big Data Didn&amp;rsquo;t Win the U.S. Election&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messina also held that &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; was an outdated concept and the future of political campaigning depended on what he termed &amp;ldquo;little data&amp;rdquo;: &amp;ldquo;Huge &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://itbrief.co.nz/story/machine-learning-big-disruptor-says-ovum/&#39;&gt;Machine learning: The big disruptor, says Ovum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Machine learning is tipped to be the biggest disruptor for big data analytics in 2017, according &amp;hellip; The cloud will sharpen Hadoop-Spark co-opetition.. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.tableau.com/resource/top-10-big-data-trends-2017&#39;&gt;Top 10 Big Data Trends 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to fulfill the need for analytics on Hadoop. But enterprises with complex, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dbta.com/Editorial/News-Flashes/Bridging-the-Gap-Between-Traditional-and-Big-Data-with-Data-Modeling-115268.aspx&#39;&gt;Bridging the Gap Between Traditional and Big Data with Data Modeling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As more enterprises incorporate new technologies such as Hadoop and NoSQL and new strategies like data lakes to manage fast-growing volumes of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.quickenloans.com/blog/using-big-data-find-clients-real-estate-business&#39;&gt;Using Big Data to Find Clients for Your Real Estate Business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data refers to large amounts of data that have been collected over time, specifically on the internet. Since becoming publicly available in 1991, the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.proactiveinvestors.com.au/companies/news/170210/byte-power-group-to-expand-its-big-data-offering-for-china-170210.html&#39;&gt;Byte Power Group to expand its big data offering for China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Byte Power Group&amp;rsquo;s (ASX:BPG) subsidiary, subsidiary Byte Power (Hong Kong) Ltd, has signed an agreement to set up a &amp;lsquo;big data&amp;rsquo; joint venture with &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.floridatoday.com/story/money/business/2016/12/08/big-tech-news-uses-big-data/95137568/&#39;&gt;The big tech news in 2016 was the uses of Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I logged into Facebook recently I was presented with a video titled Your Year in Review. The message accompanying the video read, Scott, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Cloud Computing News from @cloudfeednet - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Cloud Computing news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#34;&gt;@cloudfeednet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://chromeunboxed.com/epson-printers-coming-back-online-with-google-cloud-print/&#39;&gt;Epson Printers Coming Back Online With Google Cloud Print&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just hours after reporting on an apparent bug affecting Epson printers using Google Cloud Print it appears that users on social channels are reporting &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://tech.economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/corporate/microsoft-is-driving-digital-transformation-of-the-manufacturing-sector-peter-gartenberg/55855898&#39;&gt;Microsoft is driving digital transformation of the manufacturing sector:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ETtech.com This is done by security teams across Microsoft, Windows, Microsoft Azure and Office365. No other cloud provider offers the breadth of trust features &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.infotechlead.com/networking/yahoo-japan-deploys-active-archive-system-ddn-ibm-44305&#39;&gt;Yahoo Japan deploys active archive system by DDN and IBM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new system allows Yahoo Japan to cache dozens of petabytes of data from its OpenStack Swift storage solution in a Japan-based data center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com.au/news/digital-sense-wins-brisbane-council-contract-to-migrate-virtual-machines-443969&#39;&gt;Digital Sense wins Brisbane council contract to migrate virtual machines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The council&amp;rsquo;s IT environment is currently located across two data centres owned by the council and will be migrated to Digital Sense&amp;rsquo;s vCloud Data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/07/slack-partners-google-native-google-drive-support/&#39;&gt;Slack forms partnership with Google for native Drive support&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; main data store for all files uploaded to any of their Slack channels, ensuring that everything that is shared on Slack is backed up on Google Cloud. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ciol.com/slack-partners-google-for-new-google-drive-integrations/&#39;&gt;Slack partners Google for new Google Drive integrations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a bid to become the de facto communications portal in the enterprise workflow, Slack has entered into a strategic partnership with Google Cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Microsofts-Bletchley-blockchain-project-gets-two-new-partners-on-Azure-Marketplace-440410&#39;&gt;Microsofts Bletchley blockchain project gets two new partners on Azure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes In September, it announced the next phase of its support of blockchain on Microsoft Azure with the launch of an early version of the Bletchley v1 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://bnlfinance.com/2016/12/08/why-amazon-is-undervalued-but-amzn-stock-will-struggle-in-2017/&#39;&gt;Why Amazon Is Undervalued, But AMZN Stock Will Struggle In 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe this service and Amazon Go will be an absolute blockbuster, and because of patents, Amazon Web Services, and Amazon.com&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.phoneworld.com.pk/google-team-up-with-slack-to-provide-better-google-cloud-integration/&#39;&gt;Google Teams Up With Slack to Provide Better Google Cloud Integration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slack announced a planned partnership with Google Cloud today. It will be rolled out over the first half of 2017. This partnership will bring a number of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techseen.com/2016/12/08/slack-partnership-google-cloud/&#39;&gt;Google, Slack partner to provide better Google Cloud integration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slack has announced a strategic partnership with Google Cloud this morning, which will bring a number of new features to its collaboration platform for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/241657/google-partners-slack-to-dive-deeper-into-workplace-market&#39;&gt;Google Partners Slack to Dive Deeper into Workplace Market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier, though Google Cloud users could discuss work and share files using the Slack platform, the expanded partnership will give users much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/pattern-energys-amazon-wind-farm-awarded-a-top-plant-award-by-power-magazine-300375094.html&#39;&gt;Pattern Energy&amp;rsquo;s Amazon Wind Farm Awarded a Top Plant Award by POWER&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire (press release) All of the electricity generated by Amazon Wind Farm Fowler Ridge supplies the electric grids that service Amazon Web Services (AWS) datacenters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://mspoweruser.com/microsoft-adds-two-new-blockchain-partners-to-the-azure-marketplace/&#39;&gt;Microsoft adds two new blockchain partners to the Azure Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft yesterday announced that they have added two new partners and solutions to the blockchain ecosystem in the Azure Marketplace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://launchpad.net/picasso&#39;&gt;OpenStack Functions-as-a-Service (Picasso)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;on OpenStack. Details coming soon! &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/cake-accelerize-leverages-amazon-web-services-continue-delivering-advanced-multi-channel-otcqb-aclz-2181828.htm&#39;&gt;CAKE by Accelerize Leverages Amazon Web Services to Continue Delivering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) NEWPORT BEACH, CA&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - Dec 8, 2016) - Accelerize ( OTCQB : ACLZ) ( OTCBB : ACLZ) and its digital marketing software division CAKE, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161208005285/en/Red-Hat-Launches-OpenShift-Dedicated-Google-Cloud&#39;&gt;Red Hat Launches OpenShift Dedicated on Google Cloud Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the availability of OpenShift Dedicated on Google Cloud Platform, users can speed adoption of containers, Kubernetes, and cloud-native &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.redhat.com/en/about/press-releases/red-hat-launches-openshift-dedicated-google-cloud-platform&#39;&gt;Red Hat Launches OpenShift Dedicated on Google Cloud Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;users can speed adoption of containers, Kubernetes, and cloud-native &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/sogeti-usa-announces-details-of-winning-projects-from-the-2016-iot-hackathon-300374857.html&#39;&gt;Sogeti USA Announces Details of Winning Projects from the 2016 IoT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire (press release) The competing teams were allowed to build an IoT application on their choice of platforms, including IBM Watson IoT, Covisint, and Microsoft Azure IoT &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://baseballnewssource.com/markets/amazon-com-inc-amzn-downgraded-by-vetr-inc/273362.html&#39;&gt;Amazon.com Inc. (AMZN) Downgraded by Vetr Inc.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com Inc. logo Vetr cut shares of Amazon.com Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) from a strong-buy rating to a buy rating in a research report released on &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.otcmarkets.com/stock/ACLZ/news?id=146666&#39;&gt;CAKE by Accelerize Leverages Amazon Web Services to Continue Delivering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAKE by Accelerize Leverages Amazon Web Services to Continue Delivering Advanced Multi-channel Digital Marketing Capabilities for Growing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blogs.oracle.com/linux/entry/training_thursdays_learn_about_oracle&#39;&gt;Training Thursdays: Learn about Oracle OpenStack for Oracle Linux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;while allowing you to deploy different configurations and integrate with a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cbronline.com/news/enterprise-it/software/red-hat-openshift-dedicated-google-cloud-platform-container-adoption/&#39;&gt;Red Hat&amp;rsquo;s OpenShift Dedicated to Google Cloud Platform &amp;amp; container adoption&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nan Boden, head of Technology Partners, Google Cloud, said: Customers consistently tell us that they are looking for open solutions that will enable &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/bluedata-delivers-ultimate-flexibility-and-choice-for-big-data-deployments-on-amazon-web-services/&#39;&gt;BlueData Delivers Ultimate Flexibility and Choice for Big Data Deployments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) BlueData EPIC on AWS is generally available now  with planned support for Google Cloud Platform, Microsoft Azure, and other public cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nasdaq.com/article/amazoncom-inc-amzn-stock-is-a-buy-with-or-without-amazon-go-cm718467&#39;&gt;Amazon.com, Inc. (AMZN) Stock Is a Buy With or Without Amazon Go&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The difference now, though, is that its main businesses are more established than ever, from Amazon Web Services to its e-commerce core and even &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcmag.com/news/350179/microsoft-and-linkedin-put-a-ring-on-it&#39;&gt;Microsoft and LinkedIn Put a Ring On It&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nearly six months after Microsoft spent $26.2 billion to buy LinkedIn in the &amp;hellip; imbuing LinkedIn with the cloud infrastructure power of Microsoft Azure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2016/12/internet-of-google-api-change-triggers-epson-printer-revolt/&#39;&gt;Internet of $@!%: Google API change triggers Epson printer revolt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The affected printers all had one thing in commonthey were connected to the Google Cloud Print service. A change in Google&amp;rsquo;s application interface &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.investors.com/news/technology/amazon-set-to-disrupt-retailers-in-apparel-groceries-services/&#39;&gt;Amazon Set To Disrupt Retailers In Apparel, Groceries, Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another positive is Amazon Web Services, which is the leading provider of public cloud services. It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;well positioned to benefit from the continued &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://mspoweruser.com/azure-ad-pass-authentication-seamless-single-sign-now-available-preview/&#39;&gt;Azure AD Pass-Through Authentication and Seamless Single Sign-on now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MSPoweruser Microsoft yesterday announced that Azure AD Pass-Through Authentication and Seamless Single Sign-on are now available in public preview. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://thestack.com/cloud/2016/12/08/red-hat-container-platform-openshift-dedicated-launches-on-google-cloud/&#39;&gt;Red Hat container platform OpenShift Dedicated launches on Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Hat has announced the general availability of OpenShift Dedicated across Google Cloud Platform, bringing the open source container platform as &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.traderplanet.com/news/view/146848/&#39;&gt;Endurance Collaborates with Google to Empower Small Businesses Globally&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trader Planet BURLINGTON, Mass. , Dec. 8, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Endurance International Group (NASDAQ: EIGI) today announced it has worked with Google &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.realwire.com/releases/UKCloud-becomes-first-UK-public-sector-cloud-provider-to-support-OpenStack&#39;&gt;UKCloud becomes first UK public sector cloud provider to support OpenStack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RealWire (press release) UKCloud supports OpenStack in order to help its UK public sector customers comply with government policy stating that open standards must be used &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.gospelherald.com/articles/68654/20161208/aws-re-invent-how-does-amazon-plan-to-revolutionize-2017.htm&#39;&gt;AWS Re:Invent: How Does Amazon Plan to Revolutionize 2017?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Amazon&amp;rsquo;s recently concluded AWS: re:Invent annual conference (AWS stands for Amazon Web Services) held in Las Vegas, the multi-billion &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/project-bletchley-new-blockchain-partners-come-to-azure-marketplace/&#39;&gt;New Blockchain partners come to Azure Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;solutions to the growing blockchain ecosystem in the Azure Marketplace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ciodive.com/news/public-private-hybrid-how-to-optimize-roi-for-the-tiered-business-cloud/431784/&#39;&gt;Public, private, hybrid: How to optimize ROI for the tiered business cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recent developments, such as Google&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Platform announced earlier in 2016, have made the transition to a more robust and customizable &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161208006034/en/Amazon-Web-Services-Cloud-Customers-Data-Centers&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services Cloud Now Available to Customers from Data Centers in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) SEATTLE&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;(NASDAQ:AMZN)  Amazon Web Services, Inc. (AWS), an Amazon.com company, today announced the launch of the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.darkreading.com/endpoint/phishing-services-reap-twice-the-profit-for-attackers/d/d-id/1327673&#39;&gt;Phishing Services Reap Twice The Profit For Attackers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the thing about Amazon Web Services  if a phisher&amp;rsquo;s server gets blocked, they burn it and build another one,&amp;rdquo; he explains. &amp;ldquo;And no one&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://smartstocknews.com/57200-amazoncom-inc-amazon-go-and-improved-international-prime-penetration-to-bolster-growth-over-20-next-year/&#39;&gt;Amazon.com, Inc.: Amazon Go and Improved International Prime Penetration To&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smrt Stck Nws Revenue from Amazon Web Services (AWS) is expected to be up 56% this year and 44% next year. Apparel may be a material vertical of opportunity &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dabcc.com/new-microsoft-azure-training-and-discounted-certifications/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+AllArticles+%28All+DABCC+Virtualization+%2F+Cloud+Computing+Resources+%28Citrix%2C+VMware%2C+and+Microsoft%29%29&#39;&gt;New Microsoft Azure Training and Discounted Certifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you missed the recent news, Microsoft joined the Linux Foundation, further demonstrating our commitment to open source for Azure, and as a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/tech-and-science/technology/epson-printers-perpetually-rebooting-after-google-code-change/article/481293&#39;&gt;Epson printers perpetually rebooting after Google code change&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ars Technica reports it affects Epson&amp;rsquo;s WorkForce, Work Force Pro and XP series of internet-connected smart printers. Owners can use Google&amp;rsquo;s Cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.reuters.com/article/idUSB8N179099&#39;&gt;BRIEF-Amazon Web Services announces launch of AWS Canada (central) region&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON, Dec 8 The U.S. House of Representatives on Thursday overwhelmingly passed legislation to keep federal agencies funded until April &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.com-unik.info/2016/12/08/decatur-capital-management-inc-increases-stake-in-amazon-com-inc-amzn.html&#39;&gt;Decatur Capital Management Inc. Increases Stake in Amazon.com Inc. (AMZN)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com logo Decatur Capital Management Inc. increased its position in Amazon.com Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) by 2.8% during the third quarter, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blogs.vmware.com/vcloud/2016/12/vmware-macquarie-cloud-services-match-made-cloud.html&#39;&gt;VMware and Macquarie Cloud Services  A Match Made in the Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Service Provider on the VMware vCloud Air Network, offers a cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://mspoweruser.com/microsoft-announces-new-cloud-console-azure-portal/&#39;&gt;Microsoft announces the new cloud console for the Azure portal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To fix this problem, Microsoft yesterday announced the new Azure Cloud Console. The new Cloud Console allows users to build their applications on &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://data-economy.com/red-hat-takes-containers-google-cloud-platform/&#39;&gt;Red Hat takes containers into Google Cloud Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;adoption of containers, Kubernetes, and cloud-native application patterns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.geekwire.com/2016/amazon-web-services-expands-first-canadian-region/&#39;&gt;Amazon Web Services expands with its first Canadian region&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services has opened a region in Canada, its first in that country. The Canada (Central) region, located in Montreal, means local AWS &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thecerbatgem.com/2016/12/08/amazon-com-inc-amzn-given-overweight-rating-at-piper-jaffray-cos.html&#39;&gt;Amazon.com Inc. (AMZN) Given Overweight Rating at Piper Jaffray Cos.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com Inc. logo Piper Jaffray Cos. reissued their overweight rating on shares of Amazon.com Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) in a research report sent to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://baseballnewssource.com/markets/amazon-com-inc-amzn-shares-bought-by-highland-capital-management-llc/272329.html&#39;&gt;Amazon.com Inc. (AMZN) Shares Bought by Highland Capital Management LLC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com logo Highland Capital Management LLC increased its position in Amazon.com Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) by 14.3% during the third quarter, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.informationweek.com/partner-perspectives/redhat/the-case-for-openstack-and-ceph-subscriptions-supporting-the-community-in-more-ways-than-one-/a/d-id/1327674&#39;&gt;The Case For OpenStack And Ceph Subscriptions: Supporting The Community In&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;InformationWeek As more of the world moves to build data centers with OpenStack as the core, a comprehensive support program for this environment is crucial. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.rcrwireless.com/20161208/telco-cloud/aws-microsoft-and-salesforce-driving-cloud-market-tag2&#39;&gt;AWS, Microsoft and Salesforce driving cloud market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure IaaS and platform-as-a-service offering, which is viewed as the firm&amp;rsquo;s core cloud platform, is also seen as a growing business that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://moneymorning.com/2016/12/08/8-tech-stocks-to-watch-now/&#39;&gt;8 Tech Stocks to Watch Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has contracts with the PC market, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the only reason &amp;hellip; and has been developing a profitable cloud business (Microsoft Azure). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.enterprisetech.com/2016/12/08/google-red-hat-extend-kubernetes/&#39;&gt;Google, Red Hat Partner to Extend Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8) a &amp;ldquo;dedicated&amp;rdquo; version of its OpenShift container platform is available on Google&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Platform (NASDAQ: GOOGL). The partners said the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.mirantis.com/blog/scaling-openstack-shared-nothing-architecture/&#39;&gt;Scaling OpenStack With a Shared-Nothing Architecture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;removing single points of contention. Learn about the pros and cons of this &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dabcc.com/setting-up-azure-ad-pass-trough-authentication-with-azure-ad-connect/&#39;&gt;Setting up Azure AD Pass-trough authentication with Azure AD Connect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So today Microsoft released a public preview of Pass-trough authentication Azure AD which allows for SSO against Azure Active Directory without the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/endurance-collaborates-with-google-to-empower-small-businesses-globally-with-professional-intelligent-apps-from-g-suite-300375401.html&#39;&gt;Endurance Collaborates with Google to Empower Small Businesses Globally&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire (press release) This venture extends Google Cloud&amp;rsquo;s G Suite apps availability to small businesses through sub-resellers around the world. Customers are now able to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://developers.google.com/actions/develop/sdk/getting-started&#39;&gt;Getting Started with the Actions SDK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go to the Google Cloud Console projects page. Select a project if you already &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://adtmag.com/articles/2016/12/08/aws-lambda-csharp.aspx&#39;&gt;Amazon Cloud Adds C# Support to Lambda Service&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services Inc. (AWS) announced that its AWS Lambda tool &amp;ndash; providing serverless functionality for projects such as app back-end services &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lightreading.com/enterprise-cloud/-microsoft-closes-linkedin-acquisition-whats-next/d/d-id/728879&#39;&gt;Microsoft Closes LinkedIn Acquisition. What&amp;rsquo;s Next?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Office (winner: Microsoft) and Microsoft Azure vs. Google Cloud (winner: Microsoft has a commanding lead but Google is investing for a long &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financial-news.co.uk/38627/2016/12/azul-zulu-enterprise-deployed-internally-at-microsoft-f/&#39;&gt;Azul Zulu Enterprise deployed internally at Microsoft for Key Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FinancialNews.co.uk (blog) Azul Systems Zulu Enterprise 100% open source Java platform based on OpenJDK has been deployed by Microsofts Azure team as the Java &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3148671/cloud-computing/red-hat-brings-openshift-to-google-cloud-platform.html&#39;&gt;Red Hat brings OpenShift to Google Cloud Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Hat OpenShift Dedicated is already available on AWS, and its arrival on Google Cloud Platform (GCP) leaves only one major cloud infrastructure &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lightreading.com/enterprise-cloud/-microsoft-closes-linkedin-acquisition-whats-next/d/d-id/728879&#39;&gt;Microsoft Closes LinkedIn Acquisition. What&amp;rsquo;s Next?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud (winner: Microsoft has a commanding lead but Google is investing for a long fight). With the LinkedIn acquisition, Microsoft is taking a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.seattletimes.com/business/amazon/2000-stores-amazon-knocks-down-report-of-retail-plans/&#39;&gt;2000 stores? Amazon knocks down report of retail plans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s what it did with Amazon Web Services, which rents out computing power and storage to other companies, many of them fierce retail rivals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.insideindianabusiness.com/story/34010492/benton-county-wind-farm-earns-industry-award&#39;&gt;Benton County Wind Farm Earns Industry Award&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chief Executive Officer Mike Garland says the facility was the first investment in a wind farm by Amazon Web Services. He adds the company is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.mirantis.com/blog/bailian-goes-brick-mortar-brick-click-using-openstack-devops/&#39;&gt;Bailian: From Brick &amp;amp; Mortar to Brick &amp;amp; Click using OpenStack, DevOps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;retail by using OpenStack and DevOps for increased agility, efficient &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.eweek.com/video/windows-10-creators-updates-includes-new-security-features.html&#39;&gt;Microsoft Fortifies Windows 10 Creators Update With Security Features&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DAILY VIDEO: Microsoft bolsters security features in windows 10 creators &amp;hellip; DAILY VIDEO: Microsoft Azure flaw posed RHEL hacking risk; Google &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/sqlreleaseservices/released-public-preview-for-microsoft-azure-sql-database-management-pack-6-7-11-0/&#39;&gt;Released: Public Preview for Microsoft Azure SQL Database Management Pack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Database. Your feedback on this public preview will improve the quality &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://technical.ly/delaware/2016/12/08/congressional-app-challenge-winner-announced/&#39;&gt;A Newark eighth grader just won Delaware&amp;rsquo;s Congressional App Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Updated: A previous version of this article reported that Rohan Kanchana would win $50,000 in Amazon Web Services credits when, in fact, Kanchana &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/Azure/New-Microsoft-Azure-training-and-discounted-certifications/m-p/34529&#39;&gt;New Microsoft Azure training and discounted certif&amp;hellip;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top Cloud Myths of 2016 blog post, the use of cloud technology has become &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.zdnet.com/article/red-hat-launches-openshift-on-google-cloud/&#39;&gt;Red Hat launches OpenShift on Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Red Hat is expanding its OpenShift Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) cloud to the Google Cloud Platform. This move comes days after Red Hat completed &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily IoT/Blockchain news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/europe-internet-of-things-market-forecast-2016-2023-300374823.html&#39;&gt;Europe Internet Of Things Market Forecast 2016-2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The global Internet of Things market is poised to grow in 2017-2023. Various reasons for growth of the Internet of things market are growing Internet &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3148484/networking/bluetooth-5-is-out-now-will-home-iot-take-off.html&#39;&gt;Bluetooth 5 is out: Now will home IoT take off?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bluetooth is aiming straight for the internet of things as the fifth version of the wireless protocol arrives with twice as much speed for low-power &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/08/klarm-china-promotes-5-axis-machining-services/&#39;&gt;Klarm China Promotes 5 Axis Machining Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is advantageous in the event of power outages, as well as when moving the magnetic pallet from machine to machine. The use of magnetic &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3168628&#39;&gt;Block Chain +, Puyin Group contributes to the financial development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Block chain finance is actually the application of block chain technology in the financial field. Block chain is a Bitcoin-based underlying technology, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.datamation.com/applications/iot-and-ai-adoption-outpace-vr-at-businesses.html&#39;&gt;IoT and AI Adoption Outpace VR at Businesses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Businesses are likelier to embrace the Internet of Things and artificial intelligence before buying virtual reality headsets and 3d printers, finds a new &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesskorea.co.kr/english/news/money/16703-blackchain-movement-blockchain-consortium-launched-south-korea&#39;&gt;Blockchain Consortium Launched in South Korea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NH Investment &amp;amp; Securities managing director Park Sun-moo and Daily Intelligence CEO Lee Kyung-joon signed an MOU at a blockchain consortium &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161207006430/en/UNH-IOL-Shines-Spotlight-Internet-Interoperability&#39;&gt;UNH-IOL Shines Spotlight on Internet of Things Interoperability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DURHAM, N.H.&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;The University of New Hampshire InterOperability Laboratory (UNH-IOL), an independent provider of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://ibsintelligence.com/ibs-journal/ibs-news/cme-ventures-exec-joins-us-blockchain-group/&#39;&gt;CME Ventures exec joins US blockchain group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last month, CME Group announced plans with Britain&amp;rsquo;s Royal Mint to launch a blockchain-based digital platform for trading gold. Further info here. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cioreview.com/news/internet-of-things-world-event-on-may-16-18-2017-at-santa-clara-convention-center-ca-nid-23483-cid-133.html&#39;&gt;Internet of Things World Event on May 16 - 18, 2017 at Santa Clara&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CIOReview FREMONT, CA: Internet of Things World event is scheduled on May 16-18, 2017, Santa Clara Convention Center, CA. Internet of Things World 2017 is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ciol.com/unity-hires-ubers-machine-learning-head-to-add-to-its-ai-prowess/&#39;&gt;Unity hires Uber&amp;rsquo;s machine learning head to add to its AI prowess&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just after a year as Uber&amp;rsquo;s head of machine learning, Dr. Danny Lange is now joining game engine startup Unity to head its AI and machine learning &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Blockchain-platform-Stellar-goes-global-partners-with-Coinsph-Flutterwave-ICICI-Bank-and-Tempo-438031&#39;&gt;Blockchain platform Stellar goes global partners with Coinsph Flutterwave&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes It is built on blockchain technology and enables people to send remittances across international borders at lower prices via proprietary digital money, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Referral-Foundation-explores-blockchain-for-referral-marketing-industry-440356&#39;&gt;Referral Foundation explores blockchain for referral marketing industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company&amp;rsquo;s mission to upgrade the industry with the help of blockchain provides early insights into the adoption of digital currency and its impact &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://shipandbunker.com/news/emea/812962-port-of-hamburg-partners-on-internet-of-things-emissions-monitoring-pilot-project&#39;&gt;Port of Hamburg Partners on Internet of Things Emissions Monitoring Pilot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ship &amp;amp; Bunker Kii Inc. (Kii) has announced its collaboration with the Hamburg Port Authority (HPA) on an Internet of Things (IoT) pilot project, which was launched by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Digital-Asset-solves-confidentiality-issue-with-new-blockchain-platform-440459&#39;&gt;Digital Asset solves confidentiality issue with new blockchain platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital Asset Holdings, a blockchain startup headquartered in New York, has developed a platform that will enable traders to use blockchain &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/patimes/interview-mit-prof-dr-wil-van-der-aalst-eindhoven-university-technology/8288/&#39;&gt;Interview mit Prof. Dr. Wil van der Aalst, Eindhoven University of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Predictive Analytics Times The Internet of Things (IoT): all physical objects connected to the network. The IoT includes all things that have a unique id and a presence in an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Microsofts-Bletchley-blockchain-project-gets-two-new-partners-on-Azure-Marketplace-440410&#39;&gt;Microsofts Bletchley blockchain project gets two new partners on Azure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes In September, it announced the next phase of its support of blockchain on Microsoft Azure with the launch of an early version of the Bletchley v1 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-in/blog/project-bletchley-new-blockchain-partners-come-to-azure-marketplace/&#39;&gt;New Blockchain partners come to Azure Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;solutions to the growing blockchain ecosystem in the Azure Marketplace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.sourcingfocus.com/site/newsitem/gearing_up_for_the_internet_of_things/&#39;&gt;Gearing up for the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An article in the latest issue of the Economist focuses upon the transition of Siemens and General Electric to the Internet of Things and how both firms &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.greenbiz.com/article/why-ibm-sees-blockchain-breakthrough-traceability&#39;&gt;Why IBM sees blockchain as a breakthrough for traceability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both are the subject of innovative supply chain traceability experiments using an emerging software system called &amp;ldquo;the blockchain.&amp;rdquo; Another common &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.siliconrepublic.com/machines/us-borders-donald-trump-iot-dhs&#39;&gt;IoT a &amp;lsquo;game-changer&amp;rsquo; for securing US borders under Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps there is another way, using millions of sensors along the 3,000km-plus US southern border as part of the internet of things (IoT). While likely &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.elektormagazine.com/news/my-journey-in-the-cloud-a-small-senor-board&#39;&gt;My Journey into the Cloud (13): a small sensor board&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the commands in the rudimentary MQTT library functions I could almost use their &amp;hellip; The results can be checked with an MQTT client of your choice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cbronline.com/news/mobility/networks/bt-huawei-team-5g-network-trials/&#39;&gt;BT and Huawei team up for 5G network trials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will cover network architecture, radio frequency, network resource allocation, machine-to-machine communications and security. The research &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.realwire.com/releases/open-source-foundations-and-projects-use-oneM2M-standards&#39;&gt;Boost for IoT interoperability as open source foundations and projects use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RealWire (press release) Sophia Antipolis, France, 8 December 2016. oneM2M, the global standards partnership for Machine-to-Machine (M2M) communications and the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.arabianbusiness.com/darkmatter-throws-its-weight-behind-ieee-world-forum-on-internet-of-things-conference-655767.html&#39;&gt;DarkMatter throws its weight behind IEEE World Forum on Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ArabianBusiness.com SPONSORED CONTENT: DarkMatter&amp;rsquo;s Dr. David Kravitz to share a keynote presentation on Blockchain  Compatible Identity &amp;amp; Access Management &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Coinbase-Coin-Center-USV-and-Consensys-prepare-Blockchain-Token-Securities-Law-Framework-440587&#39;&gt;Coinbase Coin Center USV and Consensys prepare Blockchain Token Securities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes A digital token created on a blockchain is called a blockchain token (or App Coin), which may function as a digital currency (such as bitcoin) or &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Blockchain-makes-it-to-Virgin-Medias-Disruptor-10-companies-440740&#39;&gt;Blockchain makes it to Virgin Media&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Disruptor 10&amp;rsquo; companies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Virgin Media Business has announced &amp;lsquo;Disruptor 10&amp;rsquo;, where ten companies including Blockchain, the digital currency wallet, are recognized for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theinternetofthings.eu/ashissh-raichura-mesh-networks-could-end-blues-bluetooth&#39;&gt;Ashissh Raichura: Mesh Networks could end the Blues for Bluetooth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;though, a dash of smartness may transform the way we use the technology. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.telecompaper.com/news/bt-huawei-to-pioneer-new-5g-technologies--1175372&#39;&gt;BT, Huawei to pioneer new 5G technologies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; will allow operators to apportion network resources to specific services; machine-to-machine communications in Internet of Things (IoT) applications, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/south-korea-sees-first-blockchain-consortium/&#39;&gt;South Korea Sees its First Blockchain Consortium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A group of 21 financial investment companies and five blockchain technology firms have signed a memorandum-of-understanding (MoU) to develop &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.arabianbusiness.com/darkmatter-throws-its-weight-behind-ieee-world-forum-on-internet-of-things-conference-655767.html&#39;&gt;DarkMatter throws its weight behind IEEE World Forum on Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ArabianBusiness.com DarkMatter, an international cyber security firm headquartered in the UAE, announces its presence at the IEEE World Forum on Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lightreading.com/iot/m2m-platforms/orange-flags-barriers-to-licensed-spectrum-lora/d/d-id/728836&#39;&gt;Orange Flags Barriers to Licensed-Spectrum LoRa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using unlicensed spectrum, the operator has been deploying a LoRa network in France as part of its Internet of Things (IoT) strategy. LoRa is one of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.capacitymedia.com/Article/3645490/News/BT-teams-with-Huawei-for-5G-research-agreement.html&#39;&gt;BT teams with Huawei for 5G research agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BT said it will look at elements including network architecture; network slicing; machine-to-machine communications in Internet of Things applications; &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://coinjournal.net/new-blockchain-consortium-launched-south-korea/&#39;&gt;New Blockchain Consortium Launched In South Korea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Korea Financial Investment Association, along with 21 financial investments and five blockchain companies, have signed an memorandum of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cointelegraph.com/news/hashcoin-uses-emercoin-blockchain-for-vehicle-registration-and-tracking&#39;&gt;HashCoin Uses Emercoin Blockchain For Vehicle Registration And Tracking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HashCoin states that it has created a vehicle certification system using the Emer Blockchain, something which appeals to manufacturers and countries &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.home.barclays/news/2016/12/binary-future--how-blockchain-is-transforming-banking.html&#39;&gt;Binary future: how blockchain is transforming banking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;blockchain  and the opportunities that lie ahead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nojitter.com/post/240172182/ai-systems-the-brains-behind-the-bots&#39;&gt;AI Systems: The Brains Behind the Bots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a tremendous synergy between artificial intelligence and speech recognition technology and the Internet of Things, but at AI World such &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.sap.com/solution/internet-of-things.html&#39;&gt;What is the Internet of Things?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet, including smart phones and tablets and almost anything with a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theinternetofthings.eu/william-gibson-future-privacy&#39;&gt;William Gibson: The Future of Privacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;together in a satisfying way, though it continues to seem that I should. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://due.com/blog/frontier-blockchain-adoption-will-bitcoin-circa-2010/&#39;&gt;The Frontier of Blockchain Adoption will be&amp;hellip; Bitcoin Circa 2010&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but in reality most adoptions will make little use of it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.insidecounsel.com/2016/12/08/3-key-cybersecurity-concerns-for-department-operat&#39;&gt;3 Key Cybersecurity Concerns for Department Operations Staff&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IoT, as it is known, is in a high-growth phase: According to the Cisco Visual Networking Index, global &amp;ldquo;machine to machine&amp;rdquo; connections will grow 250 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.kentuckypostnews.com/2016/12/08/short-interest-change-iridium-communications-incorporated-nasdaqirdm-on-focus-after-report-of-less-shorts/&#39;&gt;Short Interest Change: Iridium Communications Incorporated (NASDAQ:IRDM) on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post News The Company&amp;rsquo;s lines of business include land mobile, machine to machine, maritime, aviation and government. Insitutional Activity: The institutional &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2016-12-08/what-happened-to-the-financial-blockchain-revolution&#39;&gt;What Happened to the Financial Blockchain Revolution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was a lot of optimism that the blockchain &amp;ndash; the technology underlying Bitcoin &amp;ndash; would help the finance industry deal with a big &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://coinjournal.net/circle-pivots-away-bitcoin-blockchain-doubles-digital-currency/&#39;&gt;While Circle Pivots Away from Bitcoin, Blockchain Doubles Down on the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoinJournal (blog) While Circle has continued their pivot away from bitcoin, Blockchain is doubling down on the digital currency. CoinJournal reached out to Blockchain &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://allcoinsnews.com/2016/12/08/blockchain-technology-coming-to-referral-marketing-industry/&#39;&gt;Blockchain Technology Coming to Referral Marketing Industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;London-based cryptocurrency start-up, Referral Foundation is introducing cryptocurrency and blockchain technology to the referral marketing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pymnts.com/news/b2b-payments/2016/stellar-blockchain-distributed-ledger-financial-institution-bank-partnership-cross-border-money-transfer-payments/&#39;&gt;Stellar Taps New Partners For Global Payments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain startup Stellar has inked new collaborations with financial institutions to explore the company&amp;rsquo;s distributed ledger platform for international &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.brit.co/the-internet-of-things-is-already-changing-your-home/&#39;&gt;The Internet of Things Is Already Changing Your Home&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these objects are collectively known as the Internet of Things (IoT). It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty broad topic and can be a little confusing, so we&amp;rsquo;re here to break it &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.scientific-computing.com/news/ni-partners-ibm-and-sparkcognition-advance-industrial-internet-things-iiot&#39;&gt;NI partners with IBM and SparkCognition to advance the Industrial Internet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientific Computing World NI, IBM and SparkCognition have announced a collaboration to increase the efficiency of industrial machinery using a combination of Industrial &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2016/12/08/us_commission_cybersecurity_recommendations/&#39;&gt;US commission whistles to FIDO: Help end ID-based hacks by 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; includes the development of open-source standards and specifications like those developed by the Fast IDentity Online (FIDO) Alliance, it said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.deccanchronicle.com/technology/in-other-news/081216/ricoh-unveils-powerful-printing-as-a-service-platform-paas.html&#39;&gt;Ricoh unveils powerful printing as a service platform (PaaS)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, they are equipped with M2M (Machine to machine communication), which communicates with the Ricoh PaaS Platform to inform when the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pymnts.com/blockchain/2016/blockchain-tracker-getting-into-the-real-estate-business/&#39;&gt;Blockchain Tracker: Getting Into The Real Estate Business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain technology has made its name in the banking sector but has also found its way into the health care world, the music industry and even the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.paymentssource.com/news/deloitte-makes-first-blockchain-investment-in-setl&#39;&gt;Deloitte makes first blockchain investment in SETL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deloitte has invested an undisclosed amount in SETL, a blockchain company focused on providing post-trade settlement solutions in financial &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2016/12/internet-of-google-api-change-triggers-epson-printer-revolt/&#39;&gt;Internet of $@!%: Google API change triggers Epson printer revolt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the Epson problem is also illustrative of the problems inherent in &amp;ldquo;Internet of Things&amp;rdquo; (IoT) devices that are dependent on Internet services to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161208005756/en/CompuCom-Establishes-Global-Headquarters-Lancaster-County-South&#39;&gt;CompuCom Establishes New Global Headquarters in Lancaster County, South&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) Leveraging CompuCom&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things (IoT) solutions, the new headquarters office is being designed as a leading &amp;ldquo;smart building&amp;rdquo; in South &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://search.cpan.org/~krenzke/Net-MQTT-Simple-Auth-0.001/&#39;&gt;Net-MQTT-Simple-Auth-0.001&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Latest Release, Net-MQTT-Simple-Auth-0.002, [Download] [Browse] &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nasdaq.com/article/how-blockchain-technology-is-improving-food-supply-chains-cm718710&#39;&gt;How Blockchain Technology Is Improving Food Supply Chains&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to look at how the food industry deals with supply chain issues, and how companies are turning to blockchain technology to try to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-age.com/will-internet-things-take-businesses-2017-123463532/&#39;&gt;Where will the Internet of Things take businesses in 2017?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason being is that the Internet of Things is a really broad term that actually refers to the full network of IoT devices  not the devices themselves. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/lte-5g-power-hyper-connected-173000317.html&#39;&gt;LTE and 5G to Power Hyper-Connected Internet of Everything&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The term Internet of Things (or Everything) has been coined to describe the vision of an interconnected network of physical objects that interact with &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/lte-5g-power-hyper-connected-173000317.html&#39;&gt;LTE and 5G to Power Hyper-Connected Internet of Everything&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In light of the fact that GSM is the most deployed cellular technology and that 2G Machine-to-Machine (M2M) connections account for the majority of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nasdaq.com/article/distributed-markets-event-to-convene-blockchain-payments-finservices-innovators-in-atlanta-cm718790&#39;&gt;Distributed: Markets Event to Convene Blockchain Payments, FinServices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nasdaq In the midst of white hot global competition for blockchain innovation and investment, the capital of financial services and fintech innovation in the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://security.itbusinessnet.com/article/IBM-Debuts-Blockchain-Ecosystem-To-Help-Accelerate-Growth-of-Networks-on-Hyperledger-Fabric-4728063&#39;&gt;IBM Debuts Blockchain Ecosystem To Help Accelerate Growth of Networks on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT Business Net ARMONK, N.Y., Dec. 7, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Blockchain has the potential to transform the way industries conduct business transactions. This will &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2016/12/maker-of-internet-of-things-connected-vibrator-will-settle-privacy-suit/&#39;&gt;Maker of Internet of Things-connected vibrator will settle privacy suit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few months back we reported on the collision of the Internet of Things and sex toys. The maker of an Internet-connected, remote-controlled vibrator &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.thomasnet.com/fullstory/p-series-plc-on-chip-features-sd-card-and-display-interface-40001064&#39;&gt;P-Series PLC on Chip features SD card and display interface.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Applications include remote response monitoring, rental equipment, field testing, proactive machine maintenance, machine to machine control, data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/12/08/referral-foundation-to-revolutionise-referral-marketing-industry-with-blockchain-tech/&#39;&gt;Referral Foundation to Revolutionise Referral Marketing Industry with&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;newsBTC The London-based cryptocurrency group aims to educate the referral marketing industry about the potential of digital currency and blockchain &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/beyond-bitcoin-circle-pivots-to-next-gen-blockchain-enabled-social-payments-1481223358&#39;&gt;Beyond Bitcoin: Circle Pivots to Next-Gen Blockchain-Enabled Social&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Magazine The Wall Street Journal posted a story on December 7, 2017 titled Bitcoin Powerhouse Will Pull the Plug on Bitcoin. In fact, bitcoin bank Circle &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.sci-tech-today.com/story.xhtml?story_id=020002348HTW&#39;&gt;Next-Gen Bluetooth Is Here: Faster and Key for Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First introduced by the Swedish telecom giant Ericsson more than 20 years ago, the wireless technology standard Bluetooth will soon enable faster &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.insidecounsel.com/2016/12/08/3-key-cybersecurity-concerns-for-department-operat&#39;&gt;3 Key Cybersecurity Concerns for Department Operations Staff&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things is the internetworking of physical (often everyday) devices that collect and share data. Automobiles that communicate oil &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/darkmatter-throws-its-weight-behind-ieee-world-forum-on-internet-of-things-conference-605450166.html&#39;&gt;DarkMatter Throws its Weight Behind IEEE World Forum on Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Newswire (press release) Dr. David Kravitz, DarkMatter&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Crypto Research Systems, is set to deliver a keynote address on Blockchain - Compatible Identity &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iotevolutionworld.com/iot/articles/427891-fixed-monthly-gsm-charge-introduced-vessel-tracking-system.htm&#39;&gt;Fixed Monthly GSM Charge Introduced for Vessel Tracking System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new monthly subscription covers all vessel tracking and M2M (Machine-to-Machine) data transmitted over GSM networks by the RockFLEET &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/metropolis-ethereum-blockchain-attacks-look-forward/&#39;&gt;Toward Metropolis: After Blockchain Repairs, Ethereum Looks Ahead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following efforts to make the blockchain-based distributed application network more resistant to attacks, two planned hard forks and one unintentional &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cuinsight.com/3-ways-blockchain-reducing-uncertainty.html&#39;&gt;3 ways blockchain is reducing uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a recent TED Talk, Bettina Warburg, Blockchain entrepreneur and researcher, describes exactly what we should be expecting from the upcoming &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio-today.com/article/index.php?story_id=020000N6REBO&#39;&gt;Next-Gen Bluetooth Is Here: Faster and Key for Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft is pushing to put more goodies into the personal computer, detailing plans for a new slate of Windows-powered virtual reality headsets and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/briansolis/2016/12/08/the-rise-of-innovation-empires-companies-set-out-to-defeat-the-new-kodak-moment/&#39;&gt;The Rise Of Innovation Empires: Companies Set Out To Defeat The New &amp;lsquo;Kodak&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forbes There was a time when the words, Kodak moment meant something powerful and nostalgic. They were the epitome of a brand and the relationship &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.ibm.com/think/marketing/how-the-internet-of-things-can-make-home-a-lifelong-connection/&#39;&gt;How the Internet of Things can make home a lifelong connection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;they&amp;rsquo;d be able to stay in their home as long as they could. At the time, I. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.eweek.com/database/slideshows/10-things-to-know-about-ibms-blockchain-ecosystem.html&#39;&gt;IBM Launches Blockchain Ecosystem to Enlist Innovative Enterprises&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IBM has introduced a new online ecosystem to encourage enterprises to develop innovative business applications for blockchain database &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blogs.cisco.com/zzfeatured/pursue-real-iot-solutions-not-big-white-whales&#39;&gt;Pursue Real IoT Solutions, not Big White Whales&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But that is not necessarily the path to success. I&amp;rsquo;m a believer in the Internet of Things (IoT) as the driver of transformational change across industries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://conversations.e-flux.com/t/trevor-paglen-on-the-new-regime-of-invisible-images/5623&#39;&gt;Trevor Paglen on the new regime of invisible images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advent of machine-to-machine seeing has been barely noticed at large, and poorly understood by those of us who&amp;rsquo;ve begun to notice the tectonic &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ukmarketnews.co.uk/2016/12/08/tessco-technologies-incorporated-nasdaqtess-under-analyst-spotlight/&#39;&gt;TESSCO Technologies Incorporated (NASDAQ:TESS) Under Analyst Spotlight&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; operating, maintaining and reselling cellular, mobile communications, wireless-fidelity (Wi-Fi), machine-to-machine, Internet of Things and wireless &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blockgeeks.com/blockchain-vs-fiat-a-confrontation-of-ages/&#39;&gt;Blockchain vs Fiat: A Confrontation of Ages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;blockchain money is any better than fiat. Blockchain vs Fiat: A Confrontation of Ages. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.maritime-executive.com/article/danes-test-onboard-internet-of-things&#39;&gt;Danes Test Onboard Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next year, a number of Danish organizations will be running a pilot Internet of Things project to test the collection of real-time data from equipment &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.csoonline.com/article/3148806/internet-of-things/the-iot-gateway-for-enterprise-hackers.html&#39;&gt;The IoT: Gateway for enterprise hackers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A very merry Christmas could give way to a not-so-happy New Year security hangover for enterprises, once a few million more Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theinternetofthings.eu/ahmed-el-adl-emergence-cognitive-digital-physical-twins-cdpt-21st-century-icons-and-beacons&#39;&gt;Ahmed El Adl: The Emergence of Cognitive Digital Physical Twins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;overall concept of Cognitive Digital Twins (CDT) as the foundation for the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.informationsecuritybuzz.com/articles/digital-identity-broken-can-fix/&#39;&gt;Digital Identity Is Broken. Can We Fix It?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While we have all been enjoying a life online, an awkward truth threatens to wreck everything. It is this: a password is the same irrespective of who &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/Blockchain-event-for-payments-and-financial-services-innovators-Distributed-Markets-to-be-held-in-February-2017-440689&#39;&gt;Blockchain event for payments and financial services innovators Distributed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes It will provide an opportunity to the participants to form the relationships needed to move financial services and blockchain forward together. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://telecomreseller.com/2016/12/08/carrier-network-virtualization-at-risk-from-the-internet-of-things-lack-of-security-at-endpoints/&#39;&gt;Carrier Network Virtualization at risk from the Internet of Things lack of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Telecom Reseller (press release) Carrier Network Virtualization at risk from the Internet of Things lack of &amp;hellip; Now with the addition of the Internet of Things, more vulnerabilities exist for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/0/bluetooth-5-need-know-new-wireless-technology/&#39;&gt;Bluetooth 5: What you need to know about the new wireless technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; technology by the industry body Bluetooth SIG, is expected to boost the creation of wireless connected gadgets, part of the internet of things. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/book-of-orbs-wallet-promotes-true-ownership-of-in-game-assets-on-the-blockchain-1481235165&#39;&gt;Book of Orbs Wallet Promotes True Ownership of In-Game Assets on the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Magazine Book of Orbs, which is available on Android and iOS, permits players to collect, send, receive and trade blockchain assets known as ORBs (Ownership &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.medgadget.com/2016/12/rising-preference-for-communication-devices-to-increase-use-internet-of-things-iot-in-healthcare-sector.html&#39;&gt;Rising Preference For Communication Devices To Increase Use Internet Of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medgadget (blog) MrrBiz74 Recently MarketResearchReports.biz has added the report &amp;lsquo;Global Internet Of Things Market In The Healthcare Sector 2016-2020&amp;rsquo; to its &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.computerworld.com/article/3148767/internet-of-things/blackberry-unveils-blackberry-secure-for-enterprise-iot-mobile-security.html&#39;&gt;BlackBerry unveils BlackBerry Secure for enterprise IoT mobile security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BlackBerry on Thursday unveiled a comprehensive mobile-security platform for a wide variety of Internet of Things devices connected to enterprises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://icrunchdata.com/blockchain-startup-says-platform-allows-confidential-trading/&#39;&gt;Blockchain Startup Says Its Platform Allows Confidential Trading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reuters  Digital Asset Holdings, a blockchain startup backed by some of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest banks, said on Wednesday it had developed a platform to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcworld.idg.com.au/article/611372/how-internet-things-putting-us-risk/&#39;&gt;How the Internet of Things is putting us at risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have all heard the reports about baby monitors being hacked, smart cars being taken over and CCTV systems being compromised. But on Friday &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://investorplace.com/2016/12/bluetooth-5/&#39;&gt;Bluetooth 5: Everything You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It also expects that one third of the estimated 48 billion Internet of Things devices that will be installed by 2021 will include Bluetooth technology. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mobile Computing News from @topmobilenews - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-mobile-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Mobile Computing news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topmobilenews&#34;&gt;@topmobilenews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.whatech.com/market-research/it/235835-detailed-examination-of-the-north-american-that-is-expected-to-contribute-the-maximum-share-in-the-mobile-device-management-mdm-market&#39;&gt;Detailed examination of the North American that is expected to contribute&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WhaTech The Mobile Device Management (MDM) market is estimated to grow from USD 1.69 Billion in 2016 to USD 5.32 Billion by 2021, at a Compound &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/qualcomm-collaborates-microsoft-support-windows-030000316.html&#39;&gt;Qualcomm Collaborates with Microsoft to Support Windows 10 Computing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Finance &amp;ldquo;Qualcomm Snapdragon processors offer one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced mobile computing features, including Gigabit LTE connectivity, advanced &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-12-08/microsoft-unveils-windows-10-for-qualcomm-chips-a-blow-to-intel-iwfrztwm&#39;&gt;Microsoft Unveils Windows 10 for Qualcomm Chips, a Blow to Intel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;s dominance in PCs and help the software maker gain a bigger foothold in mobile computing. Chips from Qualcomm, the largest maker of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scmagazineuk.com/is-byod-your-companys-norm-beware-the-ghosts-of-data-past-this-christmas/article/577378/&#39;&gt;Is BYOD your company&amp;rsquo;s norm? Beware the ghosts of data past this Christmas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the run up to Christmas, many employees will have their eyes on a new mobile device or tablet. Richard Stiennon asks, &amp;ldquo;is your organisation taking &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itwire.com/mobility/76105-windows-10-%E2%80%9Ccomputer-in-your-pocket%E2%80%9D-soon.html&#39;&gt;Windows 10 computer in your pocket soon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; and President, QCT, said, &amp;ldquo;Qualcomm Snapdragon processors offer one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced mobile computing features, including Gigabit &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://venturebeat.com/2016/12/07/qualcomms-snapdragon-processors-will-support-windows-10/&#39;&gt;Future Windows 10 desktops, laptops, and other devices will use Qualcomm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VentureBeat Qualcomm Snapdragon processors offer one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced mobile computing features, including Gigabit LTE connectivity, advanced &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/392783/Mobile-Device-Management-MDM-Market-worth-USD-5-32-Billion-by-2021.html&#39;&gt;Mobile Device Management(MDM) Market worth USD 5.32 Billion by 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The major drivers of this market include increasing smartphone and tablet penetration and strong adoption of BYOD policies, growing security &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/392783/Mobile-Device-Management-MDM-Market-worth-USD-5-32-Billion-by-2021.html&#39;&gt;Mobile Device Management(MDM) Market worth USD 5.32 Billion by 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report &amp;ldquo;Mobile Device Management Market by Solution (Device Management, Application Management, Security Management, and Network &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.desotoedge.com/stocks/new-analyst-ratings-for-alternative-networks-lonan-4/208851&#39;&gt;New Analyst Ratings For Alternative Networks (LON:AN)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A number of investment brokers have recently updated their price targets on shares of Alternative Networks (LON:AN). According to the latest broker &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cbronline.com/news/mobility/apps/microsoft-windows-10-smartphones-tablets-qualcomm/&#39;&gt;Microsoft plans Windows 10 smartphones, tablets with Qualcomm tie-up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft and mobile chipmaker Qualcomm have partnered to create a version of Windows 10 which will run on mobile computing devices powered by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://wsbreakingnews.com/volatile-movements-qualcomm-nasdaqqcom-american-express-company-nyseaxp/5255469/&#39;&gt;Volatile Movements - QUALCOMM, (NASDAQ:QCOM), American Express Company,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Financial Breaking News Qualcomm Snapdragon processors offer one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced mobile computing features, counting Gigabit LTE connectivity, advanced &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/08/mobile-device-managementmdm-market-worth-usd-5-32-billion-by-2021/&#39;&gt;Mobile Device Management(MDM) Market worth USD 5.32 Billion by 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report Mobile Device Management Market by Solution (Device Management, Application Management, Security Management, and Network &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prweb.com/releases/2016/12/prweb13907874.htm&#39;&gt;Intermezzo, Inc. and Blackwrist Interactive, LLC Partner for Comprehensive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PR Web (press release) In addition to the core functionalities provided in guest kiosks, there are several innovative features including mobile device management of casino &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://windowsreport.com/windows-10-creators-update-byod-security/&#39;&gt;Windows 10 Creators Update to get new BYOD and security features&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s commonly known as the Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy. Under BYOD, companies allow employees to bring their personal devices to the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/davealtavilla/2016/12/08/microsofts-latest-gamer-changer-windows-10-on-qualcomm-snapdragon-processors-with-full-x86-apps/&#39;&gt;Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Latest Gamer-Changer: Windows 10 Runs On Qualcomm Snapdragon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forbes &amp;hellip; the company may have just blown the lid off the entire mobile computing sector. Last night at WinHEC 2016, Microsoft unveiled that Windows 10 and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sl.com/byod-bring-data-sandbox/&#39;&gt;BYOD - Bring Your Own Data to the RTView Sandbox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monitor. After you&amp;rsquo;ve explored our demo environment, you can bring in your &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.trefis.com/stock/intc/articles/390648/opportunity-for-qualcomm-could-be-a-setback-for-intel/2016-12-08&#39;&gt;Opportunity For Qualcomm Could Be A Setback For Intel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; that it is collaborating with Qualcomm to enable Windows 10 on mobile computing platforms that will be based on Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s Snapdragon chipset. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcmag.com/news/350190/blackberry-secure-wants-to-be-fort-knox-for-your-companys&#39;&gt;&amp;lsquo;BlackBerry Secure&amp;rsquo; Wants to Be Fort Knox for Your Company&amp;rsquo;s Mobile Devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; and WatchDox, a file transfer serviceoffers BlackBerry clients an enterprise mobility management and mobile device management (MDM) suite &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.techcentral.ie/enterprise-mobility-business-issue/&#39;&gt;Enterprise mobility is a business issue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conaty said that most mobile device management (MDM) vendors had some tool set for this utilising digital rights management (DRM), but again, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financialbuzz.com/microsoft-brings-windows-10-to-mobile-devices-637750&#39;&gt;Microsoft Brings Windows 10 to Mobile Devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced mobile computing features, including Gigabit LTE connectivity, advanced multimedia support, machine learning and superior &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scoop.co.nz/stories/BU1612/S00381/out-of-date-websites-costing-new-zealand-businesses.htm&#39;&gt;Out of date websites costing New Zealand businesses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These mobile apps, by their very nature, are designed to be responsive and their popularity only goes to prove just how popular mobile computing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Security News from @trustpath - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-trust-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-trust-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Security news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/trustpath&#34;&gt;@trustpath&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://blog.executivebiz.com/2016/12/endgame-lands-air-force-contract-to-provide-cyber-threat-detection-tool/&#39;&gt;Endgame Lands Air Force Contract to Provide Cyber Threat Detection Tool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The company initially fielded its endpoint detection and response tool to the military branch&amp;rsquo;s cyber protection teams under a sole-source contract &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.irishtimes.com/business/technology/government-continues-data-sharing-projects-despite-eu-ruling-1.2896362&#39;&gt;Government continues data-sharing projects despite EU ruling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; is a growing and ever-present threat, with some studies suggesting health data breaches take up to twice as long to detect and also that health data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.tripwire.com/state-of-security/security-data-protection/75-percent-orgs-cant-effectively-detect-respond-data-breaches-reveals-survey/&#39;&gt;75 Percent of Orgs Can&amp;rsquo;t Effectively Detect and Respond to Data Breaches,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The right security solutions can help companies detect and respond to data breaches. But not every organization can afford or leverage those &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://businesswireindia.com/news/news-details/2017-cybersecurity-predictions-by-vishal-gupta-co-founder-ceo-seclore/51272&#39;&gt;2017 Cybersecurity Predictions by Vishal Gupta, Co-founder and CEO, Seclore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These will be two imperative shifts in the fight against the litany of unceasing data breaches. As hackers are taking a more targeted approach by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/china-state-sponsored-hackers-stole-data-major-us-law-firms-waves-data-breaches-report-1595455&#39;&gt;Chinese state-sponsored hackers breached major US law firms and stole data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;International Business Times UK The data breaches are believed to have occurred at the height of the US-China cybersecurity tensions, following the high-profile OPM cyberattack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businessrevieweurope.eu/technology/1182/How-can-European-businesses-prevent-cyber-attacks&#39;&gt;How can European businesses prevent cyber attacks?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The need for cyber security is increasingly apparent for European businesses. Cyber-attacks, ranging from targeted viruses to personal data breaches, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scmagazineuk.com/only-25-of-businesses-can-effectively-detect-and-respond-to-data-breaches/article/577739/&#39;&gt;Only 25% of businesses can effectively detect and respond to data breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; IT budgets, many organisations still lack the resources, visibility and threat intelligence needed to rapidly and accurately respond to data breaches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mondaq.com/canada/x/550936/data+protection/7+Ways+to+Help+Your+Organization+Prevent+Costly+Data+Breaches&#39;&gt;7 Ways to Help Your Organization Prevent Costly Data Breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Businesses spend an estimated $84 billion each year defending their data against cyber-attacks. However, a recent report by Accenture (the &amp;ldquo;Report&amp;rdquo;) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thyssenkrupp-cyber-idUSKBN13X0VW&#39;&gt;ThyssenKrupp secrets stolen in &amp;lsquo;massive&amp;rsquo; cyber attack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Globally, cyber attacks on banks, retailers and other businesses have led to widespread consumer data breaches and mounting financial losses in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://abovethelaw.com/2016/12/morning-docket-12-08-16/&#39;&gt;Above The Law In your inbox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several Biglaw firms  including Cravath and Weil Gotshal  were hit by data breaches over the course of last year, and it&amp;rsquo;s now been confirmed that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/jdl-technologies-fasttrack-proves-security-can-be-easy-and-effective-300375097.html&#39;&gt;JDL Technologies FastTrack Proves Security Can be Easy and Effective&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although victims of ransomware are often reluctant to report incidents, in 2016 businesses reported 157 data breaches affecting more than half a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dclsearch.com/only-25-of-businesses-can-effectively-detect-and-respond-to-data-breaches-it-security-news/&#39;&gt;Only 25% of Businesses Can Effectively Detect and Respond to Data Breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as well prepared as they think they are for a data breach. Tripwire has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-age.com/7-ways-cyber-attacks-will-evolve-2017-123463538/&#39;&gt;7 ways cyber attacks will evolve in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Network attacks and resulting data breaches in the headlines generally involve the loss of personally identifiable information (PII), healthcare and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.information-age.com/5-key-steps-businesses-need-take-following-security-breach-123463540/&#39;&gt;5 key steps businesses need to take following a security breach&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These days, data breaches are an all too common occurrence. Barely a week goes by without another high-profile attack taking place. With increasing &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digitaljournal.com/pr/3169636&#39;&gt;BFSI Security Market Adopts Innovation to Stay Competitive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Physical security information management is a software that act as a standalone platform that integrate multiple unconnected security application and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://betanews.com/2016/12/08/missing-basic-precautions-breaches/&#39;&gt;Companies miss basic precautions that could prevent data breaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public awareness of data security issues has never been higher. Not only have data breaches made the news but the FBI&amp;rsquo;s battle with Apple has put &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://readwrite.com/2016/12/08/data-protection-disputes-set-surge-next-five-years-dl4/&#39;&gt;Data protection disputes set to surge in the next five years&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With incidents of data breaches and other data protection issues on the rise, researchers are looking into just how much we can expect data protection &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/08/ivalue-partners-exabeam-to-address-surging-security-analytics-space/&#39;&gt;iValue Partners Exabeam to Address Surging Security Analytics Space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; behavior intelligence to unlock the potential of existing security information and event management (SIEM) and log management data repositories, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/data-theft-at-thyssenkrupp-highlights-industrial-espionage-threat/d/d-id/1327675&#39;&gt;Data Theft At ThyssenKrupp Highlights Industrial Espionage Threat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In recent years, data breaches involving theft of financial and personal information have outnumbered cyber incidents involving theft of intellectual &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.networksasia.net/article/cios-believe-their-employees-are-their-biggest-security-risk.1481232445&#39;&gt;CIOs believe their employees are their biggest security risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To combat the ongoing threat posed by BYOD, nearly all (97 per cent) of CIOs are taking action to protect their company from potential data breaches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Venture/Startup News from @topventurenews - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-venture-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Venture/Startup news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topventurenews&#34;&gt;@topventurenews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://news.fiu.edu/2016/12/venture-capitalists-check-out-startup-fiu-companies/106986&#39;&gt;Venture capitalists check out StartUP FIU companies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kathari and others from Athenian Venture Partners, MIT Enterprise Forum of South Florida, Florida Angel Nexus Fund, Urban Us and Keiretsu Forum &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techcircle.vccircle.com/2016/12/08/this-vc-is-backing-one-tech-startup-a-month-transportation-iot-ventures-under-advantedges-radar/&#39;&gt;This VC is backing one tech startup a month; transportation, IoT ventures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VCCircle This VC is backing one tech startup a month; transportation, IoT ventures &amp;hellip; We don&amp;rsquo;t expect significantly large startups to get funded but this number &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.networkworld.com/article/3147739/open-source-tools/apache-zeppelin-open-source-analytics-startup-reveals-new-name-fresh-funding.html&#39;&gt;Apache Zeppelin open-source analytics startup reveals new name, fresh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Network World ZEPL is among a slew of open-source oriented startups attracting venture funding this year. Other recent ones include Heptio (Kubernetes container &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://tech.co/startup-consolidation-low-vc-funds-2016-12&#39;&gt;Startup Consolidation Is a Clear Sign of Low VC Funds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a year ago, venture capital funding was more than plentiful. Startups from all walks of life budded like flowers in the spring, making way for an &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.builtinchicago.org/2016/12/08/tech-roundup&#39;&gt;Tech roundup: Swap.com raises $20M, Hyde Park Ventures co-founder launches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built In Chicago Tech roundup: Swap.com raises $20M, Hyde Park Ventures co-founder &amp;hellip; a planned $30 million venture fund to back financial technology startups. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Big Data News from @topdatanews - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-data-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Big Data news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/topdatanews&#34;&gt;@topdatanews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/16/12/p8779047/etiyas-serdoo-uses-ai-to-automate-customer-service-management&#39;&gt;Etiya&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Serdoo&amp;rsquo; uses AI to automate customer service management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Etiya, the leading independent software vendor providing telco CRM, catalog-driven BSS/OSS, social CRM and big data analytics, announced the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.ship-technology.com/features/featureusing-big-data-to-combat-illegal-fishing-5688984/&#39;&gt;Using big data to combat illegal fishing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The international community is desperately trying to crack down on illegal fishing and is increasingly harnessing the power of big data to achieve this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://software.intel.com/en-us/forums/intel-visual-fortran-compiler-for-windows/topic/704683&#39;&gt;subroutine in ABAQUS read big data file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;some data file and then pass is to the other subroutine &amp;lsquo;DLOAD&amp;rsquo;. The data I am &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.brighttalk.com/webcast/13073/232839?utm_medium=web&amp;utm_source=brighttalk-portal&amp;utm_campaign=all-brighttalk-upcoming&#39;&gt;Shining light on Hadoop: Wellcentive Cuts Troubleshooting from Months to&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wellcentive, a SaaS health management and data analytics company, relies on a nightly Mapreduce job to process and analyze data for their entire &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://itbrief.co.nz/story/cloudera-hadoop-changing-role-data-business/&#39;&gt;Cloudera, Hadoop and the changing role of data in business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hadoop is an eco-system of big data technologies with a very scalable database at its heart. The technology came out of Yahoo around a decade ago. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://koreabizwire.com/military-uses-big-data-for-disease-control-and-prevention/71669&#39;&gt;Military Uses Big Data for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7 (Korea Bizwire)  The Ministry of Defense is teaming up with the Ministry of Science, ICT and Future Planning for a big data research project that will &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://cds.cern.ch/journal/CERNBulletin/2016/21/Announcements/2151923?ln=zh_TW&#39;&gt;Summer School - 27 June - 6 July 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;July 2016. IBD4Health explores advanced topics related to big data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.shanghaidaily.com/opinion/The-Global-Search-for-Education-Would-Small-Data-Mean-Big-Change/shdaily.shtml&#39;&gt;The Global Search for Education: Would Small Data Mean Big Change?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must be mindful of potential drawbacks of big data, especially those related to data privacy and research ethics. When big data is used to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.shanghaidaily.com/metro/health-and-science/Science-authority-signs-agreement-with-leading-publisher-to-develop-big-data-database-for-talents-experts/shdaily.shtml&#39;&gt;Science authority signs agreement with leading publisher to develop big&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shanghai Daily (subscription) THE city&amp;rsquo;s science authority signed cooperation agreement with the world&amp;rsquo;s largest publisher for science, technology and medicine in the city today in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://qz.com/819245/data-scientist-cathy-oneil-on-the-cold-destructiveness-of-big-data/&#39;&gt;Data scientist Cathy O&amp;rsquo;Neil on the cold destructiveness of big data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data promises fairness. With enough information about individuals and populations, we can design algorithms that will identify the best possible &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/183273/hadoop-market-analysis-size-trends-share-report-and-forecast-to-2022&#39;&gt;Hadoop Market Analysis, Size, Trends, Share, Report and Forecast to 2022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Stratistics MRC, the global hadoop market is expected to grow at a &amp;hellip; demand for big data analytics are the factors influencing the market growth. &amp;hellip; North America has the largest regional market for Hadoop led by the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scotsman.com/business/companies/tech/steve-ross-big-data-still-needs-the-human-touch-1-4311195&#39;&gt;Steve Ross: Big data still needs the human touch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big data analytics failed to recognise &amp;lsquo;fake&amp;rsquo; news during the race for the White House. Picture: Ty Wright/Getty Images &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://postandparcel.info/76938/news/using-big-data-to-cut-shipping-costs/&#39;&gt;Using Big Data to cut shipping costs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers from Belgium&amp;rsquo;s Vlerick Business School have developed a Big Data analytics tool which they say will help companies substantially &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/data-science-pioneer-drew-conway-closes-25m-seed-funding-bring-machine-learning-industrial-2181338.htm&#39;&gt;Data Science Pioneer Drew Conway Closes $2.5M in Seed Funding to Bring&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) Alluvium aims to conquer one of big data&amp;rsquo;s greatest unsolved challenges for complex industrial operations with expert human operators. Alluvium&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://diginomica.com/2016/12/07/panning-right-data-gold-big-data-torrent/&#39;&gt;Panning for &amp;lsquo;right data&amp;rsquo; gold in the Big Data torrent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all know what &amp;lsquo;Big Data&amp;rsquo; means  data sets that are so large or complex, they can&amp;rsquo;t be managed with traditional data processing applications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.darkdaily.com/hoping-to-become-heavyweights-in-healthcare-big-data-ibm-watson-health-teams-up-with-siemens-radiology-and-in-vitro-diagnostics-businesses-1207&#39;&gt;Hoping to Become Heavyweights in Healthcare Big Data, IBM Watson Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DARKDaily.com - Laboratory News Big data has the potential to deliver unprecedented insight into optimizing the patient care experience and managing outcomes for healthcare &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2016/12/07/895829/0/en/JUST-Capital-and-GoodData-Announce-Partnership-to-Create-a-Big-Data-Platform-that-Supports-Corporate-Engagement-and-Their-Investor-Related-Products.html&#39;&gt;JUST Capital and GoodData Announce Partnership to Create a Big Data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GlobeNewswire (press release) JUST Capital partners with GoodData to create the foundation and single source of truth to identify JUST companies. With multiple disparate data &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/celonis-launches-the-first-enterprise-class-big-data-analytics-process-mining-platform-powered-by-artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning/&#39;&gt;Celonis Launches the First Enterprise-Class, Big Data Analytics Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) NEW YORK(BUSINESS WIRE)Celonis today announced it has launched the industry&amp;rsquo;s first enterprise-class, big data analytics process mining &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cbronline.com/news/big-data/analytics/big-data-making-cios-smarter/&#39;&gt;Is Big Data making CIOs smarter?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big Data  the &amp;lsquo;new oil&amp;rsquo;  is fast becoming a key role in business decision making. The key, however, is how to turn that data into intelligent information &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3967572&#39;&gt;Celonis Launches the First Enterprise-Class, Big Data Analytics Process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SYS-CON Media (press release) Celonis today announced it has launched the industry&amp;rsquo;s first enterprise-class, big data analytics process mining platform fueled by artificial intelligence &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.psu.edu/story/440879/2016/12/07/research/big-data-approach-water-quality-applied-shale-drilling-sites&#39;&gt;Big data approach to water quality applied at shale drilling sites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UNIVERSITY PARK, Pa.  A computer program is diving deep into water quality data from Pennsylvania, helping scientists detect potential &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/357032650/hadoop-market-2016-share-trend-segmentation-and-forecast-to-2022&#39;&gt;Hadoop Market 2016 Share, Trend, Segmentation and Forecast to 2022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;global hadoop market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 53.7% over the forecast &amp;hellip; demand for big data analytics are the factors influencing the market growth. &amp;hellip; North America has the largest regional market for Hadoop led by the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsmaker.com.au/news/183504/big-data-as-a-service-2016-market-segmentationapplicationtechnology-market-analysis-research-report-to-2020&#39;&gt;Big data as a Service 2016 Market Segmentation,Application,Technology &amp;amp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsMaker (press release) This market research report presents a detailed segmentation of the global big data as a service market by application (HaaS, analytics as a service, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://rezidenciaseverka.sk/679-papers-data-pdf-analysis-big-research&#39;&gt;Big data analysis research papers pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;expensive? Split your payment apart - Big data analysis research papers pdf. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cio.com/article/3147855/security/how-to-secure-big-data-environments-with-identity-management-and-auditing.html&#39;&gt;How to Secure Big Data Environments with Identity Management and Auditing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many organizations are deploying Hadoop to help launch their big data projects. Unfortunately, Hadoop runs in non-secure mode by default, which &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sdtimes.com/hewlett-packard-enterprise-enriches-hpe-idol-machine-learning-engine-natural-language-processing/&#39;&gt;Hewlett Packard Enterprise enriches HPE IDOL machine learning engine with&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the biggest challenges facing organizations trying to leverage Big Data is providing answers to users&amp;rsquo; questions in a natural, effective manner &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/07/hpes-big-data-solutions-add-machine-learning-natural-language-mix-hpediscover/&#39;&gt;HPE&amp;rsquo;s big data solutions add machine learning and natural language into the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SiliconANGLE (blog) Veis also discussed HPE big data solutions, including Vertica, which &amp;hellip; they get the performance of a Vertica front end with the economy of Hadoop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://dzone.com/articles/random-forest-as-a-regressor-a-spark-based-solutio&#39;&gt;Random Forest as a Regressor: A Spark-based Solution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consequently, it&amp;rsquo;s a perfect algorithm for making predictive analytics on Big Data. It can handle thousands of input features and variables at a time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.aiadc.org/media-center/all-news-releases/2016/december/aia-to-advocate-for-a-balanced-approach-to-big-data-at-naic-2016-fall-meeting&#39;&gt;AIA to Advocate for a Balanced Approach to Big Data at NAIC 2016 Fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learn more about AIA to Advocate for a Balanced Approach to Big Data at NAIC 2016 Fall Meeting at aiadc.org. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-12/ps-bda120716.php&#39;&gt;Big data approach to water quality applied at shale drilling sites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, sifting through big data is labor intensive, and complex patterns that might reveal potential problems can be difficult for humans to spot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thoughtworks.com/insights/blog/will-big-data-make-me-designosaur&#39;&gt;Will Big Data Make me a Designosaur?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;age and Big Data is automating many of the utilities in our lives. The potential of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://phys.org/news/2016-12-big-approach-quality-shale-drilling.html&#39;&gt;Big data approach to water quality applied at shale drilling sites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A computer program is diving deep into water quality data from Pennsylvania, helping scientists detect potential environmental impacts of Marcellus &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://prwire.com.au/pr/64662/queensland-brain-institute-overhauls-big-data-environment-to-advance-brain-research&#39;&gt;Queensland Brain Institute Overhauls Big Data Environment To Advance Brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PRWire (press release) As one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest dedicated facilities focused on understanding how the brain works and finding ways to prevent diseases, the Queensland &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.moneymanagement.com.au/news/financial-planning/big-data-will-boost-regulatory-monitoring&#39;&gt;Big data will boost regulatory monitoring&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advent of big data tools and the ability to access data will enable regulators of the banking and financial services sector to identify and respond to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.benzinga.com/pressreleases/16/12/p8784139/aia-to-advocate-for-a-balanced-approach-to-big-data-at-naic-2016-fall-m&#39;&gt;AIA to Advocate for a Balanced Approach to Big Data at NAIC 2016 Fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Benzinga The Big Data (D) Working Group will discuss its charges and work stream for 2017. &amp;ldquo;For next year, we would encourage Working Group members to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.msn.com/en-us/money/taxes/big-data-makes-more-out-of-less-in-aerospace/vp-AAlhJPg&#39;&gt;Big data makes more out of less in aerospace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kant talk about the value that start-ups can add in the aerospace sector. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Cloud Computing News from @cloudfeednet - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-cloud-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily Cloud Computing news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/cloudfeednet&#34;&gt;@cloudfeednet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bangkokpost.com/tech/local-news/1153473/aws-makes-play-through-new-services&#39;&gt;AWS makes play through new services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services Inc (AWS), the world&amp;rsquo;s largest cloud service provider, is betting on its new wave of cloud services to capitalise on the emerging &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://insidehpc.com/2016/12/ddn-and-ibm-japan-team-to-deliver-yahoo-japan-a-50-tb-per-day-inter-continental-active-archive-solution-that-offers-lower-cost-rapid-data-access-in-japan-and-u-s/&#39;&gt;DDN and IBM Team on 50 TB per Day, Inter-Continental Active Archive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;insideHPC JAPAN to cache dozens of petabytes of data from its OpenStack Swift storage solution in a Japan-based data center, and transfer data to a U.S.-based &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cso.com.au/mediareleases/28709/tibco-releases-tibco-mashery-local-api-management/&#39;&gt;TIBCO Releases TIBCO Mashery Local API Management Solution for Hybrid&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CSO Australia Mashery Local can be deployed to any cloud environment that supports Docker containers, such as Amazon Web Services, Kubernetes or &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cso.com.au/mediareleases/28709/tibco-releases-tibco-mashery-local-api-management/&#39;&gt;TIBCO Releases TIBCO Mashery Local API Management Solution for Hybrid&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CSO Australia Microsoft and Azure are either registered trademarks or trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries. All other &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.runasradio.com/default.aspx?ShowNum=509&#39;&gt;Microsoft Azure Networking with Albert Greenberg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;working with Microsoft products. The full range of IT topics is covered from a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://enakai00.hatenablog.com/entry/2016/12/07/122030&#39;&gt;Using Cloud Vision API and Cloud Translation API from Google App Engine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;translation. from google.cloud import vision, translate def get_labels(bucket, filename, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://openstack.cioreview.com/cxoinsight/standardizing-maintaining-and-scaling-openstack-adoption-nid-18269-cid-120.html&#39;&gt;Standardizing, Maintaining, and Scaling OpenStack adoption&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As more and more enterprises move to the cloud, many companies are looking to OpenStack to reduce data center costs and increase technology &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://security.itbusinessnet.com/article/21Vianet-Blue-Cloud-Launches-GigaCloud-Service-in-the-Chinese-Market-for-Secure-Document-and-Email-Collaboration-4724948&#39;&gt;21Vianet Blue Cloud Launches GigaCloud Service in the Chinese Market for&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT Business Net Blue Cloud is the first domestic cloud service provider to launch Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure and Office 365 in China. GigaCloud is Blue Cloud&amp;rsquo;s latest security &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.top500.org/news/amazon-adds-fpga-instance-to-public-cloud/&#39;&gt;Amazon Adds FPGA Instance to Public Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a blog post published last week, Amazon Web Services Chief Evangelist Jeff Barr announced a new Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instance, known &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2016/12/07/epson_printers_in_reset_loops/&#39;&gt;Firmware freakout sends Epson Wi-Fi printers into reset loop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Epson Wi-Fi-connected printers are repeatedly crashing due to what looks like a combination of a firmware update gone wrong and Google Cloud &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.reuters.com/article/idUSASN0004FX&#39;&gt;BRIEF-Alma Media selects Cybercom as its Amazon Web Services partner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BRIEF-Alma Media selects Cybercom as its Amazon Web Services partner. Dec 7 Alma Media Oyj : * Alma Media has selected Cybercom as its &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cybercom.com/About-Cybercom/Press-Media/Press-releases/alma-media-has-selected-cybercom-as-its-amazon-web-services-aws-partner/&#39;&gt;Alma Media has selected Cybercom as its Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as the maintenance solution for its cloud platform. The agreement is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://microsoft.cioreview.com/cxoinsight/azure-machine-learning-for-predictive-and-analytical-work-nid-23482-cid-50.html&#39;&gt;Azure Machine Learning for Predictive and Analytical Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As it turns out, it does quite a lot, and as it stands, all these notions are brought together by Microsoft Azure. Read on to find out how. There exists a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.arabianbusiness.com/amazon-unit-says-launch-bahrain-office-in-january-655563.html&#39;&gt;Amazon unit says to launch Bahrain office in January&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services (AWS) said the office will open on January 1 in Manama and will support organisations of all sizes, from start-ups to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://github.com/kubernetes/kubernetes/issues/38274&#39;&gt;kubernetes-controller-manager container crashes when cloud-provider is&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;kubernetes, openstack, cloud-config, loadbalancer. Is this a BUG &amp;hellip; The k8s cluster is not running inside openstack/devstack. One node runs k8s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.pcmag.com/news/350133/google-cloud-print-is-turning-off-epson-printers&#39;&gt;Google Cloud Print is Turning off Epson Printers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clearly this is a problem caused by Google Cloud Print. So far, there is no fix, however, Epson support provided the following instructions as posted by &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://mspoweruser.com/microsoft-releases-new-azure-training-courses-free/&#39;&gt;Microsoft releases new Azure training courses for free&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft yesterday announced the free Azure training courses available in a self-paced, interactive online learning environment, as well as the option &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.channelemea.com/spip.php?article38822&#39;&gt;Vuzion and Union Solutions announce partnership&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; Solutions have partnered to deliver infrastructure management, data protection and site disaster recovery using the Microsoft Azure public cloud. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lightreading.com/nfv/nfv-specs-open-source/nia-tests-reveal-openstack-version-challenges/d/d-id/728784&#39;&gt;NIA Tests Reveal OpenStack Version Challenges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are de facto open source software processes substituting for standards but none of those is currently taking responsibility for OpenStack &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.technewsworld.com/story/84145.html&#39;&gt;How Amazon Could Reshape More Industries in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone who attended the recent Amazon Web Services re:Invent conference &amp;ndash; or watched many sessions online, as I did &amp;ndash; probably is still trying to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.techcentral.ie/smartftp-8-0-2273-0-64-bit/&#39;&gt;A powerful FTP client with many useful features&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SmartFTP is a fast and easy-to-use FTP client that will make quick work of all your file transfer tasks. The program supports regular FTP connections, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.afr.com/technology/up-in-the-cloud-amazons-biggest-earner-is-its-computing-powerhouse-20161205-gt4alu&#39;&gt;Up in the cloud: Amazon&amp;rsquo;s biggest earner is its computing powerhouse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Jeff Bezos founded Amazon its key market was online retail but now Amazon Web Services is the internet giant&amp;rsquo;s star performer. David Ryder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/07/cambridge-semantics-shatters-previous-record-of-loading-and-querying-trillion-triples-by-100x/&#39;&gt;Cambridge Semantics Shatters Previous Record of Loading and Querying&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Satellite PR News (press release) In the LUBM test conducted on the Google Cloud Platform on Oct. 31, 2016, Cambridge Semantics&amp;rsquo; Anzo Graph Query Engine was able to load and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.mfrtech.com/article/azul-announces-zulu-enterprise-deployed-internally-at-microsoft-for-key-cloud-se&#39;&gt;Azul Announces Zulu Enterprise Deployed Internally at Microsoft for Key&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MFRTech (press release) SUNNYVALE, Calif.&amp;ndash;Azul Systems (Azul), the award-winning leader in Java runtime solutions, today announced that Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure team has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://security.itbusinessnet.com/article/ClearDATA-Named-to-Amazon-Web-Services-Public-Sector-Partner-Program-4726160&#39;&gt;ClearDATA Named to Amazon Web Services Public Sector Partner Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AUSTIN, Texas, Dec. 6, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash;ClearDATA, a secure healthcare cloud platform and managed services company, has been selected to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161207005241/en/Avnet-Introduces-Partner-Programs-Avnet-Cloud-Marketplace&#39;&gt;Avnet Introduces New Partner Programs for the Avnet Cloud Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avnet AWS CloudFront Reseller Program: Designed to build strategic partnerships with key Avnet Amazon Web Services (AWS) partners who enable &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/quora/2016/12/07/why-is-microsoft-showing-so-much-interest-in-linux/&#39;&gt;Why Is Microsoft Showing So Much Interest In Linux?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft focuses all of its accelerators and sales training on Azure and Office 365. Its sales people lead with these. Customers renewing their &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dbta.com/Editorial/News-Flashes/Dell-Boomi-Releases-Fall-2016-version-of-its-Signature-Platform-115142.aspx&#39;&gt;Dell Boomi Releases Fall 2016 version of its Signature Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; DoubleClick by Google, Intuit QuickBooks 2016, Magento, Marketo, Microsoft Azure SQL Database and SQL Data Warehouse, Microsoft Azure Blob &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cpapracticeadvisor.com/news/12285340/xero-completes-data-migration-onto-amazon-web-services&#39;&gt;Xero Completes Data Migration onto Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xero, a maker of small business cloud accounting software, has completed its transition to Amazon Web Services (AWS), marking one of the largest &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/BlueData-Delivers-Ultimate-Flexibility-and-Choice-for-Big-Data-Deployments-on-Amazon-Web-Services-20161207&#39;&gt;BlueData Delivers Ultimate Flexibility and Choice for Big Data Deployments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World &amp;hellip; (BDaaS) software platform, today announced the general availability of its BlueData EPIC software on Amazon Web Services (AWS). BlueData EPIC &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.broadwayworld.com/bwwgeeks/article/BlueData-Delivers-Ultimate-Flexibility-and-Choice-for-Big-Data-Deployments-on-Amazon-Web-Services-20161207&#39;&gt;BlueData Delivers Ultimate Flexibility and Choice for Big Data Deployments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Broadway World BlueData EPIC on AWS is generally available now with planned support for Google Cloud Platform, Microsoft Azure, and other public cloud services in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.einnews.com/pr_news/356915489/cherwell-asset-management-now-available-in-the-microsoft-azure-marketplace&#39;&gt;Cherwell Asset Management Now Available in the Microsoft Azure Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Cherwell Asset Management provides an enterprise-class IT asset management solution utilizing Microsoft Azure global scale and agility. Cherwell&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cloud.google.com/blog/big-data/2016/12/analyzing-nyc-biking-data-with-google-bigquery&#39;&gt;Analyzing NYC Biking Data with Google BigQuery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;program, Sara uncovers interesting New York City bicycling trends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techseen.com/2016/12/07/agero-amazon-web-services/&#39;&gt;Agero uses Amazon Web Services to revamp driver safety&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discussed on stage at AWS re:Invent and built on the Amazon Web Services (AWS) Cloud, Agero&amp;rsquo;s mobile telematics platform is designed to detect &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://data-economy.com/uks-largest-data-centre-gets-board-microsofts-azure-expressroute/&#39;&gt;UK&amp;rsquo;s largest data centre gets on board Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Azure ExpressRoute&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;available on Microsoft Azure ExpressRoute to ease private connections &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lightreading.com/nfv/nfv-tests-and-trials/2016-nia-eantc-nfv-interoperability-test-report/d/d-id/728802&#39;&gt;2016 NIA-EANTC NFV Interoperability Test Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vendor members have upstreamed test findings to open source projects such as OpenStack, and to standards-developing organizations such as ETSI &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://techcrunch.com/2016/12/07/slack-and-google-announce-partnership-focused-on-better-integrating-their-services/&#39;&gt;Slack and Google announce partnership focused on better integrating their&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TechCrunch Slack announced a strategic partnership with Google Cloud this morning, which will bring a number of new features, including deeper integrations &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/insitecommerce-announces-version-e-commerce-181000198.html&#39;&gt;InsiteCommerce Announces New Version of e-Commerce Platform on Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Finance InsiteCommerce has been a Gold Partner of Microsoft for the last ten years, providing commerce solutions for B2B companies. Azure allows Insite &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.gurufocus.com/news/462432/the-strategy-behind-amazon-web-services-growing-margins&#39;&gt;The Strategy Behind Amazon Web Services&amp;rsquo; Growing Margins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services has been cutting prices whenever it gets a chance. Amazon EC2, its on-demand reserve instances, has gone through 53 price &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://9to5google.com/2016/12/07/google-partners-with-slack-to-provide-better-google-cloud-integration/&#39;&gt;Google partners with Slack to provide better Google Cloud integration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two companies, well aware of this, have decided to team up to offer an even deeper integration of Google Cloud within Slack, so come along after &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blog.google/topics/google-cloud/google-and-slack-deepen-partnership-help-teams-work-better-together/&#39;&gt;Google and Slack deepen partnership to help teams work better together&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;same vision for the future of work: that smart software can bring teams &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://insights.ubuntu.com/2016/12/07/webinar-running-an-enterprise-grade-openstack-without-the-headaches/&#39;&gt;Webinar: Running an enterprise-grade OpenStack without the headaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;highly scalable OpenStack clouds with BootStack on a Supermicro &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itnews.com.au/news/building-the-biggest-database-ever-in-aws-443699&#39;&gt;Building the &amp;lsquo;biggest database ever&amp;rsquo; in AWS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; different from its competitors - like fintech firm Fidelity National Information Services (FIS), which has partnered with Google cloud services for its own &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://satprnews.com/2016/12/06/teradeep-takes-rapid-video-analytics-to-the-cloud-with-amazon-web-services/&#39;&gt;TeraDeep Takes Rapid Video Analytics to the Cloud with Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CAMPBELL, Calif., Dec. 6, 2016 /PRNewswire/  TeraDeep, a developer of accelerated deep learning applications for the cloud and on-premise &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.lightreading.com/services/ott/google-both-best-telco-partner-and-biggest-threat---hr-survey/d/d-id/728815&#39;&gt;Google Both Best Telco Partner &amp;amp; Biggest Threat  HR Survey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; including a potentially game-changing partnership between Amazon Web Services Inc. and AT&amp;amp;T Inc. (NYSE: T) in areas including IoT (the Internet &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-in/blog/new-features-in-azure-application-insights-metrics-explorer/&#39;&gt;New features in Azure Application Insights Metrics Explorer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;several new features that allow more options for visualizing metrics, and simplify &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.techrepublic.com/article/slack-teams-with-google-cloud-adds-docs-preview-drive-bot-and-more/&#39;&gt;Slack teams with Google Cloud, adds Docs preview, Drive Bot, and more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud customers will soon get more functionality from chat platform Slack, as the two companies announced new features and a deeper &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blogs.vmware.com/vcloud/2016/12/journey-public-cloud-reality-based.html&#39;&gt;Journey to the Public Cloud with Reality-Based IT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Systems and Technology (IS&amp;amp;T). Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://rcpmag.com/blogs/scott-bekker/2016/12/microsoft-expands-azure-training.aspx&#39;&gt;Microsoft Expands Azure Training with Free Courses, Testing Discounts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hoping to help narrow a skills gap around its public cloud services for partners and customers, Microsoft on Tuesday rolled out six new and free &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.computerdealernews.com/news/microsoft-offering-free-azure-training-for-partners/51877&#39;&gt;Microsoft offering free Azure training for partners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft is addressing the skills gap that may be preventing partners from diving into the cloud with free Azure training for its partners. In a Dec. 5 blog &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://betakit.com/slack-and-google-to-work-together-on-integrations-through-strategic-partnership/&#39;&gt;Slack and Google to work together on integrations through strategic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BetaKit Slack has announced a strategic partnership with Google Cloud in an effort to facilitate deeper integrations with Google services on its platform. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://siliconangle.com/blog/2016/12/07/wikibon-trip-report-amazon-web-services-reinvent-welcome-aws-2-0/&#39;&gt;Wikibon trip report from Amazon Web Services&amp;rsquo; re:Invent: Welcome to AWS 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the first decade of Amazon Web Services  call it AWS 1.0  Amazon.com Inc. devoted much of its time to proving the cloud could work. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchstorage.techtarget.com/blog/Storage-Soup/SwiftStack-public-Cloud-Sync-starts-with-Amazon-Google&#39;&gt;SwiftStack public Cloud Sync starts with Amazon, Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blandini credited said SwiftStack customers requested additional cloud support beyond Amazon Web Services. Customers buy servers from multiple &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://rcpmag.com/whitepapers/2016/12/arrow-electronics/grow-microsoft-csp-practice-free-end-user-qualified-leads.aspx?tc=page0&#39;&gt;Grow Your Microsoft CSP Practice with FREE End User Qualified Leads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to grow your MSP Practice? Partner with Arrow to build cloud solution expertise needed by almost every business today while &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.techrepublic.com/article/how-to-connect-multiple-google-cloud-accounts-to-grive2/&#39;&gt;How to connect multiple Google cloud accounts to Grive2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; account configured to sync with Grive2; if not, you can follow the steps as outlined in the post, How to sync your Google Cloud on Linux with Grive2. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchstorage.techtarget.com/blog/Storage-Soup/SwiftStack-public-Cloud-Sync-starts-with-Amazon-Google&#39;&gt;SwiftStack public Cloud Sync starts with Amazon, Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other use cases include active archiving, cloud bursting, offsite disaster recovery and cold archiving with Amazon Glacier and Google Cloud Storage &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://access.redhat.com/solutions/2798581&#39;&gt;Red Hat Openstack Platform and Red Hat Ceph Storage compatibility matrix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution Verified - Updated 2016-12-07T22:35:14+00:00 -. English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cbronline.com/news/cloud/aas/google-cloud-slack-integration-collaboration/&#39;&gt;Google Cloud &amp;amp; Slack double down on collaboration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slack and Google Cloud are formalising their partnership in order to provide a more integrated experience for customers. Google Docs and Drive &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bluedata.com/blog/2016/12/now-available-bluedata-epic-on-aws/&#39;&gt;Now Available: BlueData EPIC on Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;availability of BlueData EPIC on Amazon Web Services (AWS). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://searchstorage.techtarget.com/blog/Storage-Soup/SwiftStack-public-Cloud-Sync-starts-with-Amazon-Google&#39;&gt;SwiftStack public Cloud Sync starts with Amazon, Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Object storage provider SwiftStack Inc. has added hybrid cloud synchronization to its OpenStack-based software controller. SwiftStack Cloud Sync &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://mspoweruser.com/microsoft-azure-iot-hub-awarded-9-industry-certifications/&#39;&gt;Microsoft Azure IoT Hub Awarded 9 Industry Certifications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Microsoft today announced that Azure IoT Hub has been awarded several major compliance certifications for the public cloud. Compliance &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.com-unik.info/2016/12/07/amazon-com-inc-amzn-given-outperform-rating-at-cowen-and-company-2.html&#39;&gt;Amazon.com Inc. (AMZN) Given Outperform Rating at Cowen and Company&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com Inc. logo Cowen and Company reaffirmed their outperform rating on shares of Amazon.com Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) in a report published &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//cloudfeed.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Daily IoT/Blockchain news from &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/surgethings&#34;&gt;@surgethings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketingprofs.com/chirp/2016/31228/how-the-internet-revolutionized-offline-retail-infographic&#39;&gt;How the Internet Revolutionized Offline Retail [Infographic]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, in the near future, the Internet of Things (IoT) will result in the merger of the online and offline worlds to give consumers a seamless experience &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://mediasmarts.ca/blog/spies-your-stocking-privacy-smart-toys-internet-things&#39;&gt;Spies in Your Stocking: Privacy, Smart Toys and the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet, is one of the biggest current trends in tech  one research firm &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.itnews.com/article/3147336/internet-of-things/privacy-groups-urge-investigation-of-internet-of-toys.html&#39;&gt;Privacy groups urge investigation of &amp;lsquo;internet of toys&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;data protection for children in the rapidly emerging internet of things,&amp;rdquo; said &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.the-blockchain.com/2016/12/07/rsk-making-bitcoin-blockchain-like-ethereum-2-0/&#39;&gt;RSK: Making the Bitcoin Blockchain More Like Ethereum 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Buterin, the challenge was that Satoshi Nakamoto had designed the bitcoin Blockchain in a way that it could only support currency &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/KPMG-Microsoft-India-partner-to-foster-blockchain-and-other-innovative-technologies-436123&#39;&gt;KPMG Microsoft India partner to foster blockchain and other innovative&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes &amp;ldquo;KPMG in India will also extend its services to the entire spectrum of Microsoft productivity tools, intelligent Cloud, blockchain technology and cyber &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/blockchain---global-market-outlook-2016-2022-300374153.html&#39;&gt;Blockchain - Global Market Outlook (2016-2022)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, Dec. 6, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; According to Stratistics MRC, the Global Blockchain Market accounted for $XX million in 2015 and is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bna.com/blockchain-faces-cost-n73014448131/&#39;&gt;Blockchain Faces Cost Challenges, Fed Paper Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an Oct. 7 speech in Washington, Fed Governor Lael Brainard said that it would be premature to consider a relaxed-rules sandbox for blockchain &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.nasdaq.com/article/blockchain-identity-solutions-the-key-to-irrefutable-data-integrity-cm717382&#39;&gt;Blockchain Identity Solutions: The Key to Irrefutable Data Integrity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it is often a very cumbersome, time-consuming and costly process. Blockchains change all that. Imagine having a level of data integrity that would &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/big-data-and-internet-of-things-conference-tickets-29970675096&#39;&gt;Big Data and Internet of Things Conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet of Things Conference - Tuesday, 7 March 2017 at Adelphi House, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cnet.com/news/kids-talking-toys-iot-internet-of-things-privacy-ftc/&#39;&gt;Kids&amp;rsquo; talking toys accused of sharing their secrets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For many people, the allegations underscore the potential dangers associated with the Internet of Things, the notion of tying any and every thing into &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2016/12/07/big_switch_takes_big_bet_it_can_beat_off_big_attacks/&#39;&gt;Big Switch takes big bet it can beat off big denial of service attacks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; botnet attacks may be volumetric but they&amp;rsquo;re coming from a host of different source IP addresses  all those compromised Internet of Things devices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theonlinecitizen.com/2016/12/07/imda-to-de-register-2g-only-mobile-devices-from-1-january-2017/&#39;&gt;IMDA to de-register 2G-only mobile devices from 1 January 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile Devices can include mobile phones, point-of-sales terminals, machine-to-machine equipment, etc. IMDA said that this is a continuation of the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.openpr.com/news/391744/Intelligent-Energy-Storage-Systems-Internet-of-Things-IoT-Technology-benefitted-the-Energy-Storage-Industry-NextGen-Technological-Advancements-Professional-Survey-Industry-Analysis-2024.html&#39;&gt;Intelligent Energy Storage Systems: Internet of Things (IoT) Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;openPR (press release) Intelligent energy storage systems are a smart network of various energy storage units in a complex that help users enhance their total energy savings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iothub.com.au/news/voice-id-without-sound-now-a-possibility-443896&#39;&gt;Voice ID without sound now a possibility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An Israeli company has developed technology that enables the use of voiceprint verification for biometric authentication without the use of sound. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/06/fintech-stellar-blockchain-stripe-remittances/&#39;&gt;Stripe-Backed Stellar Kicks Off Worldwide Money Transfers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For instance, one partner, Coins.ph, a two-year-old blockchain-based mobile payments startup that caters to the Southeast Asia market, will now allow &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.econotimes.com/IBM-unveils-Blockchain-Ecosystem-to-enable-organizations-collaborate-using-Hyperledger-fabric-437934&#39;&gt;IBM unveils Blockchain Ecosystem to enable organizations collaborate using&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EconoTimes Technology giant IBM has announced that it is building a blockchain ecosystem to boost the growth of networks on the Hyperledger Fabric and IBM &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.huffingtonpost.in/nitin-narkhede/7-ways-in-which-blockchain-can-help-create-a-cashless-economy-af/&#39;&gt;7 Ways In Which Blockchain Can Help Create A Cashless Economy After&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huffington Post India A few months ago, news reports quoted an RBI official saying that the central bank may soon set up a committee to study the use of &amp;ldquo;blockchain&amp;rdquo; &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.oilandgaseurasia.com/en/tech_trend/honeywell-and-sparks-dynamics-collaborate-industrial-internet-things-iiot-solutions&#39;&gt;Honeywell And Sparks Dynamics Collaborate On Industrial Internet Of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oil and Gas Industry Latest News Honeywell and Sparks Dynamics announced they will collaborate to help industrial customers leverage the power of the Industrial Internet of Things &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.computer.org/web/computingnow/archive/interoperability-in-the-internet-of-things-december-2016-introduction&#39;&gt;Interoperability in the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;virtual objects and resources that are equipped with sensing, computing, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://hivedata.com/blog/venturebeat-ibm-goes-all-in-on-blockchain-launches-app-making-ecosystem/&#39;&gt;[VENTUREBEAT] IBM GOES ALL-IN ON BLOCKCHAIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;development of blockchain-based applications for business. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://telecom.economictimes.indiatimes.com/tele-talk/internet-of-things-value-beyond-connecting-billions-of-devices/1982&#39;&gt;Internet of Things: Value beyond connecting billions of devices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet of Things (IoT) presents new opportunities for mobile operators to enable that digital transformation by leveraging their core assets and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.accountingtoday.com/blogs/debits-credits/news/get-ready-for-blockchain-big-impact-80064-1.html&#39;&gt;Get Ready for Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s Big Impact&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accountants need to watch out for the wide-ranging impact of blockchain, a technology popularized by digital currencies such as bitcoin. Blockchain &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.digital.nyc/news/how-election-recounts-could-be-obsolete-using-blockchain&#39;&gt;How election recounts could be obsolete using the blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;could make back-of-house monetary operations more efficient and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.natlawreview.com/article/commission-enhancing-national-cybersecurity-releases-its-report-securing-and-growing&#39;&gt;The Commission on Enhancing National Cybersecurity Releases Its Report on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The National Law Review &amp;hellip; critical infrastructure, cybersecurity research and development, cybersecurity workforce, identity management and authentication, Internet of Things, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/stellar-partners-icici-bank-enables-blockchain-money-transfers-india-africa-philippines/&#39;&gt;Stellar Partners ICICI Bank, Enables Blockchain Money Transfers in India,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CryptoCoinsNews Stellar, the open blockchain platform and non-profit payment protocol has unveiled a slew of new partners including, notably, India&amp;rsquo;s largest private &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.vanillaplus.com/2016/12/07/24120-no-customer-left-behind-supporting-the-unconnected-in-the-internet-of-things-age/&#39;&gt;No customer left behind: Supporting the unconnected in the Internet of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VanillaPlus (press release) (blog) The rise of connected devices has been described by some as the next Industrial Revolution. This new age of connectivity is expected to permeate &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.bizcommunity.com/Article/196/94/154940.html&#39;&gt;Spotlight on IIoT/Industry 4.0 at Africa Automation Fair 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Berg Insight, a dedicated machine-to-machine / IoT market research firm based in Sweden, the installed base of wireless IoT devices in &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.financemagnates.com/cryptocurrency/news/european-and-japanese-central-banks-launch-a-joint-blockchain-study/&#39;&gt;European and Japanese Central Banks Launch a Joint Blockchain Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;European and Japanese Central Banks Launch a Joint Blockchain Study. The international study will explore the possible use of distributed ledger &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dailydot.com/layer8/iot-ransomware-attacks/&#39;&gt;The Frightening Future of IoT Ransomware Attacks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the beginning of the year, several distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks warned of the mounting threat of Internet of Things botnets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.institutionalinvestor.com/article/3645076/banking-and-capital-markets-banking/for-banks-2017-is-shaping-up-to-be-the-year-of-blockchain.html&#39;&gt;For Banks, 2017 Is Shaping Up to Be the Year of Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In November the debate over blockchain&amp;rsquo;s value flared up again when four banks reportedly left R3 CEV, a high-profile consortium dedicated to the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.whatech.com/market-research/medical/235671-new-report-shares-details-about-the-internet-of-things-iot-healthcare-global-market-growth-that-is-expected-to-register-a-cagr-of-12-5-from-2014-to-2021&#39;&gt;New report shares details about the internet of things (IoT) healthcare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WhaTech Internet of things (IoT), comprising of intermediary components, such as devices, network connectivity, electronics system, and software, is basically &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.automationworld.com/iiot-and-changes-it-demands&#39;&gt;IIoT and the Changes It Demands&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During a panel discussion at PI North America&amp;rsquo;s general meeting, industry experts talked about how the Industrial Internet of Things is affecting the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theinternetofthings.eu/david-franquesa-leandro-navarroxavier-bustamante-circular-commons-digital-devices-tools-and-services&#39;&gt;David Franquesa, Leandro Navarro,Xavier Bustamante: A Circular Commons for&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The eReuse.org commons represents a global federation of local groups, organisations, and communities that deal with the circular life of digital &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.iotevolutionworld.com/m2m/articles/427809-altair-completes-interoperability-testing-lightweight-m2m.htm&#39;&gt;Altair Completes Interoperability Testing For Lightweight M2M&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The motivation of Lightweight M2M is to develop a fast, deployable client-server specification to provide machine to machine service, said Joaquin &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.finextra.com/blogposting/13440/blockchain-wants-to-be-friends-with-your-financial-supply-chain&#39;&gt;Blockchain Wants To Be Friends With Your Financial Supply Chain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only a few months ago, blockchain was considered to a bit geeky, and known mainly in crypto-hacking and techno-banking circles. Critics said it was &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.banks.am/en/news/interviews/13023/&#39;&gt;Matej Michalko: Armenia has a huge potential in Blockchain Technologies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are going to use the intellectual potential, the resources and experience that Armenia has for development of Blockchain technologies. We want to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.smh.com.au/technology/innovation/internet-of-things-google-home-is-a-promising-start-20161128-gszm8k.html&#39;&gt;Internet of Things: Google Home is a promising start&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google&amp;rsquo;s latest gadget is an always on, always listening little speaker called Home. It&amp;rsquo;s a cute design, a friendly blob that looks like a half-finished &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/japans-central-bank-european-central-bank-partner-for-blockchain-research/&#39;&gt;European Central Bank &amp;amp; Japan&amp;rsquo;s Central Bank Partner for Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CryptoCoinsNews The Bank of Japan has revealed a new joint research project with the European Central Bank to study potential use-cases of blockchain technology. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/reuters/article-4009386/Digital-Asset-says-blockchain-platform-allows-confidential-trades.html&#39;&gt;Digital Asset says blockchain platform allows confidential trades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dec 7 (Reuters) - Digital Asset Holdings, a blockchain startup backed by some of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest banks, said on Wednesday it had developed a &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/after-the-bell-blockchain-in-2017-looking-ahead-at-collaboration-scaleability-regulation-what-is-tickets-26306650901&#39;&gt;After the Bell - Blockchain in 2017: Looking Ahead at Collaboration,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that we&amp;rsquo;re coming to the close of 2016, we can see that the blockchain hype is over and we&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to 2017 bringing practical &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.marketwired.com/press-release/igear-joins-association-high-technology-distribution-power-up-industrial-internet-things-2181458.htm&#39;&gt;IGear Joins Association for High Technology Distribution to Power Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marketwired (press release) &amp;ldquo;Joining AHTD will help us to expand our go-to-market distribution efforts for our new SQUEAKS platform - a mobile-first Industrial Internet of Things &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.scmagazineuk.com/iotsf-conference-eu-should-become-de-facto-regulator/article/577218/&#39;&gt;IoTSF conference: EU should become de facto regulator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The European Union should become the de facto world regulator for the security of the Internet of Things, according to one of the speakers at the IoT &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/igear-joins-association-high-technology-140100954.html&#39;&gt;IGear Joins Association for High Technology Distribution to Power Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Sports &amp;hellip; to leverage the IIoT and expand their current Machine-to-Machine strategies to evolve to support Machine-to-Human collaboration,&amp;rdquo; said Korfhage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.forbes.com/sites/theyec/2016/12/07/trust-but-verify-how-blockchain-could-disrupt-your-world/&#39;&gt;Trust, But Verify: How Blockchain Could Disrupt Your World&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin is digital money, the transfer of which is recorded on a global ledger called the blockchain. This blockchain ledger is replicated by thousands of &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/07/circle-blockchain/&#39;&gt;Why This Well-Funded Startup Just Gave Up on Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has led one-time bitcoin companies to focus on the blockchain, the underlying distributed ledger technology that powers bitcoin. Blockchain is &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/blockchain-token-security-coinbase-leads-legal-framework-launch/&#39;&gt;Is Your Blockchain Token a Security? Coinbase Leads Legal Framework Launch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though a black-and-white issues for many enthusiasts, from a legal perspective, innovation with cryptocurrencies and blockchains remains in the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techcitynews.com/2016/12/07/blockchain-startup-setl-scores-funding-from-deloitte/&#39;&gt;Blockchain startup Setl scores funding from Deloitte&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Setl, a blockchain startup for financial services, has received funding from business advisory firm Deloitte. Based in London, the firm, which specialises &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.gereports.com/destiny-holds-internet-things-home-according-amazons-alexa-smart-home-director/&#39;&gt;What Destiny Holds for The Internet Of Things In The Home, According To&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, GE announced its latest LED table lamp featuring Amazon Alexa. It&amp;rsquo;s only the beginning for the smart home of the future, according to Charlie &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://hardware.itbusinessnet.com/article/FreeWave-Technologies-Secures-Second-Consecutive-IoT-Evolution-Product-Of-The-Year-Award-4726166&#39;&gt;FreeWave Technologies Secures Second Consecutive IoT Evolution Product Of&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IT Business Net BOULDER, Colo., Dec. 6, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash;FreeWave Technologies, Inc., a leader in industrial, secure Machine-to-Machine (M2M) and &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://fortune.com/2016/12/07/digital-asset-blockchain/&#39;&gt;This Blockchain Startup Allows Confidential Trades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital Asset Holdings, a blockchain startup backed by some of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest banks, said on Wednesday it had developed a platform to allow &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://news.sys-con.com/node/3967410&#39;&gt;HID Global is First to Enable End-to-End Identity and Access Management for&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SYS-CON Media (press release) HID PIV represents the industry&amp;rsquo;s first comprehensive IAM solution that provides trusted identities for accessing both IT and physical domains, said &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.automationworld.com/drives/role-drives-industrial-internet-things&#39;&gt;The Role of Drives in the Industrial Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As ABB introduces new remote service offerings, manufacturers are realizing that it is the sub processeslike motors and drivesthat will significantly &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20161207005211/en/MAX-Smart-Home-Chooses-Ayla-Networks-Connect&#39;&gt;MAX Smart Home Chooses Ayla Networks to Connect Its Safety Products to the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Wire (press release) SANTA CLARA, Calif.&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;MAX Smart Home, manufacturer of smart home safety and security products, today announced it has &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://cointelegraph.com/news/blockchains-perfect-storm-removing-money-laundering-from-the-financial-system&#39;&gt;Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s Perfect Storm: Removing Money Laundering from the Financial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoinTelegraph This is the first in a three-part report that looks at Anti-money laundering (AML) and the efforts of the Blockchain community to bring everyone together &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://technical.ly/dc/2016/12/07/ubiquitous-computing-noble-ackerson/&#39;&gt;10 smart takes on wearables and the Internet of Things from a local founder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if computing power was all around us, integrated into our lives through wearables and Internet of Things-connected devices, constantly able to &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://sports.yahoo.com/news/sigma-designs-inc-reports-third-210500973.html&#39;&gt;Sigma Designs, Inc. Reports Third Quarter Fiscal Year 2017 Financial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yahoo Sports &amp;ldquo;Our profitable third quarter was led by a healthy rebound in our Internet-of-Things revenue on top of our seasonally strong Smart TV business, strong &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/290433/digital-eyes-see-what-people-are-up-to.html&#39;&gt;Digital Eyes &amp;lsquo;See&amp;rsquo; What People Are Up To&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among other transformation, the Internet of Things will, in effect, create a lot more of what I view as digital eyes. Various types of sensors and tracking &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.theinternetofthings.eu/crowd-mapping-over-1000-organisations-across-europe-using-digital-technology-social-good&#39;&gt;Crowd-mapping over 1000 organisations across Europe using digital&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Digital technologies and the internet are providing new opportunities to address social challenges. We call this phenomenon digital social innovation &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://3dprint.com/156858/cubichain-calram-blockchain/&#39;&gt;Cubichain Stores Data of 3D Printed Aircraft Parts in Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;calram Cubichain Technologies and CalRAM have announced the deployment of a decentralized and immutable blockchain network to facilitate the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://allcoinsnews.com/2016/12/07/virgin-media-business-disruptor-10-selects-blockchain/&#39;&gt;Virgin Media Business Disruptor 10 Selects Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain, provider of digital currency and distributed ledger software, has been announced as a Virgin Media Business &amp;lsquo;Disruptor 10&amp;rsquo; in the Sunday &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.darkreading.com/partner-perspectives/malwarebytes/survey-stresses-importance-of-securing-the-internet-of-things/a/d-id/1327661&#39;&gt;Survey Stresses Importance Of Securing The Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attack surfaces continue to grow, especially as businesses add endpoints and permit new Internet of Things (IoT) devices to connect to their networks, &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.fool.com/investing/2016/12/07/why-shares-of-sigma-designs-crashed-today.aspx&#39;&gt;Why Shares of Sigma Designs Crashed Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sigma Designs CEO Thinh Tran pointed to the company&amp;rsquo;s seasonally strong Smart TV business and a rebound in its Internet of Things business as the &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.themarketdigest.org/201612/usa-technologies-inc-usat-files-form-4-insider-buying-stephen-p-herbert-buys-2000-shares/3211980/&#39;&gt;Usa Technologies Inc (USAT) Files Form 4 Insider Buying : Stephen P Herbert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Market Digest It has designed and marketed systems and solutions that facilitate electronic payment options as well as telemetry and machine-to-machine services &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-12-07/blythe-masters-unveils-fix-for-blockchain-privacy-concerns&#39;&gt;Blythe Masters Unveils Fix for Blockchain Privacy Concerns&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain could finally drag Wall Street recordkeeping into the 21st century, but before they&amp;rsquo;ll use it financial firms want to know their data will be kept &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://blog.coinbase.com/2016/12/07/blockchain-token-securities-law/&#39;&gt;Is a blockchain token a security?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;examines securities law and App Coins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com/news/security/300083065/marc-goodman-as-more-devices-come-online-solution-providers-are-a-key-line-of-defense.htm&#39;&gt;Marc Goodman: As More Devices Come Online, Solution Providers Are A Key&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CRN The Internet of Things will bring 50 billion new things online by 2020, according to a report by research firm Gartner, and many of those devices bring &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.mckinsey.com/industries/high-tech/our-insights/video-meets-the-internet-of-things&#39;&gt;Video meets the Internet of Things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;creating new opportunities. Are companies prepared to capture growth? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thestreet.com/story/13914865/1/here-is-why-corporations-are-moving-toward-blockchain-technology.html&#39;&gt;Here Is Why Corporations Are Moving Toward Blockchain Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the fintech industry will also be booming, and one of the main drivers will be blockchain technology, which uses a distributed database that &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.wsj.com/articles/bitcoin-powerhouse-will-pull-the-plug-on-bitcoin-1481104800&#39;&gt;Bitcoin Powerhouse Will Pull the Plug on Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s underlying technology, blockchain, is widely being studied in the financial services industry as a possible tool to make everyday &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/why-legal-marketing-technologists-need-52422/&#39;&gt;Why Legal Marketing Technologists Need To Learn About Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of those technologies that I&amp;rsquo;ve been paying close attention to is blockchain. In my first post on blockchain &amp;ldquo;Blockchain: What You Need To Know,&amp;rdquo; I &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.smartindustry.com/industrynews/2016/cc-link-ie-and-profinet-launch-interoperability-specification/&#39;&gt;CC-Link IE and PROFINET launch interoperability specification&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Promoting transparency and ease of integration is one of the primary goals for achieving concepts such as the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.automationworld.com/advantech-launches-webaccess-82-hmi-scada-software&#39;&gt;Advantech Launches WebAccess 8.2 HMI/SCADA Software&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest version of WebAccess supports MQTT protocol and adds two new drivers (Ethernet/IP for Allen-Bradley PLC and B+B Wzzard MQTT) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.eweek.com/enterprise-apps/slideshows/why-ai-machine-learning-will-become-mainstream-in-2017.html&#39;&gt;What Industry Experts See From AI, Machine Learning in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence is poised to hit the mainstream in 2017, as the value of machine learning and analytics has become apparent. Here are some &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.todaystrucking.com/why-isaac-instruments-owns-the-internet-of-trucks&#39;&gt;Why Isaac Instruments Owns the Internet of Trucks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CHAMBLEY, QC&amp;ndash; You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard about The Internet of Things&amp;ndash;the phenonenon of interconnected machines working with other &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.finextra.com/pressarticle/67352/digital-asset-holdings-lifts-the-lid-on-blockchain-architecture-in-non-technical-whitepaper&#39;&gt;Digital Asset Holdings lifts the lid on blockchain architecture in&amp;hellip;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, Digital Asset is proud to release a white paper on our architecture, detailing the rationale for the technological decisions that we have made. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/north-america-internet-things-market-202900025.html&#39;&gt;North America Internet Of Things Market Forecast 2016-2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;North America has the largest market share of Internet of things market. Most of the market players are based in North America and there is awareness &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://iotbusinessnews.com/2016/12/07/64546-max-smart-home-chooses-ayla-networks-to-connect-its-safety-products-to-the-internet-of-things/&#39;&gt;MAX Smart Home Chooses Ayla Networks to Connect Its Safety Products to the&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IoT Business News (press release) (blog) MAX Smart Home, manufacturer of smart home safety and security products, today announced it has selected Ayla Networks&amp;rsquo; Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.adlawaccess.com/2016/12/articles/homeland-security-issues-iot-guidance-for-businesses/&#39;&gt;Homeland Security Issues IoT Guidance for Businesses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Entitled Strategic Principles for Securing the Internet of Things (IoT), Version 1.0, the principles seek to provide stakeholders with tools to account for &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/press-releases/press-release-btc-inc-announces-new-blockchain-event-payments-financial-services-innovators-atlanta-distributed-markets/&#39;&gt;Press Release: BTC Inc. Announces New Blockchain Event for Payments &amp;amp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoinDesk BTC Inc. the organizers of groundbreaking blockchain events, Distributed: Health and Distributed: Trade, today announced the launch of Distributed: &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://asia.nikkei.com/Tech-Science/Tech/BOJ-ECB-team-up-on-blockchain-research&#39;&gt;BOJ, ECB team up on blockchain research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TOKYO &amp;ndash; The Bank of Japan and the European Central Bank will jointly research the possible use of blockchain technology &amp;ndash; the foundation of digital &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/andy-plesser/video-wall-size-tvs-to-in_b_13495720.html&#39;&gt;(VIDEO) Wall-Size TV&amp;rsquo;s To Internet Of Things Security: GroupM&amp;rsquo;s Gotlieb On&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huffington Post LONDON - As he looks ahead to CES 2017, GroupM Chairman Irwin Gotlieb sees enormous developments in all six categories that are typically his &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/2347050/talking-dolls-putting-kids-at-risk-from-predators-by-secretly-recording-their-conversations/&#39;&gt;Talking dolls &amp;lsquo;putting kids at risk from predators&amp;rsquo; by &amp;lsquo;secretly recording&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sun With the growing Internet of Things, American consumers face unprecedented levels of surveillance in their most private spaces, and young children &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.coindesk.com/blockchain-industry-circle-bitcoin-shift-stop-payments/&#39;&gt;What the Blockchain Industry is Saying About Circle&amp;rsquo;s Bitcoin Shift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the industry segment surprised by the pivot was Chris Burninske, blockchain products lead for ARK Investment Management. Saying he was &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com/slide-shows/internet-of-things/300083068/10-steps-to-building-a-successful-internet-of-things-practice-in-the-channel.htm&#39;&gt;10 Steps To Building A Successful Internet of Things Practice In The&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CRN What must solution providers do to build out a successful Internet of Things practice? The IoT is more than just a product that can simply be deployed &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.cultofmac.com/457348/ge-led-lamp-alexa/&#39;&gt;GE&amp;rsquo;s new Alexa lamp shines light on internet of things&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve heard for years that the internet of things would imbue everything in our lives with the power of the web, all accessible by voice. If you&amp;rsquo;ve been &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.saukvalley.com/2016/12/07/want-to-stay-safe-trash-that-internet-connected-security-camera/al9etv3/&#39;&gt;Want to stay safe? Trash that internet-connected security camera&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; have shown that everyday items in the internet of things can be harnessed together in robotic networks, or botnets, to conduct crippling attacks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://mspmentor.net/blog/five-backup-and-recovery-trends-2017&#39;&gt;Five Backup and Recovery Trends for 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is thanks to developments such as the Internet of Things, big data and data analytics. MSPs should work with clients to ensure all their business &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://video.cisco.com/detail/videos/iot---internet-of-things/video/5236597041001/creating-a-custom-portal-via-cmx-connect&#39;&gt;Creating a Custom Portal via CMX Connect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;using CMX Connect via CMX Cloud. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/12/08/its-the-blockchain-not-the-bitcoin/&#39;&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the blockchain not the bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s called blockchain or distributed ledgers and this technology holds the potential of positively impacting financial transactions the world over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.dailytechnewsshow.com/dtns-2918-the-blockchain-explained/&#39;&gt;Why distributed ledger technology must adapt to an imperfect world&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://newsroom.accenture.com/content/1101/files/Cross-FSBC.pdf&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYACoTMjg5Mzc0MTQ0NjEwMDEyNjYzNzIaYzdkMzg2ZGFjNzI5NWY3OTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGa_C1XlFz5idOwl5Ovdrq9_ebtbw&#34;&gt;https://www.google.com/url?rct=j&amp;amp;sa=t&amp;amp;url=https://newsroom.accenture.com/content/1101/files/Cross-FSBC.pdf&amp;amp;ct=ga&amp;amp;cd=CAEYACoTMjg5Mzc0MTQ0NjEwMDEyNjYzNzIaYzdkMzg2ZGFjNzI5NWY3OTpjb206ZW46VVM&amp;amp;usg=AFQjCNGa_C1XlFz5idOwl5Ovdrq9_ebtbw&lt;/a&gt;  DTNS 2918  The Blockchain Explained Fitbit buys and shuts down Pebble, Sony gets into mobile games and Tom Merritt attempts to explain the blockchain to Scott Johnson. MP3 &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.crn.com/news/internet-of-things/300083071/nexgen-panel-channel-players-have-big-role-in-new-world-of-iot.htm&#39;&gt;NexGen Panel: Channel Players Have Big Role In &amp;lsquo;New World Of IoT&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things is still the &amp;ldquo;wild, wild west&amp;rdquo; for the technology industry, but if solution providers can hone the right set of skills, they can be major &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://techonomy.com/conf/te16/videos-internet-of-things-data/can-the-internet-of-things-be-secured/&#39;&gt;Can The Internet of Things be Secured?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooper Executive Director, UC Berkeley Center for Long-Term Cybersecurity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/12/08/greenpeace-receives-big-digital-currency-donation-m-blockchain/&#39;&gt;Greenpeace Receives Big Digital Currency Donation Through MA Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The M.A. Blockchain is a branch of Mind Asset, which works to provide distributed database solutions for establishing and encrypting digital currency &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/schaeffler-track-become-mobility-supplier-192500611.html&#39;&gt;Schaeffler on track to become a mobility supplier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The automobile will become part of the Internet of Things,&amp;rdquo; according to Prof. Gutzmer. &amp;ldquo;Our sensor bearings, which are being fitted wherever &amp;hellip; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>