<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iot on Crypt0 News</title>
    <link>//crypt0.net/categories/iot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Iot on Crypt0 News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Dataence. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crypt0.net/categories/iot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 11, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
War of the machine: The opportunities in machine learning for businesses The theatrical release of James Cameron&amp;rsquo;s sci-fi film Terminator 2, featuring Arnold Schwarzenegger as a cyborg with a computer brain, had a crucial &amp;hellip; more.
US State Department Offers Blockchain Development Internship Over the past few years, private investors have poured billions of dollars into blockchain research. More recently, national governments have begun to &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 10, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
THE BLOCKCHAIN IN THE IoT REPORT: How distributed ledgers enhance the IoT Business Insider Blockchain isn&amp;rsquo;t just for bankers anymore. Most of the buzz around the distributed ledger has focused on its uses in finance, where it originated. more.
State-Backed Chicago Blockchain Center Launches to Catalyze Collaboration Over the last decade, blockchain technology, a public, accessible ledger for digital assets, like Bitcoin, has received increased interest not just by &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 9, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
China&amp;rsquo;s Banking Regulators Push for Blockchain Securities Rules The Chinese securities market needs new rules focused on blockchain in order to ward off potential risks, according to a new paper from the China &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain technology and cryptography provider Stratumn raises 7m Less than two years after its inception and one year after its seed financing, Stratumn has now accomplished the largest funding round to date in the &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 8, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain: The new messiah for musicians? There is an emerging strand of thought now, reflected in a recent HBR article by Grammy-winner Imogen Heap, that a blockchain-powered rights and &amp;hellip; more.
Pew: Given the Inevitably of IoT Security Breaches, Are We Getting Ahead of Telecompetitor (blog) cybersecurity Deployments of Internet of Things (IoT) connections, devices and networks will continue to multiply over the next few years despite &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 7, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Industrial Internet of Things Drives Pharma Line Integration Industrial Internet of Things Drives Pharma Line Integration. Changes come slow to pharmaceutical packagers, but the push is on to integrate lines. more.
LiveWorx 2017: 8 Partners With The Coolest Applications At PTC&amp;rsquo;s Partner CRN At its conference, PTC added new features and manufacturing apps to its ThingWorx Internet of Things platform, aimed at better positioning its channel &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 6, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Lack of Experience May Plague IoT Security Startups Eighty-five percent of businesses plan to implement IoT by 2019, according to &amp;hellip;. IoT security very much strongly builds on core identity management &amp;hellip; more.
Defending against the dark side of the Internet of Things A frontrunner in technological advancement is the so-called Internet of Things, the linkage of embedded sensors and communications devices to a &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 5, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT Security: Nearly Half Of Businesses Experience Breaches Because Of International Business Times Nearly half of all companies in the United States that use an Internet of Things (IoT) network have been affected by a security breach that has hurt &amp;hellip; more.
Infosys industrial internet business head Gordon Muehl quits &amp;hellip; (IIC), a US-based non-profit group working to have a common set of applications for companies and IT vendors in the internet of things (IoT) space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 4, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What exactly is the Internet of Things? The Internet of Things (IoT) is an emerging technology where machines are embedded with sensors that allow them to exchange data with each other, &amp;hellip; more.
Steptoe Cyberlaw Podcast: Blockchain Takes Over the Podcast Episode 167 sees blockchain take over the podcast again. With Stewart traveling, Alan Cohn hosts another of the podcast&amp;rsquo;s periodic deep dives into &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 3, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Driving the future of smart cities with IoT But it has gone through some dramatic twists and turns with the emergence of key enablers like the internet of things. Improbable but true: the first IoT &amp;hellip; more.
Bell Set to Launch LTE-M IoT Network in Canada &amp;hellip; launch an LTE-M (Long Term Evolution, category M1) network in order to support the increasing use of Internet of Things (IoT) devices on low-power &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 2, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Walmart: Blockchain tech a boon for food safety Wal-Mart Stores on Thursday revealed encouraging results of a test of blockchain technology to aid food traceability and safety, demonstrating it could &amp;hellip; more.
Monitoring system opts for NewSQL database engine to take on IoT data The much vaunted internet of things could be too much of too many good things &amp;ndash; at least for databases. That is because IoT data from remote sensors &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jun 1, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-06-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Two Blockchain Startups Become Finalists in MassChallenge Global CoinTelegraph Last week, global startup competition and accelerator MassChallenge announced its 2017 finalists, which includes two Bitcoin/Blockchain companies, &amp;hellip; more.
Quisk to integrate blockchain into payment platform Digital cash network provider Quisk will integrate blockchain into its platforms, the company has announced, to make it easier for its banking clients to &amp;hellip; more.
Without enterprise architecture, the Internet of Things is just&amp;hellip; things With the rise of the Internet of Things, there&amp;rsquo;s never been a more critical time for enterprise architects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 31, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things Community (IoT Community) Welcomes SAS as First Platinum PR Newswire (press release) The Internet of Things Community (IoT Community) - the world&amp;rsquo;s largest group of CxOs and IoT professionals - welcomes SAS as its first Platinum &amp;hellip; more.
Danelec Marine platform links ships to the Internet of Things 2017 Birkeroed, Denmark, headquartered Danelec Marine reports that its intelligent remote management platform is bringing the Internet of Things &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 30, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Partnerships and sharing at the heart of digitalisation SHIPPING companies will have the chance to adopt blockchain technology to ensure integrity of transactions and efficiency of workflows, which could &amp;hellip; more.
If You Love the Internet of Things, You Should Check Out Sierra Wireless The Internet of Things (IoT), which consists of billions of objects linked to each other and the cloud, is widely considered the hot growth market for tech &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 29, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
MinexCoin, a Great Investment Prospect with Its Price Poised to Grow MinexCoin, the cryptocurrency fueling MinexEcosystem is set to grow strong as the blockchain platform continues to raise funds through the ongoing &amp;hellip; more.
ConsenSys Academy Opens Applications for 2017 Developer Program The participants of the program will go through a highly selective ten-week long online blockchain tutorials, which will end with an all-expense paid trip &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 28, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
&amp;lsquo;Surveillance shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the business model of the internet. We can Times of India Internet of Things devices will be lower cost and will have even worse security than our computers and phones. Many of them are not patchable, even &amp;hellip; more.
This was a big week for blockchain I had about 100 conversations with people who are at the epicenter of the blockchain wave, including one of the approximately 35 people in the world &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 27, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
A Marketer&amp;rsquo;s Guide to The Internet of Things With research firm Gartner forecasting that the number of connected things worldwide will reach 20.4 billion by 2020, the rise of the Internet of Things &amp;hellip; more.
NB-IoT? Not at Those Prices, Say DT Customers Want to know more about the Internet of Things? Check out our dedicated IoT content channel here on Light Reading. more.
Cloud Security Alliance Releases New Guidance for Connected Vehicle Dark Reading New Report from Internet of Things (IoT) Working Group Identifies Vehicle Attack Vectors and Impacts, Provides Recommendations for Securing the &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 26, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Eaton Partners with Georgia Tech&amp;rsquo;s Center for the Development and Solid State Lighting Design (press release) CDAIT is a non-profit, partner-funded center in Atlanta that the Georgia Institute of Technology created to develop and apply Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; more.
Top Blockchain and Cryptocurrency Experts to Follow in 2017 The world of cryptocurrency and blockchain has gotten very exciting over the last few months. Bitcoin and Ethereum are at all time highs with no end in &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 25, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Consensus 2017 Day 2 Recap: Finding Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s Common Ground Can regulators and the entrepreneurs who want to use blockchain to upend the markets and sectors they work in find common ground? The panels of &amp;hellip; more.
Chain Business Insights releases first benchmark survey on blockchain in Modern Materials Handling Chain Business Insights, LLC, an independent research firm focused on the application of blockchain in supply chain management and trade finance, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 24, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Intel Solutions Summit: IoT Exec Highlights Industrial, Retail Sectors As CRN Whether it&amp;rsquo;s on the factory floor or in a grocery store, more businesses are using the Internet of Things to connect their devices and solve industry &amp;hellip; more.
Toyota Is Using Blockchain to Get Its Self-Driving Cars on the Roads Sooner Toyota have developed a strategy that uses blockchain to increase the availability of information that could improve driverless car technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 23, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What&amp;rsquo;s Next for Calamp Corporation (NASDAQ:CAMP) After Having Less Shares Finance News Daily The Company&amp;rsquo;s Wireless DataCom segment offers solutions for mobile resource management (MRM) applications, the machine-to-machine (M2M) &amp;hellip; more.
As voice &amp;amp; data businesses take a hit, Airtel, Vodafone and Idea are Economic Times MUMBAI: Top Indian telcos Bharti Airtel, Vodafone India and Idea Cellular are looking to new revenue streams in the government&amp;rsquo;s smart cities &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 22, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Android Things can serve up M&amp;amp;M candies, and recognize dogs A couple years ago, Google unveiled Project Brillo, an Internet of Things platform designed to operate automated products like smart lightbulbs, &amp;hellip; more.
Exclusive: McAfee channel boss on why the future&amp;rsquo;s looking good for the new ChannelLife NZ At a time of increasing threats, rapid change, cloud and internet of things, Mahapatra McAfee&amp;rsquo;s APAC chief of channels, alliances and specialist &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 21, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
United States should not stockpile cyber weapons, Microsoft says &amp;hellip; from machine to machine by exploiting a Microsoft vulnerability affecting multiple operating systems. The attack was eventually disarmed; however, &amp;hellip; more.
Alarm.com IoT Service Receives Google Home Support The Alarm.com smart home service received support for the Google Home connected speaker, allowing users to manage Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; more.
Why Intel believes 5G wireless will make autonomous cars smarter The Internet of Things is expected to grow quickly to tens of billions of connected devices, from smart refrigerators to smart showers to smart cruise &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 20, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
AT&amp;amp;T Launches Industrial IoT Network The acronym LTE-M stands for Long Term Evolution-M, which is the machine-to-machine (M2M) version of high-speed cellular LTE. LTE-M is a very &amp;hellip; more.
University Student Involvement Supports Australia&amp;rsquo;s Booming Blockchain Bitcoin Magazine The blockchain industry is booming in Australia recently after the Australian Tax Office (ATO) announced changes to tax laws in the 20172018 &amp;hellip; more.
CRM is the latest beneficiary of blockchain technology applications Blockchain could appeal to organizations struggling to unify disparate data sources by enabling them to obtain 360-degree views of customers, said &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 19, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Intrinsic ID to Host Spring Security Summit with IoT Security Focus on May MarketWatch SUNNYVALE, CA&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - May 18, 2017) - Intrinsic ID, a leading provider of authentication technology for IoT security and other embedded &amp;hellip; more.
Berenberg Bank Boosts Telit Communications Plc (TCM) Price Target to GBX The Cerbat Gem Telit Communications PLC (Telit) is a United Kingdom-based enabler of machine-to-machine (M2M) communications providing cellular, short range &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 18, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
SAP unveils blockchain service in the cloud According to a statement released on Tuesday the &amp;ldquo;ready-to-use blockchain technology&amp;rdquo; will sit in the SAP Cloud. This means that any clients can &amp;hellip; more.
How Blockchain Could Help Emerging Markets Leap Ahead Much has been made of the potential for blockchain technologies to open up new vistas for business and society. But is there a way for this &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 17, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Member states want looser data rules in draft ePrivacy bill The draft report on the ePrivacy rules also say that a number of issues will need to be addressed in relation to machine-to-machine communications. more.
Sprint Targets Next Generation IoT Across Nationwide Network Reliable, secure and low-power peer-to-peer, machine-to-machine (M2M) network communications is the functional attribute shared by all of them that &amp;hellip; more.
In the K(NO)W: How identity can solve the dystopian future of the Internet One World Identity Birch said he sees organizations like One World Identity and its K(NO)W &amp;hellip; Because, in Birch&amp;rsquo;s view, what the world faces now with IoT is a market &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 4, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
How blockchain technology applies to your company Blockchain technology is a red-hot topic in the news these days and in many C-suite discussions. It has wide applicability to many industries and most &amp;hellip; more.
Intel opens Autonomous Driving Garage, touts 5G and big data &amp;hellip; such as allowing low and high bandwidth applications along with machine-to-machine communication, the latter of which would let cars send data &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 3, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Stifel Just Issued Hold Rating on Tangoe Inc (TNGO) &amp;hellip; infrastructure and services machine-to-machine connections enterprise social and information technology connections and encompasses the entire &amp;hellip; more.
Top US Defense Contractor Lockheed Martin Bets on Blockchain Technology Lockheed Martin announced the the forthcoming incorporation of blockchain technology into its operations. The company, one of the top defense &amp;hellip; more.
Jon Matonis Accepts Executive Position at Blockchain Firm Nchain The blockchain company Nchain wants to blaze a path toward creating on-chain solutions to the Bitcoin scaling conundrum, and now they have Jon &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 2, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
41% Of Small Businesses Would Use An AI Robot To Handle Marketing, MediaPost Communications The Internet of Things can impact businesses of all sizes, even those that are small. Many small businesses are quite small, with 89% of small &amp;hellip; more.
Can blockchain technology help poor people around the world? Big Wall Street companies are using a complicated technology called blockchain to further increase the already lightning-fast speed of international &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - May 1, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-05-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Can blockchain technology help poor people around the world? (THE CONVERSATION) Big Wall Street companies are using a complicated technology called blockchain to further increase the already lightning-fast &amp;hellip; more.
How Will The Internet Of Things Change Government And Democracy? The ability of local and national governments to access vast amounts of data has already caused well publicized conflicts, because while we know that &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 30, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT Evolution World Week in Review: Cisco, GE, Samsung That book, published recently, is called IoT Time: Evolving Trends in the Internet of Things. In a new weekly series, we&amp;rsquo;ll be previewing chapters for &amp;hellip; more.
University of Melbourne first in Australia to use blockchain for student The Australian Financial Review In an Australian first, the University of Melbourne will soon test blockchain technology to record student credentials, allowing people to share verified &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 29, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What&amp;rsquo;s Happening with Intel&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things Group So far, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen that Intel (INTC) is touching on every aspect of dataprocessing, transmitting, storing, and accessing. The company&amp;rsquo;s IoTG (Internet &amp;hellip; more.
13 stunning stats on the Internet of Things consumer behavior, transform major industries and change business forever. more.
UNOPS Issues RFI for Blockchain Tech UNOPS and the member organizations of [the] UN blockchain group have been analyzing the possible applicability of the existing or emerging &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 28, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Intel Eyes an IoT &amp;amp; 5G Future Intel is pushing ahead with trying to open up new markets such as 5G and the Internet of Things (IoT) as the chipmaker posted mixed results overall &amp;hellip; more.
Some Companies Just Don&amp;rsquo;t Mix With the Internet of Things Everyone seems like they want to be in the Internet of Things world these days. Each month, a slew of up and coming devices (mainly prototypes and &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 27, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
New IoT Navigator tool enables businesses to find tailor-made IoT platforms Yahoo Finance IoT Now is the market-leading web portal and magazine, reporting daily on the development of Machine-to-Machine (M2M) and Internet of Things &amp;hellip; more.
Spotify attempts to solve royalty riddle with blockchain technology Spotify is teaming up with a blockchain startup to help attribute the songs it hosts to its respective artists. Mediachain Labs, a young company out of &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 26, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Halal blockchain to boost supply chain transparency Bitcoin. Blockchain is already called the fourth industrial revolution. It is a digital &amp;hellip; more.
Middle East And Africa IoT Investment To Reach Usd7.8 Billion In 2017 Dubai, UAE As global cities become smarter and more connected, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to play a transformative role in enhancing &amp;hellip; more.
Chain Reaction: How Blockchain Is Infiltrating MarTech since 2013, and more than 2,500 patents involving the technology have been &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 25, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet-of-things startup Sensoro raises $18M in Series B funding Internet-of-things startup Sensoro raises $18M in Series B funding. Apr 24, 2017, 3:38pm PDT Updated Apr 24, 2017, 4:44pm PDT. Industries &amp;amp; Tags &amp;hellip; more.
Microsoft Readies &amp;lsquo;IoT Central&amp;rsquo; SaaS Solution In a bid to make Internet of Things (IoT) technologies more accessible to novices, Microsoft is readying a new Software as a Service (SaaS) offering &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 24, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Our objective is to have mroe devices in hands of consumers: Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s ETTelecom.com Our objective is to have mroe devices in hands of consumers: Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s Mantosh Malhotra NEW DELHI: In an interaction with ET&amp;rsquo;s Danish Khan &amp;hellip; more.
IoT Hub launches inaugural Australian IoT Awards Celebrating the best of IoT Hub So if you, your channel partners or your customers are involved in the creation or use of an Internet of Things-based solution to achieve your business &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 23, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
[Pre-IFA] Korean tech firms to drive innovation at IFA 2017 The Internet of Things has already reached the consumer. &amp;hellip; gaming, computing, services like the Internet of Things and the smart home, to new fields &amp;hellip; more.
Hanover fair to showcase advances in industrial internet of things Industry experts say the fair will show that Industry 4.0 the industrial internet of things, or IIoT, transforming the way goods are manufactured and &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 22, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Vodafone becomes first IoT mobile provider to exceed 50 mn connections NEW DELHI: Vodafone has emerged as the first global Internet of Things (IoT) mobile provider to exceed 50 million connections as of February 2017, &amp;hellip; more.
2017 to be year of IoT implementation Following a significant amount of activity surrounding the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) over the past 18 months, 2017 is tipped to be the year &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 21, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
How the Internet of Things Puts SCADA Systems at Risk As the Internet of Things (IoT) becomes more pervasive in everyday life, more industrial systems are connected to the Internet, which creates risk to the &amp;hellip; more.
Lantronix Expands Sales Partnerships in Asia Pacific Japan Region Lantronix, Inc. is a global provider of secure data access and management solutions for Internet of Things (IoT) and information technology (IT) assets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 20, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Four critical steps to ensure success with the Internet of Things (IoT) The Internet of Things (IoT) is the foremost tech topic of the day. And for good reason: By connecting the unconnected through sensors and networks, &amp;hellip; more.
May Be the First Hilariously Epic Failure on &amp;lsquo;The Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; things. The idea is that all your household appliances will be connected to the &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 19, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
New Tech Paper: Blockchain Technology for Ports Executives in the port, harbour and terminal industries need to understand the potential impact and implications of DLT and blockchain in business, &amp;hellip; more.
Smart mirror doesn&amp;rsquo;t prove to be bright idea for UCSD grad Martin was pitching an Internet of Things product, and the IoT is hotter than blazes. Firefly&amp;rsquo;s product video had something to do with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 18, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Rival IoT malware clash in a botnet territory battle A rival piece of programming has been infecting some of the same easy-to-hack internet-of-things (IoT) products, with a resiliency that surpasses Mirai, &amp;hellip; more.
Gambling fun or addiction? When going for the big win causes big loss I spent the next two hours drinking free iced-tea and going from machine to machine, inserting my casino cash card and shouting show me the &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 17, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Accenture chimes in on virtual care, data breaches and IoHT It&amp;rsquo;s not just the Internet of Things that&amp;rsquo;s coming. It&amp;rsquo;s also the Internet of Health Things. This was the topic of a brand new survey from Accenture. more.
Mirai Bot Infects IoT Appliances to Harvest Bitcoins During the recent years, many kinds of malicious programs for mining Bitcoins have been into existence. But, the popular Mirai bot malware utilized to &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 16, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Framework for fugitive Methane Gas Leaks Monitoring Monitoring. L. J. Klein, R. Muralidhar, F. J. Marianno, J.B. Chang, S. Lu, H.F. &amp;hellip; more.
NXT-ID Inc (NASDAQ: NXTD) On A Growth Path, Will The Stock Follow? &amp;hellip; the Company partners with industry leading companies to provide solutions for modern payment and the Internet of Things (IoT) applications. more.
Ukraine and BitFury launching first &amp;lsquo;full-scale&amp;rsquo; blockchain eGovernment Brave New Coin According to the announcement, the program will begin with a pilot project introducing Blockchain technology into Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s eGovernment platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 15, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
UK businesses face nearly 500 attacks a day Almost all of these attacks, 92 percent of them, are targeting Internet of things devices, such as networked security cameras or building control systems &amp;hellip; more.
Ubiquitous Internet of Things Devices Will Mean More Work in the PCB Design Prepare to supply the Internet of Things with an endless supply of PCBs. more.
Insurtech Startup Etherisc Wins Blockchain Oscar for Innovative Insurance Blockchain News Etherisc (etherisc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 14, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What can the Internet of Things do for Latin America? of physical devices such as cars, televisions, or home appliances to the &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain: UK regulator asks for input as it addresses emerging business JD Supra (press release) In its simplest form, blockchain is a decentralised technology or distributed ledger on which transactions are anonymously recorded. This means the &amp;hellip; more.
Bastille warns radio-based hacks pose risk to national infrastructure Bastille provides full visibility into the known and unknown mobile, wireless and Internet of Things devices inside an enterprise&amp;rsquo;s corporate &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 13, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Internet of Things: What to consider before you buy into the hype The Internet of Things is attracting major mainstream attention, but businesses may be pressured to jump on board for fear of missing out. The hype &amp;hellip; more.
Will this San Francisco fintech change how venture capitalists raise money? San Francisco-based Blockchain Capital sold its entire $10 million venture fund offering represented by digital tokens in just six hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 12, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
CME Group Royal Mint test blockchain for gold trading American financial market company CME Group has collaborated with Britain&amp;rsquo;s The Royal Mint and have begun testing a blockchain platform for gold &amp;hellip; more.
IoT Spending Soars, AI Investments Heading To $46 Billion Now some new numbers are out showing the global scale of the Internet of Things. IoT technology spending will hit $.5 trillion, or 7% of all technology &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 11, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What Is The Internet Of Things &amp;ndash; A Complete Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide In 2017 Amazon Echo. FitBit. Even your coffee pot. While you might be thinking one of these things is not like the other, they are all examples of the Internet of &amp;hellip; more.
Fidelity joins forces with academic researchers on blockchain Fidelity Investments has joined with a group of universities and technology companies working to develop blockchain technology, becoming the first &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 10, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
As cities get smarter, hackers become more dangerous: This could stop them Cities around the world are using various technologies smart devices, apps, sensors, big data analytics and Internet of Things applications to &amp;hellip; more.
Fidelity Becomes First Asset Manager to Join Blockchain Group IC3 The Boston-based fund manager will collaborate with the group to develop blockchain programs to help make financial systems more efficient and &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 9, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Android Things Developer Preview 3 Now Available The Developer Preview is a great way to get feedback from all of the developers working on the Internet of Things. Google has been asking &amp;hellip; more.
Brazil pilots Bitcoin solution for real estate registration Ubitquity LLC recently launched to a pilot project in Brazil, recording real estate ownership on the Bitcoin blockchain. The Delaware-based startup &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 8, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IBM Watson and Internet of Things Top Highlights at Upcoming 15th Annual Yahoo Finance During the session, &amp;ldquo;Made in China 2025: Transformation, Outcomes and Leadership in the Age of Internet of Things,&amp;rdquo; Sanjay will discuss the new &amp;hellip; more.
Cryptocurrency and Blockchain Market Growth by 2021- Industry Size, Shares, Green Mountain Outlook Cryptocurrency and Blockchain Market Report Forecast 2017-2021 is a respected source of insightful data for business planners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 7, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Connected IO launches new miniature modem for Internet of Things ASX-listed Connected IO continues to blaze a trail in the burgeoning internet of things global market with the launch of a new wireless modem device &amp;hellip; more.
Latest Report Reveals Mac Malware Grew 744% in 2016! While it&amp;rsquo;s still easier to stay safe from Mac malware try not to install malicious software it&amp;rsquo;s more difficult to secure Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 6, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Sigfox Pioneers Internet of Things Interoperability to Further Accelerate IoT Business News (press release) (blog) Sigfox demonstrates IoT interoperability with Internet compression technology, enabling LPWAN applications to transparently run over different IoT &amp;hellip; more.
Maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t really need a Wi-Fi-connected sex toy The internet of things is gaining a lot of attention these days as this growing network of internet- and Wi-Fi-enabled products are increasingly showing &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 5, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Strange behavior with multiple MQTT nodes has the topic set to &amp;ldquo;temp/1&amp;rdquo; and the other &amp;ldquo;temp/2&amp;rdquo; When I reset each &amp;hellip; more.
How to survive in the Wild West of the Internet of Things The Internet of Things (IoT) has arrived, and government agencies are looking to protect themselves from its threats while still reaping its benefits. more.
Greater Phoenix Economic Council campaign focuses on internet of things GPEC latest campaign, &amp;ldquo;The Connected Place,&amp;rdquo; puts emphasis on the internet of things, &amp;ldquo;where objects send and receive data, learn from it, and &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 4, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Why Energy Blockchain Intrigues Big Players Like Siemens Not so long ago energy blockchain technology had the futuristic feel of flying cars or colonies on Mars. But that has changed in recent months as &amp;hellip; more.
Connecting the Health Ecosystem - Presentation - CA40226015 section of IDC Health Insights&amp;rsquo; 2016 Connected Health and Value-Based IT &amp;hellip; more.
Dubai Electricity &amp;amp; Water Authority&amp;rsquo;s initiatives in the areas of 3D OpenGov Asia Under the first MOU collaborative research will be conducted to develop additive manufacturing technologies, rapid prototyping, digital technologies, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 3, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
2degrees launches New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s first unlimited mobile plan but with The National Business Review &amp;hellip; can you tether your phone to another device like a laptop to use it as a modem, or use it as wi-fi hotspot or for machine-to-machine communication. more.
3 essentials to capitalize on APAC&amp;rsquo;s IoT supremacy The Internet of Things (IoT) have come a long way since ATMs, one of the first connected objects to go online back in 1974.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 2, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What is the Internet of Things? It features heavily in discussions about the future and, increasingly, the &amp;hellip; more.
This is an era of Internet of Things: Top quotes from PM Modi&amp;rsquo;s address at On Saturday, Prime Minister Narendra Modi addressed over 10,000 aspiring innovators who will be aiming to solve 598 problems at &amp;lsquo;Smart India &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain Entertainment Studio Ropes in Hollywood Talent as Advisor SingularDTV, a blockchain entertainment studio and rights management platform building a decentralized entertainment industry on the Ethereum &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Apr 1, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-04-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Second Life? Failed DAO Creators Are Making a Comeback Bid Finally, the lost funds were returned via a controversial hard fork of the ethereum blockchain that resulted in what appears to be a permanent schism in &amp;hellip; more.
Almost half of insurtech funding targets AI and IoT: Accenture Artificial intelligence (AI) and the internet of things (IoT) accounted for almost half of total investment in insurtech startups globally in 2016, according to &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 31, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
AMR Meters Market Expected To Receive a Natural Boost in Adoption As EconoTimes Wilmington, Delaware, United States, March 30, 2017 &amp;ndash; The report Global AMR Meters Sales Market Report 2017, available on MarketIntelReports, &amp;hellip; more.
Editorial: Guarding privacy on the internet &amp;hellip; to guard privacy in the age of advancing technology, including the so-called Internet of Things, a growing variety of Net-connected devices including &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 30, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Press Release: Mastercard Enhances Security of the Internet of Things with One World Identity PURCHASE, N.Y (March 29, 2017) Mastercard (NYSE:MA) today announced it has entered into an agreement to acquire NuData Security, &amp;hellip; more.
Beijing Officials Demand Chinese Blockchain Standards Sina Finance is reporting that a Beijing city regulator has demanded country officials to adopt a standard approach to Blockchain technology &amp;hellip; more.
Spanish Bank BBVA joins Hyperledger Project &amp;hellip; of R3, which is also participating in Hyperledger, and of the Ethereum Enterprise Alliance, which supports the creation of blockchain standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 29, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Asavie Continues Global Expansion with New Point of Presence and Offices to Yahoo Finance IoT Asia - Asavie, a provider of next generation enterprise mobility management and Internet of Things(IoT) connectivity solutions, today announced &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain News Recap With Marco Barulli: BlockShow Europe 2017 Special Cointelegraph Events is thrilled to see you in Munich on April 5-7 to provide the first-hand knowledge about successful implementations of Blockchain &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 28, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Accenture Positioned as a Leader in IDC MarketScape Report for Worldwide Yahoo Finance Accenture (ACN) is positioned as a Leader in the inaugural IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Internet of Things (IoT) Consulting and Systems Integration &amp;hellip; more.
NZ policymakers need to start planning for 5G mobile infrastructure, The National Business Review &amp;hellip; about how to remove roadblocks from the looming build of a fifth-generation mobile backbone needed for more machine-to-machine interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 27, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
A Robotic Arm with a Sense of Touch The measurement and quantification of human movement in haptics is similar to the sensing that forms the basis of the internet of things. The research &amp;hellip; more.
Trusted Objects Delivers a Secure TLS Protocol to Both IP and Non-IP PR Web (press release) Trusted Objects, a security expert for the Internet of Things (IoT), in partnership with Avnet Silica and UbiquiOS technology, announces the availability &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 26, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
HCM City launches Internet of Things startup competition The Saigon Hi-Tech Park (SHTP) launched the 2017 Internet of Things Startup Competition (IoT Startup 2017) on March 25. The competition, the &amp;hellip; more.
Compare Molfar.io vs. MQTT Buddy comparison of molfar-io &amp;amp; mqtt-buddy: features pricing integrations. more.
Compare Cloud Foundry vs. MQTT Buddy Foundry (overall score at 8.0 and user satisfaction at 98%) and MQTT Buddy &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 25, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Industrial IoT can push Asean forward Moreover, a wave of technological advancement dubbed the Industrial Internet of Things (Industrial IoT) has knocked on the doors of this &amp;hellip; more.
Jessica Leigh Brown: How Will the Internet of Things Impact Education? everyday items are becoming connected devices. So, how does that &amp;hellip; more.
OPINION: Blockchain Not the Swiss Army Knife of Settlement The US Securities and Exchange Commission adopted an amendment on Wednesday that requires broker-dealers to shortened settlement cycle by &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 24, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain-based Identity Service backed by the Big 5 Canadian Banks SecureKey announced Monday that later this year it will release a blockchain-based service, giving customers the ability to control what classifying &amp;hellip; more.
Can blockchain fix the world&amp;rsquo;s food fraud problems? Ecommerce giant Alibaba has partnered with PwC alongside Australia Post and Blackmores to test whether blockchain can solve the global problem &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain Has the Power to Create a Sea Change in the Way Shipping Does This month, IBM revealed a blockchain collaboration with Maersk to track its cargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 23, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Maintaining privacy in the Internet of Things (CNN) - A recent WikiLeaks document dump, purportedly from the CIA, claimed that the agency can hack smart TVs and place them in &amp;ldquo;fake-off&amp;rdquo; mode, &amp;hellip; more.
BitPay Has Studied Bitcoin Blockchain Alternatives: None of Them Are Bitcoin Magazine BitPay co-founders Stephen Pair and Tony Gallippi have been around Bitcoin for about as long as anyone else in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 22, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Big Questions for IoT Customers at the IDTechEx Show - 10-11 May Communication and security are key areas for companies looking to utilise the Internet of Things for their businesses. Security breaches present &amp;hellip; more.
3 Great Stocks to Buy Instead of NVIDIA This trend is called the Internet of Things, and tech giant Cisco estimates that the number of connected devices will double between 2015 and 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 21, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Is Your DVR Acting Funny? It Might Be Attacking The Internet In the meantime, if you&amp;rsquo;ve got any great ideas, hey the FTC is looking for ideas on how to make the internet of things more secure, and there&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;hellip; more.
IBM Unveils Blockchain As a Service Based On Open Source Hyperledger Fabric IBM has unveiled its &amp;ldquo;Blockchain as a Service,&amp;rdquo; which is based on the open source Hyperledger Fabric, version 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 20, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IOTA, a Cryptotoken for the Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; Applications Cryptocurrencies, blockchain and the Internet of Things (IoT) are going to be the future. The IOTA tokens combine the goodness of all the three into &amp;hellip; more.
The Future of Fundraising, What&amp;rsquo;s Next? Currently mobile phones are the most multipurpose devices in the world, by 2018 this will be surpassed by the Internet of Things. Devices that fall into &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 19, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain technology can provide lawyers with an authentic, secure ledger A crash course in blockchain at ABA Techshow started Friday with Oliver Goodenough instructing participants to repeat after him its more useful &amp;hellip; more.
Business Viewpoint with Jeff Heeley: Internet of Things increases Tulsa World In 2017, Tulsa consumers will begin to regularly experience the Internet of Things (IoT) not only at work, but also at home, and that technology will be &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 18, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of things data security proves vital in digitized world Privacy concerns arise, and the threat of an internet of things security breach looms. Many people are working hard to make GPS work within buildings &amp;hellip; more.
How to Build a Business-Ready Internet of Things: Standardization Check out Part One on enterprise use cases here and Part Two on IoT &amp;hellip;. Federated identity is part of IoT device identification,&amp;rdquo; said Ramchandra.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 17, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
GE Digital&amp;rsquo;s CTO talks acquisitions, competition and Boston tech The Boston Business Journal caught up with him after his presentation to talk more about the promise of the so-called industrial internet of things and &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain Use Cases: What Does It Mean for Your Business? understanding how blockchain is applicable to them. Wednesday afternoon at MRC &amp;hellip; more.
Digital quality control for the modern food lab METER Group, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 16, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Legally-recognized Blockchain Securities: An Update on the Delaware The Delaware Legislature is now considering language that would explicitly permit corporate shares to live their entire lifecycle on a blockchain. more.
Researchers present early warning system for mass cyber attacks &amp;hellip; longer rely on vulnerable servers, but also attack networked televisions, webcams, or even refrigerators. The Internet of Things makes it possible. more.
The blockchain could help advertisers lock up our attention Today&amp;rsquo;s advertising executives must get familiar with new technology like Bitcoin and blockchain before they are left behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 15, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
There Is No Such Thing As an IoT Platform With Internet of Things (IoT) at the top of the hype curve it is no surprise that there is a growing abundance of products and services tagged with &amp;ldquo;IoT. more.
Genesys Study of IoT Maturity Puts Southeast Asia Low in Rankings Genesys, an omnichannel customer experience and contact center solutions developer, has released its 2016 Internet-of-Things (IoT)-Enabled &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 14, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Arrow and Cypress Join Forces to Support Internet of Things The Internet of Things is a concept seeking to connect devices used for everyday living to the Internet, so that they can share and exchange data and &amp;hellip; more.
Telit revenues climb as it shifts attention to Internet of Things Internet of Things-focussed technology company Telit Communications published its results for the year to 31 December 2016 on Monday, with &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 13, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Machine Tooling&amp;rsquo;s Use of IIoT, 3D Printing The Industrial Internet of Things can make a big impact on predictive maintenance, surface quality, energy use and more in metalworking, which is &amp;hellip; more.
Better Tech Dividend Stock: Intel or Texas Instruments? Intel&amp;rsquo;s growth priorities include data centers, and the Internet of Things. These businesses are performing well; Intel&amp;rsquo;s data center and Internet of Things &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 12, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Big brother, hackers are watching you and your fridge The basic vulnerabilities inherent in the internet of things - one of the biggest concepts being pursued in the technology industry - have been known for &amp;hellip; more.
How Mobile Connectivity Is To Africa What Infrastructure Is To The west Guest column by Paul Marshall, director of Eseye, a U.K.-based cellular machine-to-machine connectivity provider for Internet of Things devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 11, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Maciej Kranz: Building The Internet of Things: Overabundance Of Access As noted above, we&amp;rsquo;re all facing an overabundance of access technologies. This is further complicated by disparate devices and the tasks we want our &amp;hellip; more.
Our Special Report on Practical Blockchain looking at blockchain technologies and digital currency. A long strange trip, with &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain Entrepreneurs, Investors Debate Friendly Jurisdictions Recently about 75 representatives of blockchain startups and venture capital groups met up in San Juan, Puerto Rico for the CoinAgenda Caribbean &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 10, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Internet of Things Poses Human Health Risks: Scientists Question the Digital Journal Replicated research shows that Millimeter waves used by the Department of Defense in crowd control weapons interacts with human skin and &amp;hellip; more.
Building the Internet of Things with Agile and DevOps lives, which creates a lot of challenges. And there&amp;rsquo;s more to IoT than &amp;hellip; more.
What Is Blockchain Technology and Why Are Arizona Leaders So Excited About Phoenix New Times Congressman David Schweikert (R-CD6), is the new co-chair of the bipartisan Congressional Blockchain Caucus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 9, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Agency Taps IBM Watson So Elevators Can Talk About Their Day In Real Time Even through the Internet of Things can involve devices or machines &amp;hellip; AI and the Internet of Things is so hot right now that we wanted to do our part &amp;hellip; more.
Ontario regulators say blockchain use may require approval TORONTO (Reuters) - The Ontario Securities Commission, Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest securities regulator, said on Wednesday companies using blockchain &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 8, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Most Retailers Globally Indicate IoT Plans, Including RFID &amp;hellip; finds that the majority of retailers surveyed globally expect to embrace radio frequency identification and other Internet of Things (IoT) technologies, &amp;hellip; more.
WikiLeaks dump shows CIA can use IoT to hack &amp;lsquo;anything, anywhere&amp;rsquo; &amp;hellip; which are apparently turned into covert microphones. It&amp;rsquo;s that mastery of Internet-of-Things (IoT) technology that has caught the attention of experts. more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 7, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Survey: retailers drive demand for Internet of Things Nearly 70 percent of retail decision makers surveyed are ready to make changes to adopt the Internet of Things (IoT), and 65 percent plan to invest in &amp;hellip; more.
GE, Siemens battle it out to transform manufacturing with cloud-based IoT Computer Business Review Germany&amp;rsquo;s Siemens and its US rival General Electric are competing to roll out an &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; cloud platform for the manufacturing industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 6, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
You Can&amp;rsquo;t Block the Beacon But before you give up and declare the &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; to be taken over by capitalism (it has been, by the way, that fight&amp;rsquo;s lost), there are two more &amp;hellip; more.
Industrial Internet of Things in CeBIT Hannover 2017 The use of IoT technology in manufacturing is called Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT). IIoT has the capacity to transform organizations and countries, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 5, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Airtel and Nokia join hands to prepare for 5G and IoT in India &amp;hellip; network operator, Airtel has joined hands with Nokia to prepare for the next generation of communications &amp;lsquo;5G&amp;rsquo; and Internet of Things (IoT) in India. more.
Locally and nationally, pinball has surged in popularity, with competitions Omaha World-Herald One by one, players dropped off as pairs moved from machine to machine. (Most pinballers have favorite machines, Waldeck said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 4, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Big Data, Machine Learning, and Deep Learning Command Line Tools Organizations are now inundated with data from all sources including transactions, survey, social media, and machine-to-machine data. With new &amp;hellip; more.
Leveraging Data Analytics and Internet of Things in Your Digital CIO Introducing the Internet of Things an ecosystem of sensors, machines, and other everyday items that are producing data and, in many cases, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 3, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Research report explores the global machine-to-machine communication market The Machine-to-Machine Communication Market to 2025 - Global Analysis and Forecasts by Technology and End-user report provides a detailed &amp;hellip; more.
We found a hidden backdoor in Chinese Internet of Things devices  The Register IoT devices from a Chinese vendor contain a weird backdoor that the vendor is refusing to fix, we&amp;rsquo;re told. The vulnerability was discovered in almost all &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 2, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Hacked by Your Fridge: Why the Internet of Things will Cause Havoc in 2017 As business use of internet-connected devices catches up with consumer usage, we&amp;rsquo;re now on the cusp of an Internet of Things revolution. The first &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain Meets Securitization Market In New Chamber Of Digital Commerce CoinTelegraph The Chamber of Digital Commerce has announced a partnership with securitization group SFIG to explore how Blockchain can benefit the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Mar 1, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-03-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Manufacturing a Digital Future - @ThingsExpo #IoT #IIoT #M2M #Sensors SYS-CON Media (press release) IIoT is not a single technology: it is a whole raft of new generation technologies - sensors, new applications, machine-to-machine interfacing, machine &amp;hellip; more.
Integrating the Ethereum Blockchain into Java Apps application using web3j. The Ethereum blockchain is a decentralized platform &amp;hellip; more.
Cisco Jasper grows Internet of Things reach, breadth Nearly a year after it bought Jasper for $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 28, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Connected IO signs new agreement in the US with AT&amp;amp;T Connected IO (ASX:CIO) has successfully formalised and strengthened its relationship with AT&amp;amp;T Inc (NYSE:T) under a new machine to machine &amp;hellip; more.
The Brown Advisory Inc. Increases Stake in Iridium Communications Inc DailyQuint Brown Advisory Inc. raised its position in shares of Iridium Communications Inc (NASDAQ:IRDM) by 22.3% during the fourth quarter, Holdings &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 27, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Higher IoT Speeds Coming To 11 Cities Wireless connectivity within the Internet of Things may be receiving a boost in speed soon as new efforts launch to implement and leverage 5G &amp;hellip; more.
WA can gain from digital ledger blockchain WA&amp;rsquo;s resource companies have been urged to get aboard blockchain or risk being left behind in the inevitable global take-up of what is widely &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 26, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Industrial Internet of Things Market is expected to grow at CAGR of 16.2% MENAFN.COM Industrial internet of things market is expected to grow at CAGR of 16.2% during the forecast period and expected to reach market size of US 1.0 &amp;hellip; more.
IOHK, University of Edinburgh to collaborate on blockchain research Blockchain research and development company IOHK and the University of Edinburgh have established a Blockchain Technology Laboratory at the &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 25, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Maciej Kranz: Building The Internet of Things: Standards And Technology 24/02/2017-03:43. Source. Did I say this chapter was about standards and &amp;hellip; more.
Preparing for the Internet of Things making a significant impact on IT infrastructure budgets already. Is your network &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain: The Next Frontier for Cybersecurity? changing the world of transactions and a whole new ecosystem has &amp;hellip; more.
Technologies That Will Drive Superfast Internet This is especially so as new-age tech such as the Internet of Things (IoT) and virtual working are fast becoming the norm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 24, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT Innovation Heats up in Berlin &amp;hellip; at our openBerlin Innovation Center, where we connected partners and customers with some of the foremost leaders in the Internet of Things (IoT). more.
Blockchain Cloud Storage Provider Raises $3 Million in Seed Financing Storj Labs, a blockchain-based distributed cloud storage provider, has raised $3 million in a seed financing round to advance its open source, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 23, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things Managed Services Market by Service Type, Vertical, and Yahoo Finance NEW YORK, Feb. 22, 2017 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Growing inclination toward cost-efficient managed services is expected to drive the growth of the IoT &amp;hellip; more.
What&amp;rsquo;s Blockchain and Can It Help You Trust Your Data? economy but also of giving decision-makers back their trust in company &amp;hellip; more.
How IoT is Creating Investment Opportunity in Healthcare Such convenience will soon become a reality for healthcare consumers and providers over the next decade as the Internet of Things (IoT) transforms &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 22, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IOTA, a Cryptoplatform for the Internet of Things, Will Debut at MWC 2017 Coinspeaker The team behind IOTA is going to introduce the first decentralized blockless tokens for the Internet of Things that will allow users make transactions at &amp;hellip; more.
Can Blockchains Help Build Trust in Governments? Blockchain technologies are about to hit it big. By the year 2018, nine in 10 governments will be investing in blockchain the technology behind &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 21, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Hills Limited is now solely a value-added tech distributor &amp;hellip; areas such as the DIY business called iProtect, fire safety technology and further &amp;ldquo;investment opportunities&amp;rdquo; in IoT and machine-to-machine learning. more.
Oracle &amp;amp; Wind River: fixing pumps, performance bumps &amp;amp; diagnostic lumps &amp;hellip; always had a primary focus on the embedded software market, even before we started using the Internet of Things (IoT) as a piece of terminology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 20, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
FinTech to distrupt retail banking by 92% in Nigeria Banks and Funds transfer and payments players are the most familiar with the blockchain trend perhaps this is linked to the sectors in which we have &amp;hellip; more.
ST Engineering to thrive amidst Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation initiative &amp;hellip; in 2017 as it is in a structural sweet spot of heightened demand for data analytics, machine-to-machine communications and urbanisation trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 19, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain: The Untapped Goldmine Of Blockchain That Virtually No One Knows Blockchain is the new and revolutionary way to make transactions locally and internationally. It negates a need for a centralized authority such a &amp;hellip; more.
Fermat announces alpha release of blockchain-enabled open source project Fermat has made upgrades to the technology and architecture behind the decentralized and blockchain-enabled open source project Internet of &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 18, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Insurance Coverage for the Internet of Things cybercrime has caught the attention of business owners and boardrooms, the &amp;hellip; more.
EU Commits To More Support For Blockchain The European Union has announced its intention to do more to support blockchain development, as startups, banks and regulators turn an increasing &amp;hellip; more.
Give Blockchain Five Years, Says Development Consortium Mainstream adoption of blockchain technologies could take another five years, as developers and stakeholders continue to work to develop uses for &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 17, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things (IoT): from Everyday Items to Conduits of Digital EIN News (press release) DALLAS, TX, UNITED STATES, February 16, 2017 /EINPresswire.com/ &amp;ndash; Digital Commerce is no longer restricted to computers, tablets and mobile &amp;hellip; more.
The Internet of Things An Opportunity for Transformation in Market Research embedded technology to communicate and sense or interact with their internal &amp;hellip; more.
IBM, Indiegogo and Arrow Electronics Partner to Fuel the Next Generation of Yahoo Finance MUNICH, Feb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 16, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Schneider Electric Exec: Data Analytics In IoT Could Provide A Windfall For CRN Solution providers who are looking for the money in the Internet of Things would do well to look beyond connectivity solutions to the use of real-time &amp;hellip; more.
Researchers Claim New System Makes Bitcoin Transactions Harder to Track The use of public keys gave users with a sense of anonymity; however, all transactions are essentially visible on the blockchain, but more and more &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 15, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Firms Face Increased Data Risk Due to Internet of Things In a report titled, The Internet of Evil Things (IoET), researchers found a common point-of-view among IT leaders the Internet of Things (IoT) is &amp;hellip; more.
Oracle Internet of Things Cloud Applications Enable Organizations to IT Business Net SAN JOSE, Calif., Feb. 13, 2017 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Oracle Modern Supply Chain Experience Oracle announced that it is expanding its Internet of Things &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 14, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Smart manufacturing the rise of IIoT With the rapid uptake of the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT), IT professionals are increasingly trying to figure out how best to ensure it reaches its full &amp;hellip; more.
&amp;lsquo;Internet of things&amp;rsquo; is vulnerable to hackers Q. I read about the hacker attack last October that used household electronics, such as security cameras, to bombard a website with messages, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 13, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain to be breakthrough tech for Dubai and government &amp;hellip; creation of the Dubai Blockchain Strategy and went on to found Hexayurt. more.
To Fight corruption, China Embraces Blockchain Bitcoin And Blockchain The 17th five year plan, recently published by the Chinese government, lists blockchain technologies among the main &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain and insurers: Something or nothing? Blockchain has been much considered by the media in recent months as a relatively new concept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 12, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Mentors: Hyperledger Blockchain Hackathon Training Riyadh held in IBM Riyadh to provide an overview of blockchain and the &amp;hellip; more.
Microsoft Releases Project Rome SDK for Android, Why Is This Important? This is important because it is a step up for Microsoft with the Internet of Things. The Internet of Things, also known as IoT, is the &amp;ldquo;inter-networking&amp;rdquo; of &amp;hellip; more.
Bitcoin Apostle Andreas Antonopoulos to Spread the Message across SouthEast newsBTC The session titled A Day with Andreas: Discover, Engage and Connect to the Future of Blockchain and Cryptocurrency is being organized at the &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 11, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Quest for Security in the Growing Internet of Things Clancy says the Internet of things is going to more than triple in just the next 5 years from 10 billion devices plugged into the Internet to 34 billion. more.
What the Vizio case in tells us about the development of the Internet of Vizio, an American manufacturer of smart televisions was fined $2.2 million by the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) following an investigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 10, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Accenture Debuts Hardware-Based Security Solution to Simplify and Enable According to a new press release, Accenture has unveiled a patent-pending solution that simplifies the ability of blockchain technology to integrate &amp;hellip; more.
B2X Expands Customer Care Offering to Internet of Things and Announces Twice MUNICH B2X, the leading global provider of end-to-end customer care solutions for mobile devices, today announced that it will expand its range of &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 9, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Applying Lessons Learned to the Internet of Things Today, the Niskanen Center submitted comments to the Department of Commerce&amp;rsquo;s National Telecommunications and Information Administration &amp;hellip; more.
Banks to bet heavily on blockchain technology in 2017: Report The adoption of blockchain technology by banks is expected to grow faster in the coming years. According to an Infosys Finacle-LTP survey, 50% of &amp;hellip; more.
HCL study finds that half of the organizations in US and Europe lag in IoT ETCIO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 8, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
8.4 BILLION connected things to be in use in 2017 The Internet of Things (IoT) has stormed onto the scene in recent years like a bull in a china shop. And its growth is showing no signs of slowing. more.
Badir partners with KACST and IBM to host &amp;lsquo;Blockchain Hackathon&amp;rsquo; RIYADH The Blockchain Hackathon will kick-off in Riyadh on Feb. 9-11, 2017 hosted by King Abdulaziz City for Science and Technology (KACST) &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 7, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Should we invest solely in cyber security - or teach our machines instead? &amp;hellip; use their own data to identify suspicious behaviour within automated processes, such as verifying identities and machine-to-machine interactions. more.
Credit Suisse taps R3 for blockchain-based hackathon The Swiss bank put together teams from India, the United States, Great Britain and Poland and challenged them to find ways of using blockchain &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 6, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IT Brief Australia - Internet of things, data centre aid Intel in IT Brief Australia Strength in its internet of things and data centre offerings helped drive Intel revenues for 2016 up, but weren&amp;rsquo;t enough to save the company from &amp;hellip; more.
SK Telecom signs IoT network rollout deal with Thailand SK Telecom will deploy its Internet of Things network in Thailand together with state-owned telco CAT Telecom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 5, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things World 2017 - World&amp;rsquo;s Largest IoT Event the morning, we cover IoT technology from a value-centric perspective. more.
Cumberland&amp;rsquo;s Numerex to exhibit, present at IoT Evolution Expo Cumberland-based Numerex Corp, a provider of Internet of Things solutions, announced that it would be exhibiting and presenting at the IoT Evolution &amp;hellip; more.
Acer launches CloudProfessor IoT starter kit Together with companies such as Gigo, Acer isproviding learners with the easiest ways to get into the Internet of Things (IoT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 4, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Visionstate releases business update as IoT industry continues to grow Visionstate Inc., a division of Visionstate Corp (TSX VENTURE:VIS) specializes in the Internet of Things and analytics. The Company&amp;rsquo;s core product, &amp;hellip; more.
Unsecure IoT makes DDoS attacks stronger, says Kaspersky These included the increasing use of Internet of Things (IoT) botnets to carry out DDoS attacks, examples of the use of this method are the attacks on &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 3, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things Inc. Targets Industrial IoT Market in China /EINPresswire.com/ TORONTO, ON(Marketwired February 02, 2017) Internet of Things Inc. (TSX VENTURE: ITT) (IoT Inc. or the Company), &amp;hellip; more.
Six Unique Internet of Things Startups In 2017 The buzz around Internet of Things technology (IoT) is getting more interesting and intriguing with each passing day. With this technological reform &amp;hellip; more.
Understanding the Impact of the Internet of Things on Field Service current state of the Internet of Things in a field service context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 2, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Senate, House Aides Said to Vie for Top NTIA Spot &amp;hellip; major evolution of the wireless industry toward 5G networks and pervasive machine-to-machine communication, known as the internet of things.. more.
GameCredits Blockchain Payment Solution Goes Mobile In 2017 Blockchain payment solution innovated by GameCredits aims to launch in mobile store spring of 2017, paving the way for mass cryptocurrency &amp;hellip; more.
How To Make 2017 The Year Of IoT Security People who make Internet of Things (IoT) devices still aren&amp;rsquo;t getting the message on security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Feb 1, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Bitcoin Lightning Network Creator Joins MIT Digital Currency Effort Dryja will now work full-time at the famed technical university&amp;rsquo;s cryptocurrency and blockchain research effort a division of its larger MIT Media Lab &amp;hellip; more.
Amex joins JPMorgan, IBM in hyperledger effort &amp;hellip; has signed on to the Hyperledger Project, a industry group of more than 100 members developing blockchain technology for corporate use. more.
Internet of Things Platforms and Standardisation Workshop you actively involved in Internet of Things (IoT) Platforms &amp;amp; Standards?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 31, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Australian technology investment on the decline In particular, 36 per cent of businesses in Australia and New Zealand have invested in machine-to-machine or IoT solutions or will do so over the next &amp;hellip; more.
Another Set Of IoT Security Principles Introduced The effort to bring better security to the Internet of Things continues, as another alliance has developed its own set of security principles. The Smart &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 30, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
China gung-ho on blockchain, aims to tackle fraud in market After reportedly testing a blockchain based digital currency, the People&amp;rsquo;s Bank of China (PBOC) is further looking to reap the benefits of the technology &amp;hellip; more.
CBA&amp;rsquo;s test of government bond using the blockchain, is just that Blockchain has generated an enormous amount of excitement in a short time. But despite the hype, actual use of blockchain in finance has been slight &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 29, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things Messaging, Part 3: Testing Mosquitto So, in the last installment of this series on the messaging protocol MQTT, we installed the Mosquitto MQTT broker. Now we&amp;rsquo;ll test it which we&amp;rsquo;re going &amp;hellip; more.
ReferralCoin Strengthens Network Marketing Industry, Invites Investors to Yahoo Finance 28, 2017 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; The organization behind ReferralCoin, Referral Foundation is in the process of introducing the state-of-the-art blockchain &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 28, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Microsoft Canada JumpStarts its digital transformation strategy Besides products, Nair added that markets segment such as artificial intelligence, Internet of Things, cloud, and may even include areas like robotics. more.
Applications of Blockchain in Healthcare: Cybersecurity, Interoperability &amp;amp; &amp;hellip; conditions. I foresee the integration of blockchain into healthcare which cross the matrix of cybersecurity, interoperability and precision medicine. more.
Short range connectivity options for IoT The concept of connecting devices to the Internet is called, the Internet of Things (IoT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 27, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Bitfury Group raises $30M for Chinese blockchain expansion The Bitfury Group, a world leading Bitcoin and blockchain infrastructure provider, announced today that Credit China Fintech Holdings Limited will &amp;hellip; more.
Why consumer IoT devices will deploy advanced security Looking across the overall Internet of Things (IoT) security landscape, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that &amp;lsquo;consumer IoT&amp;rsquo; should be viewed as a separate segment, given &amp;hellip; more.
William Mougayar: The Future Of Blockchain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 26, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Intel&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things Acquisition History in 16 Slides With its mobile business looking like a dead end and its PC business under pressure, Intel is betting big on the Internet of Things and making &amp;hellip; more.
Hey, Alexa Tell Me About My Privacy Rights! For internet-of-things watchers, some information to chew on: several news outlets have reported on a dispute between Amazon and law enforcement &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 25, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Cisco buys AppDynamics for $3.7 billion, plots business performance ZDNet AppDynamics will be run by its CEO David Wadhwani under a new unit housed in Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Internet of things division. Wadhwani will report to Rowan &amp;hellip; more.
DMC X Sheffield Digital Mash Up distract from the real benefits and potential applications, and Internet of Things &amp;hellip; more.
Alipay to Integrate Blockchain into Payment App CoinTelegraph has revealed that Alipay, the payment application developed by Ant Financial a subsidiary of Alibaba, is currently planning to &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 24, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Silicon Labs Makes Internet of Things Grab with Zentri Acquisition Semiconductor vendor Silicon Labs has agreed to acquire cloud-connected Wi-Fi provider Zentri, expanding Silicon Labs&amp;rsquo; presence in the Internet of &amp;hellip; more.
Learn details of the machines of the future to speak through cellular IoT 2G, 3G and 4G LTE are the major cellular technologies used for machine-to-machine communication. The cellular technologies at present have &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 23, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
China Mobile deploys Brocade&amp;rsquo;s NFV to support Internet Plus initiative &amp;hellip; such as fixed and mobile Internet connectivity, cloud computing, Big Data, and the Internet of Things. In addition to providing IP connectivity services, &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain could save banks $8 billion a year, says Accenture Blockchain technology could reduce investment banks&amp;rsquo; infrastructure costs by 30 per cent, according to new report from Accenture. The report &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 22, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Top 5 Hottest Cryptocurrencies Right Now The second difference is that Tether doesn&amp;rsquo;t have its own blockchain like most cryptocurrencies. Instead, it runs on the Omni Layer, which is a platform &amp;hellip; more.
Distinguished Speakers Panel: The Internet of Things 15, 2017 6:00 pm to 9:00 pm. Location: Red and White Club - McMahon &amp;hellip; more.
How smart (or snoopy) do you want your home to be?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 21, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Raising Standards across the Internet of Things role of standards in shaping the Mobile Internet of Things. Dino Flore &amp;hellip; more.
Blockchain for good: Donorcoin makes your money count London Blockchain Week: Crack down on corruption - and help the causes you care about most. The jihadist group Boko Haram are notorious in &amp;hellip; more.
Next Weeks Broker Price Targets For Zayo Group Holdings, Inc. (NYSE:ZAYO) Its products and services enable high-bandwidth applications, such as cloud-based computing, video, mobile, social media and machine-to-machine &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 20, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Marquette Catholic High School Welcomes Students From China for Winter LaPorteCountyLife.com English as a New Language class is held on MQTT&amp;rsquo;s campus and is directed by the schools&amp;rsquo; ENL instructor. Mr. Edwin Shelton, local artist and MQTT&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; more.
Refineries Increase Reliability and Predictability using the Industrial OilVoice Oil refineries are capitalizing on functionality from the Industrial Internet of Things (IIOT). IIoT is the interconnection via the Internet of technologies and &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 19, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things Market Forecast to 2021 with Key Companies Profile, Digital Journal It comprises advanced sensor technologies, machine-to machine communication, real-time data analytics, and machine learning algorithms to &amp;hellip; more.
Why a software-first attitude is a must for Internet of Things era ahead Technology managers need to step up and help business leaders navigate the intricacies of digital competition, and embrace the Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 18, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
5 Things CalAmp Corp. Management Wants You to Know But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean the market is correct in its pessimism for the machine-to-machine communications specialist.As I pointed out at the time, &amp;hellip; more.
What next for the ASX and Blockchain in 2017? The reason that ASX signed up for the Blockchain revolution was that it has for years been delaying the replacement of its 20 year old CHESS clearing &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 17, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Customer Experience In Travel, Let&amp;rsquo;s Get The Basics Right &amp;hellip; technology and pushing the most innovative practices as far as they can go with things like artificial intelligence, chatbots, and the internet of things, &amp;hellip; more.
Lawsuit Reveals Intricacies of Bitcoin Scheme (Brattleboro Reformer) Plaintiffs in a civil suit over bitcoin mining characterized the defendant as the man behind the curtain, in a filing in opposition &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 16, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What insurance industry CIOs predict about insurtech in 2017? This will encompass all the buzzwords that all of us are hearing all around us like Internet of Things (IoT), intelligent apps etc. Internet of things will not &amp;hellip; more.
St. Francis College hosts management festival The student Club of BMS of St. Francis College for Women Arista, hosted its annual national management festival &amp;lsquo;Cypher The Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 15, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Bitseed Review - A Plug &amp;amp; Play Full Bitcoin Node It&amp;rsquo;s what creates the decentralization of the system the fact that thousands of computers around the world own a full copy of the blockchain and are &amp;hellip; more.
Swift explores blockchain in new payments initiative Swift has announced the launch of a Proof of Concept (PoC) to explore whether distributed ledger technology (DLT) can be used by banks to improve &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 14, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Report: Blockchain Slated to Become $8 Billion Global Industry By 2024 The global Blockchain technology market size was valued at USD 509.1 billion in 2015 and is predicted to gain momentum over the forecast period. more.
Russia Embraces Bitcoin - No Plans to Ban Cryptocurrencies The Bank of Russia is not going to take measures to prohibit the use of Bitcoins, recently said deputy chairman Olga Skorobogatov at the Gaidar &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 13, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain: Equibit targets $7m coin offering Equibit Development Corporation, which is building a blockchain-based securities platform, said it plans to raise as much as $7m in an initial coin &amp;hellip; more.
Ericsson, China Mobile Sign Agreement To Cooperate On Internet Of Things (RTTNews.com) - Ericsson ( ERIC ) and China Mobile Communication Co., Ltd. signed a strategic agreement to cooperate on the Internet of Things at &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 12, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What Do IT Pros Think About Emerging Tech? There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of talk about artificial intelligence, virtual reality, internet of things and 3D printers, but which of these are the biggest business drivers? more.
IBM Watson Health and FDA to Collaborate on Blockchain Project IBM Watson Health announced today a collaborative project with the U.S. Food and Drug Administration aimed at applying emerging blockchain &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 11, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Franklinton man sentenced for receiving stolen goods at pawn shop Moseley also pleaded guilty to misdemeanor charges of failing to report daily entries of secondhand goods and changing the identity of things. For that &amp;hellip; more.
Technology cooperation to ease IIoT deployment Cirrus Link Solutions: Middleware vendor supporting MQTT software and server products to enable the distribution of data to users and return &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 9, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Security expert: Weigh online risks with benefits Parts of the Internet of Things a description of the world&amp;rsquo;s growing network connecting devices, buildings, vehicles and everything else with Wifi or &amp;hellip; more.
Technology: Customer convenience will drive innovation Internet of Things (IoT) is what will make it happen. It is the confluence of great hardware with exceptional software which makes the former even more &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 8, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Bosch Dev Kit to Ease IoT Every sensor and wireless chip maker is edging into the Internet of Things (IoT) market, one of the fastest growing international markets, predicted to &amp;hellip; more.
AI, IoT &amp;amp; robotics; 5 cool products at CES 2017 Internet of Things(IoT), Artificial Intelligence(AI) and Virtual reality(VR), since its emergence, have impacted humankind in various ways, directly and &amp;hellip; more.
Intel Announces Compute Card To Power Smart Devices &amp;hellip; modular small form factor compute system for smart appliances, home automation, industrial applications, and other Internet of Things (IoT) devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 7, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
CES 2017: New routers defend smart homes against hacks The &amp;ldquo;internet of things&amp;rdquo; refers to the growing collection of smart gadgets that can be controlled via the net. &amp;ldquo;Pretty soon everything will be connected &amp;hellip; more.
Bloomberg: The Internet of Things Has Gone to the Bedroom 06/01/2017-09:38. Source. First time the National Sleep Foundation has organized a &amp;hellip; more.
China to Restrict Bitcoin Marketing, But Blockchain Firms Unaffected DJ Qian, CEO of blockchain-as-a-service startup BitSE, for example, indicated that the news &amp;ldquo;does not affect its business&amp;rdquo; due to its focus on &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 6, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Verizon and Cypress Bring Secure Connectivity to Robust Internet of Things The offering, which will be commercially available early in the second quarter of 2017, gives developers the ability to access Verizon&amp;rsquo;s ThingSpace &amp;hellip; more.
8 tips to help keep you secure while using the Internet of Things The Internet of Things is only as strong as its weakest link. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s so important to understand and treat each connected device as part of a &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 5, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
AT&amp;amp;T Helping Businesses Unleash Internet of Things Potential LAS VEGAS, Jan. 4, 2017 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;re making it easier for businesses to succeed with the Internet of Things (IoT). Greater efficiencies, new &amp;hellip; more.
$25000 Prize Offered in FTC IoT Security Challenge It appears as if the Federal Trade Commission is getting serious about Internet of Things security issues &amp;ndash; and it wants the public to help find a solution &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 4, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT, cognitive computing is the future: Experts Addressing the gathering of students from various colleges of city, Nasscom&amp;rsquo;s Regional Head Srikanth Srinivasan said Internet of Things was going to &amp;hellip; more.
Intel to Acquire 15 Percent Ownership of Mapmaker HERE Now Intel is adding map functionality to its growing internet of things &amp;hellip; and location-based services for automotive and the Internet of Things (IoT). more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 3, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Predicting What&amp;rsquo;s Next In The World Of Tech At CES Changes in the tech world are coming faster than ever before, and are more complex. The Internet of things, artificial intelligence, robotics, biometrics, &amp;hellip; more.
Hoax? Blake Messick Claimed He Hacked Neighbor&amp;rsquo;s Unsecured Wireless Printer The Inquisitr With the Internet of Things enabling so many things with wireless connectivity from toys to cars to toasters to refrigerators to printers and beyond &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 2, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Duncan Brodie: Flagship pioneering use of the &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; installed in 12 flats in Ipswich, with the aim of improving communications and &amp;hellip; more.
This is the time to face up to cyber threats The Internet of Things (IoT) ecosystem is set to explode, with more than 24 billion devices expected to be connected to the internet by 2019. The sheer &amp;hellip; more.
New Radio-Frequency Identification Protocols for Hack-proofing Devices Soon &amp;hellip; information &amp;ndash; between suppliers and retailers, for example, or between various components of an Internet of Things &amp;ndash; would have obvious benefits,&amp;rdquo; &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Jan 1, 2017</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2017-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Markets Update: Massive Gains Year-to-Date Across Crypto-Markets Ethereum, the second most traded blockchain after Bitcoin, ends the year with more than a 900% gain, despite a second half marred by poor press &amp;hellip; more.
Stocks: Lantronix Inc. (LTRX) gets Hold status by The Zacks Investment DailyQuint &amp;hellip; communications products with a focus on the convergence of mobility with machine-to-machine systems. It provides solutions that enable machines, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Activity spikes on San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things network A little more than a year after launch, San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things (IoT) network has taken off, with a handful of departments planning pilot &amp;hellip; more.
FINTECH: MBAs Are Exploring The Investment Case For Blockchain Technologies Kraken asked MBA programs from around the globe to prepare a video answering the question: If you had $1m to invest across two blockchain &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Slo-mo energy harvesting could see finger presses powering touchscreen New Atlas &amp;hellip; energy into electricity are already widely used to help power wearable electronics, biomedical devices and things in the growing &amp;ldquo;Internet of Things&amp;rdquo;. more.
China urges fresh standards for the internet of things China has called for a global effort to jointly set up a demonstration platform for the internet of things and promote the healthy development of the &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Unfurling the blockchain hype: Why it&amp;rsquo;s all about relationships and trust Just like with many innovations, this first manifestation of Blockchain is no longer the big show. The technology instead inspired the minds of many to &amp;hellip; more.
All About Blockchain - Top 10 Blockchain Reads in 2016 For your interest, here is a recap of the most popular posts in 2016 on Blockchain matters, all aspects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
2017 predictions say 5G&amp;rsquo;ll impact on IoT Internet of things-based attacks, like the botnet that brought down Twitter and Netflix this year, are going to get more ambitious and more damaging. more.
The IoT Demands a New IAM Approach (IoT) will have 24 billion connected devices by the year 2020. more.
Why Cloud may shower billions on only a few tech companies Increasingly, it is also entangled with mobile phones, sensors and all sorts of other devices in the socalled Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT 2017: Virtual Worlds Rise, AI Gets Serious The end of the year is all about trends and predictions for the next year and the Internet of Things is making a grand appearance this time around. more.
R3&amp;rsquo;s Corda blockchain platform now available on Microsoft Azure The platform offers a variety of consensus algorithms for the management and recording of financial transaction on R3 blockchains, to keep financial &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
5G Era: Mobile Carriers Focus on Services Rather than Speeds &amp;hellip; by converging ultra-high speed, hyper connected and ultra-low latency network technologies, artificial intelligence (AI), Internet of Things (IoT) and &amp;hellip; more.
Vladimir Putin may have done us a big favor Another possibility is to impose security standards on the Internet of things the label for connecting cars and home appliances to the Internet. Now &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
DataCore Software Chairman Wins Innovator of the Year at Best in Biz Awards Satellite PR News (press release) &amp;hellip; unpredictable demands of enterprise workloads, business applications, data analytics, Internet of Things (IoT) and highly virtualized environments, &amp;hellip; more.
Tech This Week Offers Your Dose Of Disruptive Tech Every Week !  From the enabling infrastructure for 5G and the Internet of Things, to emerging applications in virtual reality and digital health, the company is shaping &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Drones, IoT influencing information security regulations How has popular consumer technology like the internet of things and drones changed information security threats? Monique Ferraro: It&amp;rsquo;s changed &amp;hellip; more.
Inflight Wi-Fi provider Gogo Launches Bug Bounty Gogo, a familiar provider of Wi-Fi for anyone who flies, has announced the launch of its bug bounty program with Bugcrowd. The payouts will range &amp;hellip; more.
Internet of Things (IoT) Challenge: The Sensor That Cried Wolf My daughter called with a frantic message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Raj Kosaraju: Evaluating Microsoft Versus Linux for IoT interview, Linux is a cancer, and Linux contaminates all other software with &amp;hellip; more.
Top 4 Most Vulnerable Industries To Cyberattack in 2017 The Internet of Things and the Internet of Everything paradigms are causing enterprises and governments to rethink how they collect and process &amp;hellip; more.
New AQ Rewards app by Avanquest Software uses blockchain to reward users Avanquest Software, a global developer of consumer software and apps, has released a new AQ Rewards app that is powered by blockchain &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Corporate Patents on Blockchain Could Create Legal Problems for Startups As the Blockchain essentially a shared, cryptographically secure ledger of transactions evolves beyond its techno-utopian roots and startups like &amp;hellip; more.
Rogers Communications Slips to Sell, Lags Industry Mark Rogers Communications is the first wireless operator in Canada to offer Internet of Things services like End-to-End Incident Management, Farm &amp;hellip; more.
Rachel O&amp;rsquo;Dwyer: Data politics and the internet of things between wild imaginaries of connected futures (&amp;lsquo;Your house will know when &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
7 Last-Minute Tech Gifts for People Who Hate Tech Thanks to the internet of things, even technophobes and luddites can wear a smart shirt or use a wireless speaker. Photo: Getty Images/iStockphoto. more.
Chinese Logistics Industry Enters Blockchain Era with the New Blockchain PR Newswire (press release) Among multiple major events, the founding of the Blockchain Application Sub-Committee initiated by China Federation of Logistics &amp;amp; Purchasing &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Goldman, JPMorgan to invest in blockchain startup Axoni -sources The Axoni deal represents the latest Wall Street effort to gain traction with blockchain, which first emerged as the system underpinning digital currency &amp;hellip; more.
Goldman, JPMorgan to invest in blockchain startup Axoni - sources in blockchain startup Axoni, people familiar with the deal said this week. more.
Connecting my Particle Photon Internet of Things device to the Azure IoT My vacation continues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Google News &amp;amp; Updates: Tech Giant Unveils Internet Of Things (IoT) OS Gamenguide Google finally announced its newest Internet of Things (IoT) platform called Android Things. Essentially based on the original Android OS used on &amp;hellip; more.
IoT device users are open to ads NEW YORK: Almost two-thirds (62%) of US consumers own at least one Internet of Things device, such as a smart TV or fitness tracker, and a similar &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
ABN Amro launches pilot blockchain application for Commercial Real Estate The Netherlands&amp;rsquo; third largest bank, ABN Amro, and its technology partner, IBM, recently launched a pilot to explore how blockchain technology can &amp;hellip; more.
Think cyberthreats are bad now? They&amp;rsquo;ll get worse in 2017 with &amp;lsquo;spear USA TODAY They included predictions about the hacking of presidential candidates and security dangers posed by the Internet of Things, ransomware, complex &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The next multi-billion dollar tech market was quietly born this year, says Business Insider &amp;hellip; on edge computing, which he sees as the next enormous change in computing, the real result of the &amp;ldquo;internet of things,&amp;rdquo; he told Business Insider. more.
Blockchain market for businesses will grow to $20B in 10 years, report says Businesses across the globe spent $2.5 billion this year on blockchain, the cryptographic technology that makes digital currencies like bitcoin possible &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Digitalization changing how products come to life Digital Darwinism is a significant threat, said Helmuth Ludwig, chief information officer at Siemens&amp;rsquo; Munich headquarters. Twenty-six of the Fortune &amp;hellip; more.
New Deloitte Virtual Technology Cluster for Healthcare Can Assist Bitcoin Magazine The Virtual Technology Cluster (VTC) Group, an organization that wants to help major multinational companies to attract emerging and disruptive &amp;hellip; more.
Sigfox and Thinxtra to Launch Internet of Things network in Hong Kong LABEGE, FRANCE and HONG KONG, CHINA&amp;ndash;(Marketwired - Dec 15, 2016) - Sigfox, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading provider of connectivity for the Internet of &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Worldwide Internet of Things (IoT) Market This is one of the comprehensive research report published on Internet of Things (IoT). Within this research report, VENN Research has covered the &amp;hellip; more.
3 benefits a smart city can gain from smart infrastructure John Horn joined Ingenu after serving as president of RacoWireless, a leading provider of machine-to-machine (M2M) connectivity solutions. He led &amp;hellip; more.
HID Global Wins Award for Best Identity &amp;amp; Access Management Solutions HID Global, a worldwide leader in trusted identity solutions, today announced that it was awarded the highest honor as Best IAM Vendor in the Hot &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The 5 Elements to Capturing Value from IoT Getting an Internet of Things Initiative in manufacturing up and running is difficult for several reasons. The ability to target IoT value creation using &amp;hellip; more.
Google&amp;rsquo;s Android Things looks to take control of the IoT landscape With a better connected future in its sights, Google announced a Developers Preview of Android Things, a new platform for the Internet of Things (IoT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
D&amp;amp;H Sees 77% Growth in IoT, 31% in TV Sales in 2016 The distribution company saw sales gains of 77 percent in Internet of Things (IoT), which it defines as smart home, Wi-Fi and Bluetooth connected &amp;hellip; more.
Machine learning and Blockchain power $235bn Insurtech market The researcher also underpin this growth on Blockchain investments which underpins smart contracts. The study, Fintech Futures: Market Disruption, &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
XPED Ltd (ASX:XPE) Delivery of Production Samples Utilising ST Micro ABN Newswire (press release) Xped is pleased to advise that it has begun building samples of the first production ready ADRC&amp;trade; and DiscoverBus&amp;trade; enabled products for &amp;hellip; more.
Monnit Named One of CRN&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things 50 Monnit Corporation announced that CRN has named the wireless sensors company to its 2016 Internet of Things 50 list, which recognizes &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Asavie gets behind the internet of things Asavie, the software company backed by tech multimillionaires and wealth funds, has a unique way of demonstrating the internet of things ability &amp;hellip; more.
Short Interest Worth Watching: What&amp;rsquo;s Propelling Logmein Incorporated Post News The Company&amp;rsquo;s services are focused on markets, such as identity and access management, collaboration and the Internet of Things, and are delivered &amp;hellip; more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Top 5 Insurtech Trends for 2017 The emergence of insurtech has been fueled by new digital capabilities and Internet of Things (IoT) devices that are reducing costs, changing systems &amp;hellip; Blockchain &amp;amp; Fragmentation: We&amp;rsquo;re in a Weird Spot But Boivin, vice president of BNY Mellon&amp;rsquo;s markets group strategy unit, also understands that distributed-ledger technologies like blockchain represent &amp;hellip; &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m Afraid, Dave&amp;rsquo; - Global Havoc-Causing Mirai Malware Evolves, Adapts Mirai (from a Japanese word meaning &amp;lsquo;the future&amp;rsquo;) is a type of malware that not only hijacks &amp;lsquo;zombie&amp;rsquo; computers, but also finds Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; qBiq Launches Kickstarter for Real-Time Monitoring IoT Device TORONTO&amp;ndash;(BUSINESS WIRE)&amp;ndash;Ubiqweus Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Secure IoT Through Oversight, Open Source and Open Standards My idea is that to secure the Internet of things, we need to take a three pronged approach that includes oversight, open source and open standards. Is Machine to Machine Communication (M2M) Dead? M2Mi or Machine-to-Machine Intelligence Corporation was founded in 2006 to enable organizations to create value and monetize their connected &amp;hellip; Startup addresses financial institutions&amp;rsquo; blockchain privacy concerns trusted parties will be able to decrypt their meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Europe Internet Of Things Market Forecast 2016-2023 The global Internet of Things market is poised to grow in 2017-2023. Various reasons for growth of the Internet of things market are growing Internet &amp;hellip; Bluetooth 5 is out: Now will home IoT take off? Bluetooth is aiming straight for the internet of things as the fifth version of the wireless protocol arrives with twice as much speed for low-power &amp;hellip; Klarm China Promotes 5 Axis Machining Services This is advantageous in the event of power outages, as well as when moving the magnetic pallet from machine to machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
How the Internet Revolutionized Offline Retail [Infographic] Finally, in the near future, the Internet of Things (IoT) will result in the merger of the online and offline worlds to give consumers a seamless experience &amp;hellip; Spies in Your Stocking: Privacy, Smart Toys and the Internet of Things Internet, is one of the biggest current trends in tech one research firm &amp;hellip; Privacy groups urge investigation of &amp;lsquo;internet of toys&amp;rsquo; data protection for children in the rapidly emerging internet of things,&amp;rdquo; said &amp;hellip; RSK: Making the Bitcoin Blockchain More Like Ethereum 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Industrial Internet Peek into tomorrow, today Industrial Internet Peek into tomorrow, today. With the industrial Internet and Internet of Things (IoT), we can, today, pre-empt breakdowns and even &amp;hellip; IHE on FHIR: emerging interoperability standards in action This approach to machine-to-machine communication is rapidly gaining support in the industry, as it is less time consuming and complex to implement &amp;hellip; A Chinese 20 Million Dollars Venture Fund is Ready to Finance Bitcoin The Merkle Huiyin Group, a Chinese-based investment firm, announced the creation of a Blockchain-centered subsidiary, Huiyin Blockchain Venture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT eminently hackable 900000 routers down and millions vulnerable Hacked Internet of Things (IoT) devices are powering massive botnets and cybercriminals are offering DDoS attacks as a service. 900,000 XyXEL &amp;hellip; IoT Applied in Retail: 7 Real Examples Many business have started hearing about Internet of Things. There are not too many cases of big retailers implementing pilots and incorporating &amp;hellip; China&amp;rsquo;s Huawei To Build R&amp;amp;D Base In Tokyo Huawei plans to cooperate with Japanese enterprises to promote Internet of Things and 5G technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Industrial Analytics Based On Internet Of Things Will Revolutionize Forbes Predictive and prescriptive maintenance of machines (79%), customer/marketing related analytics (77%) and analysis of product usage in the field &amp;hellip; Tata Docomo Business Services launches new product, unveils growth strategy &amp;hellip; Mobility Solutions, and new age digital technologies such as Internet-of-Things (IoT)/Machine-to-Machine (M2M) have found a steady uptake in the &amp;hellip; Russia&amp;rsquo;s Central Bank Hacked, $31 Million Stolen Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank suffered a major cyberattack that made it possible for hackers to steal no less than 2 billion rubles, which is approximately $31 &amp;hellip; Industry 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain: redefining the future of real estate? who may not trust or indeed know one another, to share a set of verified, &amp;hellip; NASA forays into the Internet of Things Las Vegas Many of the commercial products around the Internet of Things may just seem like toys, but officials at NASA&amp;rsquo;s Jet Propulsion Laboratory &amp;hellip; I made my dumb appliances smarter with the Internet of Things Sometimes I forget things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
First post-explosion SpaceX launch set for Dec. 16 Space-X&amp;rsquo;s Falcon 9 rocket with the Jason-3 satellite aboard, stands ready for flight at Vandenberg Air Force Base, Calif. on Saturday, Jan. 16, 2016. Supply chain finance on blockchain debuts in India about seven years old, the open source platform serving the bitcoin network was &amp;hellip; How PwC&amp;rsquo;s Vulcan Blockchain Seeks to Bring Banks into the New Digital Era The Vulcan offering marks PwC&amp;rsquo;s continuing commitment to bringing blockchain technology to financial services and other industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Dec 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-12-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Global Internet Of Things Market By Application Forecast 2016-2023 Internet of Things finds application in multiple verticals like smart energy, building and home automation, smart manufacturing, connected logistics, &amp;hellip; Global Smart Infrastructure - The Direction is Smart Cities and AI The latest developments are in M2M (machine-to-machine) and IoT (Internet of Things) sphere where we link machines and different data sets &amp;hellip; Avnet Inks Deal with relayr to Support Internet of Things Electronics and IT distributor Avnet Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Shutterstock to Present at the Raymond James Technology Investors SYS-CON Media (press release) NEW YORK, Nov. 29, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Shutterstock, Inc. (NYSE: SSTK), a leading global provider of imagery and music, announced today that &amp;hellip; ChannelAdvisor to Present Marketplace Strategies for Brands Selling on SYS-CON Media (press release) ChannelAdvisor Corporation (NYSE: ECOM), a leading provider of cloud-based e-commerce solutions that enable retailers and branded &amp;hellip; Hyperledger Project and Chamber of Digital Commerce partner for blockchain Automated Trader Linux Foundation&amp;rsquo;s Hyperledger Project partners with the Chamber of Digital Commerce to advocate for blockchain-friendly policy and regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Roundup Of Internet Of Things Forecasts And Market Estimates, 2016 This years&amp;rsquo; series of Internet of Things (IoT) and Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) forecasts reflect a growing focus on driving results using &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things is making hospitals more vulnerable to hackers Adding Internet of Things technologies can increase risks so needs to be managed, warns security agency. Image: iStock. Ransomware and denial of &amp;hellip; The evolution of cyber attacks powered by the internet of things These are but a few of the latest conveniences made possible by the Internet of Things a concept that describes the networked interconnectivity of &amp;hellip; Understanding General Electric&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things Story in 10 Slides The Internet of Things is changing the world by connecting devices and generating insights from the resulting data to make processes more efficient, &amp;hellip; Verizon&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things Acquisition History in 10 Slides As the wireless-carrier market continues to find itself in a challenging climate because of saturation and heavy competition, Verizon (NYSE: VZ) is &amp;hellip; Blockchain has the potential to revolutionize the supply chain Hopefully, the supply chain problem can be remedied with blockchain, the emerging technology that has proven its value in bringing transparency and &amp;hellip; Blockchain and IoT devices could revolutionize the supply chain A number of companies are rolling out new technology solutions that pair blockchain with connected sensors to provide history, visibility, and security &amp;hellip; Argentina&amp;rsquo;s Central Bank is Warming Up to Blockchain With its currency volatility, one might expect Argentina&amp;rsquo;s central bank to be hesitant in exploring blockchain technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Safran Identity &amp;amp; Security Trusts in Comprion Network Bridge for Remote SIM IoT Business News (press release) (blog) Comprion has announced today that they supply Safran Identity &amp;amp; Security with their &amp;hellip; As a global leader in security and identity solutions, Safran Identity &amp;hellip; This testing task is very complex as it involves a variety of components, like &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Broker Outlook For The Week Ahead Acorn Energy, Inc. (ACFN) &amp;hellip; Security Sonar Solutions (DSIT), Smart Grid Distribution Automation (GridSense) and Machine-to-Machine Critical Asset Monitoring &amp;amp; Control (M2M) &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things (IoT) and Machine-to-Machine (M2M) Communication Market: Digital Journal The global Internet of Things (IoT) and Machine-To-Machine (M2M) market is segmented into four major categories, on the basis of technology and &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Noven Financial Group adds VirnetX Holding Corporation (VHC) to its TheFounders Daily &amp;hellip; voice over Internet protocol (VoIP) mobile services streaming video file transfer remote desktop and machine-to-machine (M2M) communications. Bitcoin Pioneer Charlie Shrem Launches New Blockchain Venture Intellisys Capital, he said, now intends to issue tokens representing blockchain-based shares in manufacturing, real estate or even sanitary waste &amp;hellip; Walmart and IBM test blockchain for custom supply chain tracking Distributed ledger blockchain technology may be be known for its original use for powering bitcoin and more recently for its financial technology &amp;hellip; Bitcoin startup Blockchain hits 10 millionth wallet Blockchain said that it is seeing record levels of activity across its platform, which signifies that people are embracing the need for a more globally &amp;hellip; Blockchain Issues Ten Millionth Bitcoin Wallet due to Unprecedented Finance Magnates Blockchain Issues Ten Millionth Bitcoin Wallet due to Unprecedented Activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Teleradiology platforms: the business case for blockchain Teleradiology is ripe for blockchain. Healthcare image diagnosis and treatment is based on trust; It could be based on truth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how. Air Force Chief Gen. David Goldfein Eyes Common Operating System for Data ExecutiveGov We got to get into the next stage, which is machine-to-machine, human/machine teaming, and artificial intelligence to turn all that data into &amp;hellip; IBM Watson launches global consulting unit for internet of things IBM has launched its first global consulting practice for the internet of things (IoT), a part of its major artificial intelligence investment Watson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Political Party D66 Proposes Stricter European Internet of Things The Merkle Regulatory bodies are taking a close look at Internet of Things devices. In fact, political party D66 has proposed a new guideline to ban sales of all IoT &amp;hellip; Is There Any Value In Blockchain-based Supply Chain Transparency? Depending on who you pose the question to, blockchain technology will either change our daily lives or have no impact at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
More Than 1100 Professionals Attend RSA Conference 2016 Abu Dhabi &amp;hellip; RSA: As the world transforms digitally and people and things become more interconnected - cloud computing, Internet of Things (IoT), smart cities &amp;hellip; Blockchain: Quickly off the starting Blocks The traditional banking sector has shown its resilience through the years, surviving the financial crisis and global regulatory crackdowns to remain &amp;hellip; &amp;lsquo;Shark Tank&amp;rsquo; South Africa Sees Its First Bitcoin Investment I made the investment in bitcoin because I believe that it&amp;rsquo;s the right blockchain for the Augmentors team to leverage to build a globally accessible &amp;hellip; Flipkart&amp;rsquo;s Bansals on why they invest in startups &amp;amp; what have they learnt ETtech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Professor to Congress: &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things security is woefully inadequate&amp;rsquo; cybersecurity breaches severe enough to shut down hospitals and other vital &amp;hellip; Nokia drives ahead with internet of vehicles According to Li Kun, director of business development of internet of things at Nokia Greater China, the 5-km test route is the first of its kind in China. Trump&amp;rsquo;s plan to spend on infrastructure leads companies to pitch their Los Angeles Times &amp;ldquo;The country should focus on infrastructure investments that incorporate Internet of Things (IoT) technology and artificial intelligence to improve &amp;hellip; How Procurement Could Secure Internet of Things Securing the internet of things is among the federal government&amp;rsquo;s largest technological challenges and a policy nightmare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Ethereum Foundation Has Set a New Date for Blockchain Hard Fork Ethereum, the decentralized smart contract and blockchain platform has gone through a rough patch of late. After delaying the hard-fork that was &amp;hellip; &amp;lsquo;Alexa, make me comfortable&amp;rsquo;: How the Internet of Things is hitting home Touchscreen mirror In a 2011 video, Corning Glass showed off a lot of the technologies that would come to be known as the Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Korea Exchange uses blockchain tech for new startup marketplace The Korea Exchange is using blockchain technology for document and identity authentication at a new marketplace for trading equity shares in &amp;hellip; Blockchain wallet adding bitcoin buying option Blockchain will soon provide users of their ever popular wallet with the option to buy bitcoin. After eight months of development, the service launches &amp;hellip; Congress had an office that gave expert tech analysis; let&amp;rsquo;s bring it back In fact, according to Cisco, the estimated number of machine-to-machine connections will grow from 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Blockchain: A Guide for Legal and Business Professionals Solutions from Thomson Reuters. Get free shipping on law books. Deloitte is partnering with a London startup to launch a blockchain Business Insider LONDON, Nov 15 (Reuters) - London-based fintech company SETL and global auditing firm Deloitte have joined forces to produce a contactless card &amp;hellip; Healthcare, retail industries give blockchain a try The technology in question isn&amp;rsquo;t something one might expect to see in the healthcare IT toolkit; rather, it&amp;rsquo;s blockchain, the technology that underpins &amp;hellip; US Ganjapreneurs Look to Blockchain for Nascent Legal Cannabis Industry There are numerous Blockchain startups and cryptocurrencies who stand to benefit from the normalization of marijuana and in last week&amp;rsquo;s green letter &amp;hellip; OCBC Bank Pilots Blockchain-based Funds Transfer Between Bank Subsidiaries Blockchain technology can play a big part in faster, more convenient, and cheaper transfers of value across borders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
3 Top Internet of Things Stocks to Buy Now After a seemingly constant stream of discussion by the media, it&amp;rsquo;s hard not to have heard of the Internet of Things. The trend of connecting everything to &amp;hellip; How the &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; Could Transform the Food Supply Chain An international leader in refrigeration and food safety technology, Emerson is leveraging the Internet of Things to help customers meet these new &amp;hellip; CABA launches Connected Multi-Dwelling Units (MDUs) and Internet of Things Contractor Mag The Continental Automated Buildings Association, through its Connected Home Council, has launched a collaborative research study entitled &amp;hellip; Samsung bets $8B on connected cars with Harman deal &amp;hellip; and Internet-of-Things (IoT) devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The 4 Best Dividend Stocks of 2025 IoT in particular looks to be a big driver over the next decade thanks to an explosion of machine-to-machine communications and the company&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; Manufacturers Get Smarter for Industry 4.0 The second level is machine-to-machine connectedness where intelligent machines self-diagnose and self-correct. In these smart factories, machines &amp;hellip; Building cybersecurity capacity through benchmarking: the Global The European Sting With the advent of machine-to-machine communications, big data, smart cities and connected people, it would be a costly oversight to underestimate &amp;hellip; Hong Kong Central Bank: Blockchain Holds &amp;lsquo;Enormous Potential&amp;rsquo; The move comes just over two months after the two sides began collaborating on blockchain applications, a process that has seen activity amongst &amp;hellip; R3 Banks Trial Blockchain Identity Registry Ten global banks have tested a distributed ledger-based know-your-customer registry through the R3 blockchain consortium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
SmartMetric Asks, Is It Time For A Biometric National ID Card In this age of insecurity, the need for a national ID Card is compelling. From law agencies being able to rabidly identify the validity of an identity &amp;hellip; Red squirrels! Adorable, right? Wrong they&amp;rsquo;re riddled with leprosy Blighty&amp;rsquo;s dwindling population of red squirrels is riddled with leprosy, according to new research. Not full-on leprosy, but leprosy-lite, according to a &amp;hellip; Better together: improving the management of &amp;lsquo;systems of systems&amp;rsquo; With the development of the &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo;, the ability to do this is &amp;hellip; field of research - the Internet of Things,&amp;rsquo; says Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
FG grants petrovice patent on solution for last mile connectivity &amp;amp; Guardian &amp;hellip; connectivity with the use of 802.11af WI-FI ( establishing connectivity through machine to machine integrated 802.11af in auto mobile, POS machine, &amp;hellip; Internet of Things Drives Focus on Edge Computing Data Center Frontier: Edge computing and the Internet of Things are currently two of the hottest topics in the data center industry. How might these &amp;hellip; Cisco/Ericsson: Assessing the mega-deal a year later &amp;hellip; management and control, and global services to offer integrated systems for service providers, mobile enterprises, and Internet of Things packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Everything will change our lives but cyber gangs can&amp;rsquo;t wait to Irish Independent The statistic we so often hear about the Internet of Things is that by 2020 there&amp;rsquo;ll be 20.8bn connected devices in operation worldwide. What we often &amp;hellip; HID Global delivers new solutions that secure IoT applications for smart SecurityInfoWatch London, November 2nd 2016 - HID Global, a worldwide leader in secure identity solutions, today announced new solutions that secure Internet of &amp;hellip; Using Drones to Hack Smart Light Bulbs, the Internet of Things Many cybersecurity officials have warned about Internet of Things vulnerabilities, but researchers have demonstrated one particular weakness and &amp;hellip; Interconnected machines set to change out lives The Internet of Things - a network of connected devices - is the future of online technology, writes Kim MacDonald.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
How Hills CEO David Lenz plans to get distie back to growth Lenz also hinted at further investment opportunities in IoT and machine-to-machine learning, particularly in physical security and surveillance. Internet of Things is the only constant: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s Nishant Batra As India embraces Internet of Things (IoT), it is believed that the country will finally catch up with the world when 5G is deployed. Nishant Batra, global &amp;hellip; Lisk Delegates to Prepare for Forging Rewards Lisk, the blockchain application platform, announced today plans to issue block rewards to Lisk delegates, a critical milestone that will be reached &amp;hellip; Excelpoint Expands Its Portfolio in India With the Distributorship of Marketwired (press release) More specifically, the combination will allow developments in segments such as machine-to-machine connectivity, security and surveillance, factory &amp;hellip; MTN and Huawei Launched the first NB-IoT solution in Africa &amp;hellip; Today, MTN and Huawei jointly launched the Smart Water Metering solution, the first Narrowband Internet of Things (NB-IoT) solution in Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Nokia joins Bristol&amp;rsquo;s programmable city initiative The high-powered operating system developed by Bristol University will host this machine-to-machine communication, allowing the development of a &amp;hellip; Webjet tests blockchain for hotel bookings ASX-listed Webjet has just completed a six-month blockchain proof of concept for the travel industry. In collaboration with Microsoft, the companies &amp;hellip; Does the Internet of Things Need a Standardized Communication Architecture? The true power of the Internet of Things is its far-reaching foundationthe more devices we connect, the more powerful our data and insights will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Your WeMo Smart Home Device May Be Spying On Your Android Phone As if the threat of malicious Internet of Things devices is not troublesome enough, security researchers continue to discover new flaws and &amp;hellip; Fine Arts Student of the Week &amp;ldquo;The topic this year is whether the benefits are provided by the &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; outweigh the harms of decreased personal privacy and is it a good &amp;hellip; Korean Startup Presents DIY Internet of Things By assembling the right modules together, users can create devices that function in a specific manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Upgrades And Downgrades For I.D. Systems, Inc. (IDSY) I.D. Systems, Inc. (I.D. Systems) develops, markets and sells wireless machine-to-machine solutions for managing and securing enterprise assets, &amp;hellip; WenZhan Song named Mickey A. Brown Professor in Engineering at UGA Cyber-physical systems, also known as the internet of things, are smart systems that link the physical world with the virtual world of information &amp;hellip; Blockchain Project Brings Time-Based Cryptocurrency to Change the Labor CryptoCoinsNews ChronoBank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Caterpillar introduces oscillatory vibe system with new CB10 asphalt Equipment World Magazine &amp;hellip; the Cat Compaction Control system, such as Auto-Adjustable Compaction, machine-to-machine communication and intelligent compaction features. Tyfone looks to open-source to solve IoT security issues The Internet of Things will connect through over 50 billion IoT hubs by 2020, creating a huge threat surface for attack by hackers and cybercriminals, &amp;hellip; Mobile Edge Computing (MEC) Market - Global Industry Analysis, Size, openPR (press release) MEC is an important part of edge computing and is applied on several frameworks including machine to machine (M2M), big data analytics and &amp;hellip; OTT and IoT evolution: Consumer choice fuels innovation The Internet of Things (IoT) world may be exciting, but there are serious technical challenges that need to be addressed, especially by developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IBM Trials Blockchain For Supply Chain Dispute Resolution Bitcoin showed IBM&amp;rsquo;s Jerry Cuomo what blockchain could do, but anonymous ledgers didn&amp;rsquo;t meet the needs of the company&amp;rsquo;s largest enterprise &amp;hellip; KT, LG Uplus Join Hands to Commercialize Internet of Things SEOUL, Nov. 3 (Korea Bizwire) KT Corp. and LG Uplus Corp., South Korea&amp;rsquo;s second- and third-largest mobile carriers, unveiled a deal Thursday to &amp;hellip; Canonical Focuses On IoT Security With Ubuntu Core 16 It has become apparent that Internet of Things devices need a major security upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Kleiner Perkins VC shares lessons from IoT attacks, cleantech bubble SILICON VALLEY Dave Mount has had a front-row seat to the evolution of the Internet of Things and cleantech bubble as an investing partner at &amp;hellip; KT, LG Uplus join hands to commercialize Internet of Things SEOUL, Nov. 3 (Yonhap) &amp;ndash; KT Corp. and LG Uplus Corp., South Korea&amp;rsquo;s second- and third-largest mobile carriers, unveiled a deal Thursday to work &amp;hellip; Nightingale Smart Home Sleep System from Cambridge Sound Management Uses Yahoo Sports Cambridge Sound Management, a leader in commercial sound masking, is using Ayla Networks&amp;rsquo; Internet of Things (IoT) cloud platform to help people &amp;hellip; Popular on JD Supra (Or What Brexit, Blockchain, and Estate Planning for JD Supra (press release) For your interest, here&amp;rsquo;s a quick recap of popular reads published on JD Supra last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
TechFlash Q&amp;amp;A: Kleiner Perkins VC shares lessons from IoT attacks, Silicon Valley Business Journal The next 38 billion connections are going to be more about machine-to-machine communications. Those machine-to-machine communications are &amp;hellip; Chuck Robbins: IoT - it&amp;rsquo;s happening now Fast forward to Q2 and machine-to-machine connections were greater than phones and tablets combined. It&amp;rsquo;s happening. We&amp;rsquo;re connecting vending &amp;hellip; Stockholm Bridges Join the Internet of Things, Tweeting Details About Their Electronics360 The bridges, which could be considered the next object to join the Internet of Things, can even tweet their conditions throughout the course of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Nov 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-11-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Onchain to deliver framework for Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s blockchain-powered email CoinReport First open-source universal blockchain framework Onchain announced in a press release sent to CoinReport that its consortium chain product, the &amp;hellip; IoT interoperability: Where it stands and what comes next Interoperability is a crucial missing piece to the progress of IoT, according to a report by McKinsey titled Unlocked the potential of the internet of things &amp;hellip; Nimbrix launches blockchain consortium and platform The Nimbrix buy-side platform will use cloud, open API, Software-as-a- Service (SaaS) and blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Editorial: Manufacturers need to better secure internet of things The more we learn about the cyberattack that brought down much of the Internet in the United States last Friday, the more appalling it becomes. Marcel Schouwenaar: Sooner or later this is going to come to us all us more acquainted with the Internet of Things. This is part 5 of a &amp;hellip; Taology: How the Blockchain Works for Creators in the Music Industry industry abused by technology and in dire need of reforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
P2P content distributor DECENT expands to Asia and Europe DECENT has also established a blockchain development hub in Yerevan, Armenia whose mission is to develop products enabling the exchange of &amp;hellip; Legislating Bitcoin: Blockchain Technology in Government Rep. Mick Mulvaney, a South Carolina Republican, discusses blockchain technology in government with Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s Scarlet Fu and Matt Miller on &amp;hellip; GE The Industrial Internet of Things Company We all know about the promise of the Internet of Things or IoT which is the vision of every object around us being connected to the cloud, from our &amp;hellip; Praetorian Partners with Microsoft to Help Secure the Internet of Things Microsoft recognizes Praetorian as a &amp;ldquo;best-in-class&amp;rdquo; Internet of Things (IoT) global auditing partner and a founding member of its new Security Program &amp;hellip; No guarantees with the Internet of Things Disruptors like Uber gain a temporary advantage, but no guarantees, by dislodging others, writes Victor Kgomoeswana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
New report examines the internet of things (IoT) in utility market that WhaTech The report &amp;ldquo;Internet of Things (IoT) in Utility Market by Software (Analytics, Security, Smart Grid Management, Predictive Asset Maintenance, and CIS &amp;hellip; Authoritative misinformation: blockchain and the humor of bad predictions The pitted history of innovation is fraught with bad information, poor advice and unstable experts. The overly enthusiastic to the sorely pessimistic &amp;hellip; How the Internet of Things Can Impact Customer Experience Being able to wave your phone at it, detect a sensor in it, Gillett said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Web devs want to make the Internet of S**t worse. Much worse Vendors including Google have spent a few years crafting an API they hope to push into browsers that will make this month&amp;rsquo;s Internet of Things &amp;hellip; Mitsubishi Heavy Industries Machine Tool Develops MSS300 Super Skiving SYS-CON Media (press release) TOKYO, Oct 27, 2016 - (JCN Newswire) - Mitsubishi Heavy Industries Machine Tool, Co., Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of things: Just what the doctor ordered This is just one example of the potential benefits of the internet of things coming to healthcare.Across the world, pharmaceutical companies are now &amp;hellip; Internet of Things gets wakeup call from fridge &amp;ldquo;Mirai is a huge disaster for the &amp;ldquo;Internet of Things, &amp;lsquo;&amp;rdquo; said a representative for XiongMai in an emailed statement to CNNMoney&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;This is the first time &amp;hellip; Cobalt DL commences beta testing with FX participants using blockchain EconoTimes Cobalt DL that leverages blockchain to re-engineer post-trade processing for the institutional FX market, has announced the commencement of beta &amp;hellip; VT Networks: Finding a business through the Internet of Things Mark Bannon and Will Ferguson, co-founders of VT Networks, are part of an emerging breed of young entrepreneurs whose businesses have been &amp;hellip; Zcash to be Integrated with Jaxx Blockchain Wallet Creators of the universal blockchain wallet Jaxx, Decentral has announced plans to integrate the new Zcash blockchain into its entire suite of software &amp;hellip; Safran Identity &amp;amp; Security to Expand to the Silicon Valley Being at the forefront of biometrics, digital identity and security technologies, it was the next logical next step for us to become a part of the vibrant &amp;hellip; Internet of Things Devices Used to Create Friday&amp;rsquo;s DDoS Attack I&amp;rsquo;ve also written previously about how the &amp;lsquo;internet of things&amp;rsquo; will affect traffic loads and thus users and content providers that rely on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
NSD and CSDC pen MoU with an eye on blockchain Both parties have also agreed to cooperate in FinTech developments with a particular focus on the application of blockchain technology in the &amp;hellip; The Day of the Zombie Baby Monitors: When hackers weaponized the Internet Washington Post The attack appears to be an unprecedented exploitation of the Internet of Things, a term that includes more and more devices that offer user &amp;hellip; SMEs can benefit from riding the wave of Internet of Things (IoT) IoT powers machine-to-machine automation and generates big data, which help businesses optimise processes automatically, minimizing waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
BREAKINGVIEWS-Internet of Things gets wakeup call from fridge It&amp;rsquo;s a clear warning for Cisco Systems, Alphabet and other investors moving headlong into the so-called Internet of Things about security risks. Internet of Things That are Trying to Attack You connect to the internet. While I&amp;rsquo;m aware I just repeated the name in a different way it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;hellip; How your business&amp;rsquo;s devices and networks may be used in cyberattacks &amp;hellip; meantime, security experts are pointing the finger at unsecured cameras, routers or other Internet-connected devices, called the &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo;, &amp;hellip; Security fears for &amp;lsquo;internet of things&amp;rsquo; But security experts said that many of the devices would never be fixed and that the broader security threat posed by the internet of Things would get &amp;hellip; US to release Internet of Things principles after Friday&amp;rsquo;s cyberattacks WASHINGTON The U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Companies urged to use multiple vendors in wake of cyber attack Eliminating the threat from the unsecured devices that make up what&amp;rsquo;s often called the Internet of Things will be a much tougher task, however. Cotton shipment pioneers blockchain trade transaction COMMONWEALTH Bank has announced it has done the first global trade transaction between two independent banks combining the emerging &amp;hellip; Accelerated aims to speed up sales with NPS &amp;hellip; of LTE, 4G and 3G router products ideal for retail or branch locations or even Machine to Machine (M2M) and Internet of Things (IoT) environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Safello acquires ICBIT and appoints founder as new CTO Safello and Everledger were the only bitcoin and blockchain technology companies out of ten in that session. The thirteen-week networking, &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things is under attack, and it could change our future Mashable The Internet of Things (IoT) winter, that is. All those digital routers, DVRs, &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; kitchen appliances and IP-enabled cameras you assumed were &amp;hellip; Hackers used &amp;lsquo;smart&amp;rsquo; home devices to carry out Dyn cyberattack Security firm Flashpoint confirmed the attack used &amp;ldquo;botnets&amp;rdquo; infected with a form of malware known as &amp;ldquo;Mirai&amp;rdquo; to access an &amp;ldquo;Internet of Things&amp;rdquo; made up &amp;hellip; Coding Battle - The Internet of Things Monday, October 24, 2016 at Microsoft, Zaventem, Zaventem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things security holes partly to blame for massive internet The Denver Post Abaove are RFID tags to keg lines at the Crazy Mountain Brewery June 9, 2016. Experts say Internet of Things devices that still have default &amp;hellip; The fourth industrial revolution and blockchain Lier - 21 oktober 2016. Ben van Lier. In 1954, German philosopher Martin &amp;hellip; Blockchain platform developed by banks to be open-source LONDON: A blockchain platform developed by a group that includes more than 70 of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest financial institutions is making its code &amp;hellip; Half of Americans Discouraged from Purchasing Internet of Things Awareness Month, IT security firm ESET in collaboration with the National &amp;hellip; dweet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
(Paid Event) MQTT: The Protocol of The Internet of Things devices connected to a network to merge the digital with the physical, IBM extends partnership with 21Vianet to deploy Blockchain in China IBM seems to be interested in pushing blockchain aggressively and this time it is aiming at China. IBM and 21Vianet, a provider of Internet data center &amp;hellip; (Paid Event) MQTT: The Protocol of The Internet of Things devices connected to a network to merge the digital with the physical, Why Verizon will struggle to achieve long-term revenue growth 5G technology will provide Verizon high-bandwidth, low latency machine-to-machine communication, which will be critical for precise IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The 5th China Cloud Expo Inaugurates with Shiny Top-Notch Technology to be Yahoo Finance The 5th China Huizhou Internet of Things and Cloud Computing Expo (the Cloud Expo) will be held in Huizhou convention and exhibition center from &amp;hellip; IT&amp;rsquo;s latest buzzword: Analytics of Things? For the Internet of Things to provide business value, it requires a smart network that supports a growing array of people, processes and things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What Does Disney Really Want Blockchain Technology For? Walt Disney Company (DIS) became the latest organization to jump onto the blockchain bandwagon after it released an open source version of its &amp;hellip; &amp;lsquo;GAME Changer&amp;rsquo; Announced at Coinsbank Blockchain Summit in Turkey The beautiful setting of the Mediterranean Sea on the Turkish Riviera welcomed some of the brightest minds in blockchain to the Coinsbank Summit. Infosys Finacle Partners With Emirates NBD and ICICI Bank to Launch Blockchain News Blockchain technology offers unprecedented opportunities to transform banking as we know it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Franklin Wireless Unveils the 4G Connected Smart Boombox OTCQB : FKWL) is a global leader in innovative hardware and software products that support machine-to-machine (M2M) applications and the Internet &amp;hellip; How to Make Your First IoT Product a Great One The Internet of Things (IoT) is often talked about as some distant future vision. Consumers dream about connected lives; journalists posture about how &amp;hellip; CIOs Set to Play Key Role in &amp;lsquo;Civilization Architecture&amp;rsquo; These domains are the Internet of Things, ecosystems, customer experienceincreasingly reshaped by the advent of chatbots and, at the center, &amp;hellip; CloudOne Presenting At The 4th Annual Internet Of Things Summit Chicago This year&amp;rsquo;s Summit will explore some of the timeliest issues impacting the Internet of Things, such as data ownership and governance, said Fred &amp;hellip; Vodafone strikes global internet of things deal with Inmarsat Inmarsat and Vodafone have agreed a global deal that will provide internet connectivity to far flung parts of the world only accessible to satellite &amp;hellip; abu dhabi securities exchange to launch blockchain evoting service Abu Dhabi Securities Exchange (ADX) has announced that it is using blockchain technology for eVoting services, which will allow the concerned &amp;hellip; digital federal credit union joins chamber of digital commerce Chamber of Digital Commerce, the leading trade association representing the blockchain industry, has announced that Digital Federal Credit Union &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things is in Trouble: Needs Fast &amp;amp; Safe DNS billion websites online today and there will be an estimated 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
In China, Two Cities Mirror Blockchain-Bitcoin Divide In this light, some rivalry is as inevitable, and it&amp;rsquo;s now spilling over into the country&amp;rsquo;s blockchain industry. In Beijing, visitors are likely to meet &amp;ldquo;bitcoin &amp;hellip; The Time Is Now For Blockchain-Based Voting Systems A blockchain-based solution should alleviate these concerns, although it remains to be seen if and when that will be integrated. Although the outcome &amp;hellip; Open Music Initiative Adds Intel Technology to Help Simplify How Creators Billboard The Open Music Initiative (OMI), an open-source framework for music rights and licensing, has announced that Intel&amp;rsquo;s blockchain technology, Sawtooth &amp;hellip; Online Platform Ask The Doctor Adds Bitcoin to Payment Options to Protect CoinTelegraph The North American health sector itself has started to explore Blockchain-based technologies and Canada is already embracing Bitcoin as a form of &amp;hellip; Don&amp;rsquo;t let your Internet of Things home go to the dark side Thanks to Internet of Things, you can see who is at your home&amp;rsquo;s front door when you&amp;rsquo;re miles away at work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Collaboration key as new threats emerge Kathy Gibson reports from Huawei Safe Cities Summit in Nairobi The nature of threats is changing, not least the issues that citizens will soon face &amp;hellip; Du CEO: Cyber security should be at heart of organisations thought Eminent international speakers raised key issues including Cognitive Security, Security for 5G, Internet of Things, Cloud Security, and Security in the &amp;hellip; What Is &amp;lsquo;Blockchain&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp; What Will It Mean For Your Tech Strategy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Identity for the Internet of Things Internet of Things, wherever they need to connect users, devices, and &amp;hellip; CNBC Exclusive: CNBC Transcript: Honeywell Chairman and CEO David Cote CNBC Now, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about internet of things and turbo golden age. These were terms that were introduced and far more about software, where who you&amp;rsquo;re &amp;hellip; chronicled demonstrates drone identity and access control system prototype EconoTimes The company, currently focused on developing a blockchain-hosted registry for the Internet of Things (IoT), has released a video that showcases a &amp;hellip; Trust Disrupted: Bitcoin and the Blockchain episode 6 analyzes the future The final episode of this six-part series explores the future implications of Bitcoin and blockchain technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain: unlocking its potential in commercial banking it to understand its potential to deliver efficiencies and reduce risks. Agenda Announced for OMA&amp;rsquo;s IoT Developer Seminar and Webinar &amp;hellip; traditional cellular operator networks and emerging networks supporting machine-to-machine device communications for the Internet of Things (IoT). Should the Internet of Vibrating Things be worried? It&amp;rsquo;s been a bad period for Canada&amp;rsquo;s Standard Innovation Corp., with the news that their popular connected pleasure device (aka a vibratornow &amp;hellip; Verizon Taps the Elements, to Offer Airborne LTE Ops in Future Verizon has exerted high focus on the Internet of Things when it comes to networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Leaky IoT devices help hackers attack e-commerce sites Get the scoop on the internet of things at its most fundamental level and find out where it&amp;rsquo;s headed, in InfoWorld&amp;rsquo;s downloadable PDF and ePub. Blockchain technology may help secure the nuclear weapons of the future DARPA is looking into the use of Blockchain technology to help secure some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most powerful weapons and assets. Since it can easily &amp;hellip; Why Jessi Baker, chief executive of Provenance, is using blockchain for The Australian Financial Review But Jessi Baker, chief executive of Provenance, is figuring out how the blockchain, the technology underpinning Bitcoin, could be used to track the &amp;hellip; ZTE presents vision for future in Athens M stands for mobile to man, man to machine, machine to machine, while Information, Communication and Technology are the other three pillars of this &amp;hellip; Wizards of the digital age: West Michigan tech leaders change the world Rapid Growth The Internet of Things is pushing the boundaries of technology, and West Michigan leaders have keen insights on a frontier that is revolutionizing the &amp;hellip; This Indian IoT Product In China Shows How Factories Will Be Part Of The Forbes I was intrigued to discover how an IoT (internet of things) product made by an Indian startup, Flutura, in Bangalore is playing a transformative role in &amp;hellip; Tiffani Bova to AT&amp;amp;T Partners: IoT Success Requires Mobility Chops AT&amp;amp;T Partner Exchange Summit - AT&amp;amp;T partners got another warning that if they want to have success with the Internet of Things (IoT), they must start &amp;hellip; Social Security CIO: IT modernization can&amp;rsquo;t be &amp;lsquo;safe, comfortable&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Right now we think electronic medical records are really, really cool, but the reality is five years from now, the Internet of Things is going to cause them &amp;hellip; How to Stop Hackers From Taking Over Your Home According to Stacey Higginbothaman authority on the Internet of things and former Fortune colleagueApple&amp;rsquo;s Home Kit is especially secure &amp;hellip; A very British crisis: One man&amp;rsquo;s 11hr mission to make internet-connected The Memo The solo tea drinker will tell you it&amp;rsquo;s always bag first brew then milk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Cyber security isn&amp;rsquo;t just about big IT; it&amp;rsquo;s about locks, lights, and even Military &amp;amp; Aerospace Electronics As it turns out, the so-called Internet of things (IoT) with its many Internet-connected devices ranging from children&amp;rsquo;s toys, smart phones, cameras, lights &amp;hellip; This Stunning House Was Made Entirely From The Remains Of A Demolished Co.Design (blog) Every once in awhile, the internet of things gets things right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain starts transition from hype to everyday use in markets The Australian Securities Exchange (ASX) has made some of the boldest moves to experiment with blockchain yet. It announced this year that it would &amp;hellip; Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Warning About Its Hackable Insulin Pump Is Terrifying Similar issues exist around &amp;ldquo;internet of things&amp;rdquo; devices like Wi-Fi lightbulbs and internet-connected printers. The difference is that a weakness in a &amp;hellip; Cloud Security Alliance Maps Out IoT Security Guidelines While internet of things devices are often small embedded systems, IoT and the cloud are heavily co-mingled, as IoT devices make use of cloud &amp;hellip; ANZ, Wells Fargo test blockchain for cross-border payments Blockchain technology promises to reduce the time and cost of transferring funds and increase access to liquidity, according to ANZ Banking Group &amp;hellip; How IoT and data analytics technologies can improve Australia&amp;rsquo;s healthcare CIO Australia &amp;hellip; IoT hardware spending will exceed US$2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
HTML5 Web Apps Help Analyze IoT Data In Real-Time JaveScript HTML5 code can be leveraged to create web applications that allow real-time visualization and analysis of Internet of Things (IoT) data. Is Hillary Clinton the President Blockchain Needs? The announcement was seen as somewhat of a surprise, as blockchain is largely associated with transactions that occur outside the watchful eye of &amp;hellip; Russia Dealbook: Mail.ru Group acquires Pixonic for $30m; Sberbank hops on DEALSTREETASIA The latest in the deals landscape in Russia has seen Mail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The hackers that ruined Christmas 2014 have been arrested It isn&amp;rsquo;t PCs anymore, it is the Internet-of-Things, or the vastly larger number of other devices (cameras, routers, modems, and such) that are now &amp;hellip; Blockchain Startup Loyyal Partakes In Dubai Future Accelerators Program For Loyyal, participating in the Dubai Future Accelerators program is invaluable. The blockchain startup will work with Dubai Holding, who focus their &amp;hellip; Stake your financial life on blockchain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Experts argue about whether the IoT needs humans Experts at the IPExpo conference argued recently about the value of humans in the age of the Internet of Things (IoT). Some said that the IoT is about &amp;hellip; Hacked by your fridge: the Internet of Things could spark a new wave of Manufacturers&amp;rsquo; Monthly The past few weeks have seen a remarkable and somewhat alarming development in cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Death of the internet: GIF at 11 Today&amp;rsquo;s reality is that DDoS attacks have become the Great Equalizer between private actors &amp;amp; nation-states.&amp;rdquo; How? With the Internet of Things (IoT). A better way to manage water with the Internet of Things is through using the Internet of Things to increase availability and &amp;hellip; Dubai to move all government documents onto Blockchain The Dubai Government will move all its documents onto Blockchain and go paperless by 2020, the Dubai Media Office announced yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
VMware AirWatch Launches Unified Endpoint Management VMware Airwatch also revealed new support for internet of things devices, touchless sensors and enterprise-level smart glasses on the same mobility &amp;hellip; European Parliament Document Suggests Future of Democracy Linked to Bitcoin Magazine Regardless of one&amp;rsquo;s opinions about the outcome, the recent Brexit referendum in the U.K. should be considered a welcome example of direct &amp;hellip; IBM Invests $200 Million in Watson IoT Blockchain Development Advertised sites are not endorsed by us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Global Metal Cutting Machine Tools Market to Witness Growth Through 2020, SYS-CON Media (press release) Technavio analysts forecast the global metal cutting machine tools market to grow at a CAGR of more than 7% during the forecast period, according to &amp;hellip; How Not to Be Overwhelmed by the IoT Feeling a little intimidated by the Internet of Things? Here&amp;rsquo;s a straightforward and pragmatic process for taking on IoT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IBM to pour $200 million into Watson Internet of Things AI business in VentureBeat IBM said today it will invest $200 million in a new global headquarters for its Watson Internet of Things business in Munich Germany. The move is part &amp;hellip; Industries have started embracing Internet of Things, says IBM Plugging computer sensors into factories, cars, shops and offices to help them operate more smartly on the industrial Internet, or so-called Internet of &amp;hellip; Carriers, Network Equipment Vendors Getting Ready for 5G &amp;hellip; streaming video and virtual reality (VR) to the internet of things (IoT), smart cities, machine-to-machine (M2M) communications and autonomous cars &amp;hellip; Qt unveils lightweight developer framework for the Internet of Things The Qt Company, which offers a cross-platform development framework for enterprises to build their applications once and run them anywhere on any &amp;hellip; The Internet Of Things&amp;rsquo; Dark Side: Hackers Easily Spread Distributed Denial iTech Post While various tech companies have claimed that the Internet Of Things will be beneficial to the public in various ways, there are already exceptions to &amp;hellip; JP Morgan Has a New Twist on Blockchain The move is a break with how some banks have approached the use of a bitcoin-style network, known generally as the blockchain, to try to replace &amp;hellip; Blockchain Makes the Payments Globe Smaller and Cheaper Blockchain and payments have come to go hand-in hand since it emerged to power bitcoin, but the real pain financial institutions are looking to solve &amp;hellip; Blockchain consultant Anthony Lewis joins R3 research lab Cryptocurrency and blockchain consultant Anthony Lewis is joining R3 blockchain consortium as director of the lab and research center in Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Ubiquiti Networks (UBNT) Shares are Up 0.56% &amp;hellip; for enterprises enable wireless local area network (WLAN) infrastructure, video surveillance products, and machine-to-machine communications. Wal-Mart&amp;rsquo;s CIO on the Retailer&amp;rsquo;s Push Into Online Grocery Shopping TERRELL: I&amp;rsquo;m so fascinated with the Internet of Things. It could make a huge difference operationally and with the improvement of the experience for &amp;hellip; &amp;lsquo;Internet of Things&amp;rsquo; Symposium Highlights Use of Urban Data Chicago Chief Innovation Officer Brenna Berman highlighted examples of data-driven analytics leading to policy reform and social change at the &amp;hellip; Source Code For World&amp;rsquo;s Largest DDoS Attack Out In Public: Mirai Botnet Tech Times The malware is designed to infiltrate Internet of Things devices which users have not protected by changing their username and passwords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Silicon Valley Selects Synereo Over Ethereum As Blockchain Platform The two will be working together to build the decentralized web on top of Synereo&amp;rsquo;s Blockchain 2.0 platform. NFX Guild has chosen Synereo over other &amp;hellip; Is Zebra Tech&amp;rsquo;s Zatar the Facebook of Things? Zebra Technologies showcased its emerging Internet of Things (IoT) technologies at the Innovation Labs World conference in Singapore this week. 10 Indian startups to participate in Japan&amp;rsquo;s largest IT forum Internet of Things or IoT refers to a network of inter-connected devices that can be accessed through the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Oct 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-10-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
T-Mobile Maintaining 2G In Hope Of Securing AT&amp;amp;T M2M Custom &amp;hellip; Over LTE available on their network or device, and a great number of customers use 2G connections for what&amp;rsquo;s called M2M, or machine to machine. 5 Quantum Cryptography and Quantum Encryption Companies Founded in 2012, Qubitekk has taken in at least $2 million in funding (in additions to various grants) in order to develop a machine-to-machine &amp;hellip; Paxos (ItBit) and Euroclear to Deploy Blockchain Network For Gold Markets Paxos, a Blockchain company formerly known as ItBit, announced its strategic partnership with Euroclear to deploy a Blockchain settlement service for &amp;hellip; JP Morgan Joins Ethereum in Developing Private Blockchain &amp;lsquo;Quorum&amp;rsquo; JP Morgan, America&amp;rsquo;s largest bank with total assets of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Overnight Cybersecurity: Report - Trump briefed Russia behind DNC hacks The Hill &amp;hellip; AccuVote machines Georgia uses can spread viruses to each other by infecting ballot definition cartridges that get carried from machine to machine. Blockchain Has Turned Finance on Its Head Claim Swiss Central Bank There is much talk about blockchain and its various applications and possibilities, so hearing about a vision for the future of blockchain applications &amp;hellip; Is blockchain the key to paperless travel?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Bigger than bitcoin: Here comes blockchain Blockchain has so far proved to be a bomb-proof way of registering and storing information about a product or an event so that it is indelibly preserved &amp;hellip; Like it or not, blockchain is coming to health IT Blockchain is invading health IT. And it&amp;rsquo;s moving fast. Sure, while blockchain&amp;rsquo;s encrypted distributed ledger technology has already made big inroads &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things (IoT) Doing Our Thing Since Y2K would come to an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What would make Blockchain a Viable Option for Enterprises? uniting the different Blockchain technology networks was one of the central &amp;hellip; How France&amp;rsquo;s Industry of the Future is creating utopia through business Investing heavily in Internet of Things and other smart technologies could dramatically accelerate consumer take-up, improving the efficiency of homes &amp;hellip; Why the telecoms industry must get a grip on the Internet of Things coverage required to power the Internet of Things (IoT) is a serious &amp;hellip; Smart Insights Publishes Blockchain White Paper Intelling, a consultancy specializing in secure transactions, has published a new Smart Insights White Paper titled Blockchain: versatility by means of &amp;hellip; ASX completes blockchain trading platform prototype The Australian Securities Exchange (ASX) has said that its blockchain initiative is on track for a final decision in the second half of 2017, with the &amp;hellip; 31% Of Consumers Limit Use Of IoT/Connected Devices; 61% Would Use More If Yahoo Finance 27, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Sales of the technology industry&amp;rsquo;s most-talked-about products, Internet of Things (IoT)/connected devices, may fall short of &amp;hellip; Currency Settlement Service CLS Reveals Big Blockchain Ambitions Multi-currency cash settlement system provider CLS is building a payments netting service that will enable cash trades on IBM&amp;rsquo;s Fabric blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Digi International Announces Immediate Availability of ConnectCore for Yahoo Finance 26, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Digi International, (DGII) (www.digi.com), a leading global provider of machine-to-machine (M2M) and Internet of Things &amp;hellip; Blockchain Just Got Much More Powerful computers process and pass along transactions on a running ledger, or chain. HellaPHY Wireless Positioning Better than 50 Meters for IOT Acorn Technologies, Inc., a semiconductor and wireless technology company focused on the Internet of Things (IoT), has developed and &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things Isn&amp;rsquo;t Coming, It&amp;rsquo;s Here The main driver in this significant growth is the Internet of Things (IoT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Connected car raises prospect of stress-free daily commute In the race to bring smart cars up to speed with handheld devices and wearables in the internet of things (IoT) space, automotive designers are putting &amp;hellip; Waste start-up says its software can deliver reduction in emissions Mr Walsh believes the recent introduction of a nationwide Internet of Things (IoT) network in Ireland will help the company, and says there is &amp;hellip; In-Car Infotainment Projected To Dominate In Connected Cars Almost all (98%) cellular machine-to-machine (M2M) data over the next five years will come from in-car infotainment systems, according to Juniper &amp;hellip; Blockchain Gets a Push in Shanghai: &amp;lsquo;A Shared Version of the Truth&amp;rsquo; A series of packed events in Shanghai billed as International Blockchain Week focused on the technological backbone for the virtual currency bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
K3OPS On RFI Identifies the Energetic Problem Delivering better code would ensure a better security for users, we can&amp;rsquo;t let hackers penetrate our privacy attacking through the Internet of Things. Cubical Labs Home Automation Review : A step in the right direction Open Systems A thriving &amp;lsquo;Machine-to-Machine&amp;rsquo; network will require mutually understandable protocols. Again, in layman terms this means machines &amp;hellip; LG Uplus to jump into global market with IoT service LG Uplus has a big lead over its competitors in Internet of Things for the residential sector with 430,000 subscribed households while the others are &amp;hellip; LG Uplus sets sights on global expansion &amp;hellip; especially artificial intelligence and the Internet of Things - two of the hottest buzzwords in the information and communication technology sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
PTC Announces Availability of Its ThingWorx Internet of Things Platform Through its participation in the program, PTC is now announcing the availability of its ThingWorx Internet of Things (IoT) platform running on the SAP &amp;hellip; Share&amp;amp;Charge Blockchain EV Charging Sharing Network Moves into Beta Underlying this all is blockchain P2P database and secure transaction technology from Ethereum, the same virtual currency transaction platform used &amp;hellip; Faster Payments faces history with RBS blockchain test The paper says the current cross-border clearing and settlement value chain is costly, inefficient, and not transparent and the team thinks blockchain &amp;hellip; The IoTS World Congress will showcase the potential of industrial IoT Embedded Computing Design From 25 to 27 October, the Internet of Things (IoT) Solutions World Congress at Fira de Barcelona will be answering these and many other future &amp;hellip; Banks Collaborate to Provide Global Payments on Blockchain Global provider of financial settlement solutions, Ripple has announced that a number of global banks are combining to establish the first interbank &amp;hellip; Can IIB&amp;rsquo;s MQTT Node use a variable for the topic name?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Blockchain to Drive Wanxiang&amp;rsquo;s $30 Billion Smart Cities Initiative Auto giant Wanxiang announced today that it will use blockchain technology as part of its newly announced smart cities initiative. Revealed at the &amp;hellip; Combine a washed-up James Bond with the Internet of Things and somehow you Yahoo News Normally, a headline about former James Bond Pierce Brosnan starring in a thriller about internet-connected fridges would be only found on the Onion &amp;hellip; Deloitte Advises on Blockchain for Health and Human Services Deloitte has released its Blockchain: Opportunities for Health Care, describing the ways in which blockchain-enabled technology can benefit health &amp;hellip; Minsheng Insurance Retains ConsenSys and BlockApps to build Blockchain Regulatory Commission, along with BlockApps, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading Ethereum enterprise blockchain developer&amp;rsquo;s platform, and ConsenSys, the largest &amp;hellip; China&amp;rsquo;s Financial Firms Urge Regulators to Help Mature Blockchain China&amp;rsquo;s major financial institutions sent a clear message to innovators in the blockchain industry today, asserting that governance and oversight &amp;hellip; Google Cloud Joins Amazon, IBM in Serving Blockchain Clients Google&amp;rsquo;s cloud services will be used to test blockchain technologies for banks, an area where IBM, Microsoft and Amazon have been courting clients &amp;hellip; Filling IOT connectivity, security gaps - Networks Unlimited Press Office Internet of things (IOT) devices are a critical component of the new digital economy, collecting and sharing information about myriad things from &amp;hellip; Global Blockchain Summit: Hyperledger wants to work with unpermissioned International Business Times UK The Linux Foundation/Hyperledger Project and IBM took to the stage at Global Blockchain Summit in Shanghai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Aerohive to Speak on IoT Panels at NetEvents Global Summit Aerohive Networks (HIVE) today announced its participation at the NetEvents Global Summit, taking place September 21-22 in Silicon Valley. So Here&amp;rsquo;s The Deal: Week Of Sept 19 In the growing effort to expand the ioT (internet of things), SAP and Bosch have come to an agreement to connect Bosch products to the internet. Accenture Touts Need For Blockchain Editing Tool bitcoins Blockchain is a digital technology for recording and verifying transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Global Market for the Internet of Things in Commercial Buildings will Yahoo Finance Memoori Research has released a new report today entitled The Internet of Things in Smart Commercial Buildings 2016 to 2021. The report focuses &amp;hellip; 66% Collect, Share IoT With Customers, Suppliers, Competitors Almost a quarter (24%) said they believe leveraging the Internet of Things can provide value and a competitive advantage today and more than half &amp;hellip; Project Bletchley - Blockchain infrastructure made easy on Microsoft Azure with the launch of an early version of the Bletchley v1 &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things and Its Impact on Education The Internet of Things or IoT is a big thing nowadays and has been revolutionizing every industry and sector of the society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Industrial IoT is inching toward a consensus on security The Industrial Internet Consortium, a group that includes some of the biggest players in the internet of things, took action on Monday to clear the air. How blockchain will grow beyond bitcoin Of equal if not greater importance is the blockchain, the technology that supports the cryptocurrency, the distributed ledger which enables &amp;hellip; PeerNova Engages with State Street on Blockchain-Based Capital Lineage FINalternatives Distributed systems specialist PeerNova has teamed with global financial services company State Street to develop a blockchain-based prototype &amp;hellip; G8 Communications Ltd continues to build sales momentum G8 is a wireless device manufacturer operating in the Internet of Things (IoT) industry and specialises in machine to machine (M2M) connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Briefs: Deutsche fights miss-selling claims, Silver Chef raises equity, Banking Day Deutsche Bank said it would fend off a $US14 billion claim from the US Department of Justice over allegations it mis-sold mortgage-backed securities &amp;hellip; Marketing Of Shipping Container Farms Leaves Internet Of Things Behind The MediaPost Communications The Internet of Things may be taking a turn toward invisibility when it comes to marketing, at least in how a new connected farm is being positioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Traditional investment banking model &amp;lsquo;no longer an option,&amp;rsquo; states McKinsey Brave New Coin In the coming years, blockchain technology could deliver a broad range of benefitsincluding faster clearing and settlement, ledger consolidation, &amp;hellip; Trai to initiate consultation on M2M communication, IoT soon Telecom regulator Trai will soon initiate a consultation process for formulating a framework to govern machine-to-machine communication and Internet &amp;hellip; Trai to initiate consultation on IoT, M2M communication soon &amp;hellip; consultation process for formulating a framework to govern machine-to-machine (M2M) communication and Internet of Things (IoT) technologies that &amp;hellip; Trai to initiate consultation on machine-to-machine communication, IoT soon New Delhi: Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (Trai) will soon initiate a consultation process for formulating a framework to govern &amp;hellip; Trai to initiate consultation on machine-to-machine communication, IoT soon Internet of Things, fuelled by machine-to-machine communication essentially refers to microprocessor and sensor fitted gadgets or &amp;lsquo;things&amp;rsquo; within a &amp;hellip; 81 FR 64139 - Multistakeholder Process on Internet of Things Security 81 FR 64139 - Multistakeholder Process on Internet of Things Security Upgradability and Patching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
VirnetX Holding Corp (VHC) Updated Price Targets &amp;hellip; file transfer, remote desktop and machine-to-machine (M2M) communications. Its portfolio is focused on securing communications over the Internet, &amp;hellip; Why Success in Frontier Tech Is Tricky Frontier tech is the collective term for significantly ground-breaking new tech in a variety of fields: artificial intelligence, the Internet of Things, virtual &amp;hellip; Cross-Gaming Trading from New Blockchain-Based Platform EverdreamSoft and IndieSquare have announced the launch of a new collaborative effort called Project ORB which will use blockchain technology to &amp;hellip; Acorn Energy, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
VoIP consultation too early, unwarranted, say operators &amp;hellip; and receive calls. Bharti has suggested a 11-digits plan, and Reliance Jio is for a 13-digit plan, similar to Machine-to-Machine communications. C-Labs Introduces Machine Monitor to Manufacturers BELLEVUE, Wash., Sept. 15, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; C-Labs Corporation, an award-winning provider of software for the industrial Internet of Things &amp;hellip; Seeing the Potential, Intel Revamps Its Portfolio to Focus on 5G For more than a year, the company has been talking about a shift in its focus away from PCs and toward data center and IoT (Internet of Things) &amp;hellip; The Future of Federal Cybersecurity Is in Predictive Security Intelligence He added that Commerce is also coordinating, via wireless machine-to-machine communications, with DHS&amp;rsquo; NCCIC, to share threat information and &amp;hellip; What Exactly Is The Internet of Things?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Australia to take global lead on blockchain standards Australia will lead the international development of standards governing blockchain distributed ledger technology after a model submitted by &amp;hellip; OMA Opens Registration for IoT Developer Seminar and Webinar &amp;hellip; Open Mobile Alliance (OMA) today announced that registration is open for its developer focused Internet of Things (IoT) seminar/webinar entitled, &amp;hellip; Solution: Internet of Things without ecological disaster turn into an ecological disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Telenor Connexion, LumenRadio in #IoT partnership LumenRadio is happy to announce a partnership with Telenor Connexion, a leading provider of Internet of Things (IoT) solutions, fully owned by &amp;hellip; IoT telecom services market size revealed Machine to Machine (M2M) billing management services segment is expected to hold the largest market share in the IoT telecom services market and &amp;hellip; Global X Expands Themed ETF Suite with 3 New Tech Options &amp;ldquo;Robotics &amp;amp; AI, FinTech, and the Internet of Things are among the most significant emerging technological trends in the world as they are set to disrupt &amp;hellip; Capital One CIO Rob Harding on Blockchain, IoT, DevOps, AI and machine MIS Asia Capital One Europe CIO Rob Harding is leading a huge transformation at the company&amp;rsquo;s UK business which involves becoming more digital, agile and &amp;hellip; AT&amp;amp;T Internet of Things Sizzle Reel IoT and what it means for the future of business and arguably culture itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
LoRa Enters SoftBank&amp;rsquo;s IoT Harem SoftBank has become the latest telco to announce a big commitment to LoRa technology, revealing that it will begin providing Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; Capital One CIO Rob Harding on Blockchain, IoT, DevOps, AI and machine CIO UK Harding has looked at Blockchain personally, and says that there are various groups in Capital One&amp;rsquo;s parent organisation looking at it too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Why app development is going micro New companies such as Workato are extending machine-to-machine workflows between SaaS systems, but they are very similar in complexity to BPM &amp;hellip; The wonders and woes of smart vehicles However, the significance of the smart car is just a dot in the spectrum of IoT or the Internet of Things, a term to describe a development in the Internet &amp;hellip; Crypto assets overview - Sep 11, 2016 Antshares, a blockchain project focused on bringing digital assets to everyone, finished its ICO on wednesday raising a total of 6130 BTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Katie Byrne: Eat, train, sleep, repeat&amp;hellip; how I crossed the line to fitness Irish Independent I was only capable of emitting the occasional &amp;lsquo;whooooosh&amp;rsquo; sound as I ambled from machine to machine, wiping sweat off my brow. Bicep curls? Blockchain &amp;lsquo;brings $10bn expense savings potential to reinsurance sector&amp;rsquo; reinsurance industry and reduce the sector&amp;rsquo;s expenses by up to $10bn, &amp;hellip; Sigma Designs Inc. (SIGM) Expected to Earn Q3 2017 Earnings of $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things Boom Felt In Long Island, N.Y. (TNS) &amp;ndash; Billions of digital conversations are going on around us, a stream of wireless chatter from machine to machine that companies on Long Island &amp;hellip; Deloitte launches its first bitcoin ATM The Toronto office, home to its Rubix blockchain division, initially offered the bitcoin ATM to employees only. But this was quickly followed by a public &amp;hellip; Intel Sheds McAfee Majority Stake Amid Failed &amp;lsquo;Synergies&amp;rsquo; &amp;hellip; mobility and the emerging market for the Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
How Will Terrorists Use the Internet of Things? The Justice Department Is Defense One In our division, we&amp;rsquo;ve just started a group looking at nothing but the Internet of Things. John P. Carlin, the U.S. Assistant Attorney General for National &amp;hellip; IoT Brings Year-Round Farming Into Shipping Containers &amp;lsquo;Shipping container farms&amp;rsquo; are entering the Internet of Things with connected features to enable remote management. That connectivity also extends &amp;hellip; Cognizant Joins Chamber of Digital Commerce The Chamber is the world&amp;rsquo;s leading trade association representing the blockchain industry and works closely with policymakers, regulators and &amp;hellip; IC Insights Trims IoT Chip Market Forecast Although the electronics industry has hardly completed the hype cycle for the Internet of Things (IoT), it&amp;rsquo;s beginning to face reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
49% of Execs Say IoT Benefits Trump Security Concerns Interest in the Internet of Things appears to be increasing and security concerns might not be a deterring factor. When it comes to IoT security concerns &amp;hellip; Identity protection suite WISeID 6 uses a blockchain for ID storage and Brave New Coin The company is well known for deploying digital identity systems for Internet of Things ecosystems, and designs identity systems for physical, mobile, &amp;hellip; (and Cultures): The Internet of Things Platform Development Project of QI&amp;rsquo;s health-related Internet of Things (IoT) Platform Development Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 7, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-07/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Major Automation Vendor Selects Matrikon Technology To Embed OPC UA Automation World &amp;hellip; 4.0 is driving requirements for open and secure connectivity between devices (e.g., machine-to-machine or M2M) and edge-to-cloud solutions. Why Intel bought &amp;lsquo;eyes&amp;rsquo; for its drones But some say the sale represents a shift into the Internet of Things. Just as the internet brings people and information together, the so-called IoT &amp;hellip; Newly Discovered Vulnerability Could Result in a Complete Take-Over of Your The Merkle The firmware used in routers and Internet of Things devices is neglected by manufacturers and their customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 6, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-06/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Internet Of Things Is Literally In The Sea The Internet of Things is in the sea. More specifically, it&amp;rsquo;s in an Oyster farm in Hobart. And we have The Yield, Microsoft, Bosch and Intel to thank. China&amp;rsquo;s US$285B social security funds will soon be using blockchain tech China&amp;rsquo;s National Council for Social Security Funds is adopting blockchain tech for the first time to keep down transaction costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 5, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-05/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Internet of Things jumpstarts asset allocation in Oil &amp;amp; Gas Sector For too long businesses in the resources industry have worked in operational silos; with the left hand rarely knowing what the right hand is doing, there &amp;hellip; The Value of Data-Driven Automation to the ITSM industry As the Internet of Things rapidly creates a new wave of data to be gathered and stored, automation will enable MSPs to better manage their customers&amp;rsquo; &amp;hellip; What to Expect From DEVCON2 and The Global Blockchain Summit Demo Day (September 22): according to the organizer&amp;rsquo;s official website, Demo Day will cover 15 Blockchain oriented startups and projects, with their &amp;hellip; How an Inventor You&amp;rsquo;ve Probably Never Heard of Shaped the Modern World But then there&amp;rsquo;s the Internet of things, the much anticipated infrastructure of a connected, smart world of the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 4, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-04/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Social security funds to use blockchain Blockchain technology will be used in China &amp;lsquo; s social security system because it can facilitate trade and lower transactions costs , according to Wang &amp;hellip; Bank of America Downgrades STMicroelectronics NV (ADR) to Underperform The Company designs develops manufactures and markets a range of semiconductor products used in applications such as Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; Zacco at the Internet of Things Conference takes place at Ideon in Lund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 3, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-03/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Pokmon Go, IoT, and System Design What do Pokmon Go and Internet of Things (IoT) system design have in common? Let&amp;rsquo;s find outbut first, a little intro. Pokmon Go is a gaming app &amp;hellip; Chi Onwurah: Data is the new property but the Conservatives cannot tell LabourList Whether it is farmers relying on GPS to guide their tractors, jewellery makers getting on Etsy and going global or startups using blockchain to address &amp;hellip; Azure IoT collaborates with DataStax on a scalable and resilient Internet Azure IoT collaborated with DataStax to build a scalable and resilient Internet of Things infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 2, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-02/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s wild VR headset gives you freedom of motion &amp;ndash; without wires &amp;ldquo;This effectively lowers the barriers to entry,&amp;rdquo; said Anthony Murray, head of Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s internet of things division. Qualcomm isn&amp;rsquo;t the only one offering &amp;hellip; Telit launches IoT Cloud-Based Event Video Recording Are you an IoT/M2M professional ? Join us at IoT WORLD FORUM 2016, on November 29-30 in London. (http://iotinternetofthingsconference.com) &amp;hellip; London tech startup and Visa partner on blockchain - and want banks&amp;rsquo; help A London-based blockchain startup has partnered with pay giant Visa and will start testing the technology to make cross-border payments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Sep 1, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
New IBM Unit to Focus on Blockchain, Watson for Financial Services IBM this week launched its Industry Platforms business unit, a new group focused on delivering blockchain solutions to enterprise customers. Chain of Things Joins Blockchain World Congress 2016 as Blockchain+IoT AllCoinsNews.com (blog) Chain of Things is participating in Infocast&amp;rsquo;s Blockchain World Congress 2016 as Blockchain+IoT Partner along with the associate initiative Solarcoin &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things can transform your business once your networks are The Register Promo The Internet of Things (IoT) creates possibilities to transform every industry, and some of those possibilities will emerge this week at Huawei &amp;hellip; Is the Internet of Things putting your business at risk?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 31, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-31/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
T-Mobile makes Internet of Things moves through partnerships with Sequans, TmoNews First up, T-Mobile is teaming up with Sequans Communications S.A. to use their LTE Cat 1 tech for T-Mo&amp;rsquo;s machine-to-machine (M2M) and IoT &amp;hellip; T-Mobile makes Internet of Things moves through partnerships with Sequans, TmoNews T-Mobile appears to be placing more of a focus on the Internet of Things lately, with these two announcements today and one from Twilio earlier this &amp;hellip; Samsung SDS, Netki and 15 other organizations join Hyperledger blockchain EconoTimes There&amp;rsquo;s been a tremendous response to our vision for creating an open community for blockchain technology and we&amp;rsquo;re proud to be celebrating this &amp;hellip; Amazon launches Dash instant-order Internet of Things buttons in the UK Ariel is just one of the 40 brands launching with Dash buttons in the UK, moving Amazon&amp;rsquo;s one-click ordering system from the website into the real &amp;hellip; Perth blockchain power trading startup takes Auckland Perth startup Power Ledger will sign up 500 solar households, schools and community groups in Auckland to its blockchain energy trading platform &amp;hellip; Morgan Stanley veteran joins blockchain startup Symbiont, contributes to EconoTimes Industry veteran and former Morgan Stanley managing director Caitlin Long has joined blockchain startup Symbiont as president and chairman of its &amp;hellip; Intel eyes China &amp;lsquo; s Internet of Things market Intel Corp will step up marketing investments in China , as the United States chip giant aims to reshape its image in one of the world &amp;lsquo; s largest chip &amp;hellip; Bitcoin blockchain payments firm Circle China talks about Alipay and International Business Times UK But we can connect Chinese consumers and RMB to the West, to Europe and the US and to the rest of the world, and to the blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 30, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 18:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-30/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Sydney-founded startup Proxy raises $2.1 million as it officially launches Sydney-founded startup Proxy has raised $2.1 million ($US1.6 million) in funding as it officially launches its first Internet of Things-focused product. Google, Apple Eyeing Blockchain For Payments Apple and Google haven&amp;rsquo;t shown much interest in blockchain technology, but that appears to be changing, with increasing interest in Ripple and the &amp;hellip; IBM links Blockchain with AI in new Industry Platforms business unit IBM has underscored how seriously its taking Blockchain technology with the creation of a new business unit centered around it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 29, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-29/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
NetComm registers record revenue as fixed wireless booms The Sydney-headquartered wireless vendor saw machine-to-machine and fixed wireless services increase 74 percent hit $58.7 million. NetComm &amp;hellip; The Internet of Things (IoT) connected living that enhances lifestyle South China Morning Post From refrigerators that order groceries, security sensors, app controlled lighting and air-conditioning and home entertainment hubs; the Internet of &amp;hellip; The connected cow business is about to jump over the moo-n When the Internet of Things goes to the farm, the result is the connected cow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 28, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-28/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Money, minds drawn to distributed ledger tech As ideas based on distributed ledger technology such as blockchain gain momentum globally, financial institutions are investing more resources in &amp;hellip; Bharti launches &amp;lsquo;India with Airtel&amp;rsquo; suite of connectivity soln &amp;hellip; Network, data centre and cloud solutions, Value Added Services and payment and billing integration, machine-to-machine, and managed services. Why China won&amp;rsquo;t own next generation manufacturing &amp;hellip; it launched another national plan, called Internet Plus, to integrate mobile Internet, cloud computing, big data and the Internet of Things with modern &amp;hellip; Kimberly Process pilots a blockchain for tracking the world&amp;rsquo;s diamonds The recently published inaugural Kimberley Process (KP) mid-term report highlights key initiatives and includes a section dedicated to blockchain &amp;hellip; US applauds Darktrace-Samsung security plan As well as reselling and distributing Darktrace&amp;rsquo;s technology, Samsung SDS will work with Darktrace to develop IT security for the Internet of Things, &amp;hellip; The most important internet companies you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of If you want somebody to handle your software downloads or your in-game purchases, your internet of things subscriptions or your Android apps, &amp;hellip; Samsung Gaet Darktrace untuk Solusi Keamanan Internet of Things Kemitraan Darktrace dan Samsung SDS mengerucut pada rencana pengembangan solusi cyber security untuk kebutuhan teknologi Internet of Things &amp;hellip; How a $64M hack changed the fate of Ethereum, Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s closest competitor Each operates on a blockchain, a digital ledger that keeps track of all transactions in transparent, peer-to-peer fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 27, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-27/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Boomtown Accelerator Appoints CFO, Adds First-of-its-Kind Expertise to Business Wire (press release) Based in Boulder, Colo., Boomtown aims to discover and support promising Internet, mobile, software, Internet of Things (IoT) and Healthtech startups. 2016 Malaysia Developers&amp;rsquo; Day: Driving The &amp;lsquo;Internet Of Things&amp;rsquo; In Asia KUALA LUMPUR, Aug 26 (Bernama) &amp;ndash; The Malaysian Communications and Multimedia Commission (MCMC) and AT&amp;amp;T will host the fourth Malaysia &amp;hellip; 70 Percent of Orgs Unprepared for Security Risks Associated with IoT, The Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to revolutionize how the world works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 26, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-26/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Lisk Unveils Long-Term Development Roadmap The team behind Lisk, the highly-publicized blockchain application development platform, has unveiled a long-term development roadmap for the &amp;hellip; Tech enthusiasts find a home at Fat Cat Fab Lab Programing everyday objects to communicate with other electronic devices like this is part of the concept called the Internet of Things the lab is &amp;hellip; FCC Proposes Automated Threat Detection, Information Sharing for 5G ValueWalk &amp;hellip; systems and share data about threats with each other, saying plans should include comment on machine-to-machine threat information sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 25, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-25/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT and companies: Everyone wants a piece of this revolution The Internet of Things is taking over the world. Well, maybe not in a literal global domination kind of way, but just about every thing we interact with &amp;hellip; Smart Cities driven by Social Innovation and the Internet of Things leveraging the Internet of Things that are creating efficiencies amid the continuous &amp;hellip; Terepac Corp. moves into Internet of Things with blockchain technology WATERLOO An agile technology company wants to be a world leader at the intersection of the Internet of Things and blockchain technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 24, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-24/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
How Blockchain Technology Could Decentralize The Energy Grid If so, blockchain technology could help keep track of electrons flowing &amp;hellip; Just as the blockchain has allowed people to track and authenticate Bitcoin &amp;hellip; Why talk up the tech revolution, when Asia&amp;rsquo;s problems are largely FT.com (registration) (blog) There, one will quickly discover that the Internet of Things and fintech mean little to people who lack economic opportunities, rudimentary legal &amp;hellip; The drivers and benefits of Edge Computing The Industrial Internet of things (IIoT), which incorporates the harnessing of sensor data, machine-to-machine communication control and automation &amp;hellip; COINSILIUM GROUP LIMITED - Investee Company Update Coinsilium Group Limited (ISDX:COIN), the ISDX quoted blockchain technology investment and development company, is pleased to announce that &amp;hellip; IU Bloomington welcomes inaugural group of intelligent systems engineering IU Bloomington Newsroom &amp;hellip; mobile technologies &amp;ndash; from designing tiny devices that detect impending seizures to realizing the promise of a hyper-networked Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 23, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-23/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Taxis Joining The Internet Of Things, With Integrated Ad Network Expected When taxis become another part of the Internet of Things, advertising within them can then be treated as another node in the consumer journey, rather &amp;hellip; Should You Be Buying Semiconductor Stocks Right Now? Other companies are seeing an increase in demand thanks to the need for chips for Internet of Things products, while other companies are ramping up &amp;hellip; The Blockchain is Perfect for Government Services, but Where is Canada?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 22, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-22/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
What brands should know about disruptive communication technologies Disruptive innovation, the term used for technological advances which involve the internet of things (IoT), artificial intelligence (AI) and big data, has &amp;hellip; Hitachi and BTMU Start Proof of Concept Testing for Utilizing Blockchain ACN Newswire (press release) In this PoC testing, Hitachi and BTMU communally developed a system in which blockchain infrastructure are used for issuing, transferring and &amp;hellip; Rosy outlook for Autech Group on brisk sales of A/Cs and fridges amid heat pulse &amp;hellip; and it will incorporate Internet of Things (IoT) into its products to enhance efficiency in the latter half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 21, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 18:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-21/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Internet of Things set to enrich digital lifestyle KUALA LUMPUR, Aug 21 (Bernama) &amp;ndash; While the diverse definition of the Internet of Things (IoT) may be complicated for the average layman to &amp;hellip; Speech by S for IT at opening ceremony of Engineering Medical Innovation 7thSpace Interactive (press release) At the same time, commercialisation of technologies such as mobile sensing and Internet of Things, also known as IoT, enable early detection of &amp;hellip; Lisk Launches Nano Client, Access Tools on Any Device Lisk, the highly-publicized blockchain application development platform, has launched Lisk Nano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 20, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-20/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
4 Inventions from Uptake Intern Internet of Things Challenge that monitor your coffee consumption. A desktop device that lights up when &amp;hellip; Blockchain &amp;amp; Bitcoin Conference Kiev Sept 23 2016 The blockchain is the main technical innovation of bitcoin, where it serves as the public ledger for bitcoin transactions. Every user is allowed to connect &amp;hellip; M1 extends HetNet rollout, sets out plan for IoT network &amp;hellip; rollout following successful trials, as well as readying the commercial launch of a separate network that caters for Internet of Things (IoT) deployment &amp;hellip; Smart Lightbulb Servers, Leaves Buyers In The Dark But it&amp;rsquo;s also not an uncommon tale in these early years of the Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 19, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-19/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Marvell Technology Group Ltd. Announces Appointment of Jean Hu as Chief PR Newswire (press release) SANTA CLARA, Calif., Aug. 18, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Marvell (NASDAQ: MRVL), a world leader in storage, cloud infrastructure, Internet of Things &amp;hellip; Intel agencies eye off blockchain to track data use Milosavljevic suspects blockchain technology could be the solution, and the federal government has offered up as much as $1 million to Australian &amp;hellip; Lloyd I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 18, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-18/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
How can IT service providers master the Internet of Things? IT service providers have spent the past decade striving to master managed services and cloud services. Now, the Internet of Things (IoT) is bringing a &amp;hellip; Release of the Array of Things Civic Engagement Report feedback collection process associated with a new Internet of Things (IoT) &amp;hellip; Cisco to Cut 5500 Jobs as It Shifts Toward Software The gradual move to fast-growing areas like security, the internet of things and the cloud is a response to sluggish demand for Cisco&amp;rsquo;s traditional &amp;hellip; Gartner puts Blockchain at the Peak of Inflated Expectations, while Bitcoin Brave New Coin Research powerhouse Gartner Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 17, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-17/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
3 Incredibly Cheap Wearable Technology Stocks InvenSense makes motion sensors for mobile devices, but it&amp;rsquo;s started focusing more on Internet of Things solutions recently, like sensors for wrist-worn &amp;hellip; Bites of IoT Rules Engine and Amazon SNS and Amazon SNS. by Brett Francis | on 16 AUG 2016 | in AWS IoT, General, &amp;hellip; Internet Of Things Meets Location-Informed Advertising This is thanks to some of the behind-the-scenes technologies of the Internet of Things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 16, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-16/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The man Intel paid $25 million to poach from Qualcomm will make his first Business Insider Intel paid roughly $25 million last year to steal him from rival Qualcomm and put him in charge of the company&amp;rsquo;s PC, mobile, and Internet of Things &amp;hellip; CSL to enjoy cash injection following buyout CSL, which describes itself as a &amp;lsquo;connectivity solutions provider&amp;rsquo; in the machine-to-machine (M2M) sector, was subject to another, Bowmark &amp;hellip; Realising the full potential of the Internet of Things The full potential of the Internet of Things is not being realised, and organisations are being advised to consider the broader impact on the world if they &amp;hellip; Verify blog waves red flags at blockchain The potential for using blockchain technology in public services has taken a second blow in a week, with a warning from the GOV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 15, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-15/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Connected car has become a big buzzword &amp;hellip; of new vehicles equipped with this capability will increase dramatically, making connected cars a major element of the Internet of Things (IoT). Connected car has become a big buzzword &amp;hellip; the value it brings to the various vertical segments with new products and services in the machine-to-machine communication space and the IoT. How IoT can change the game for education and learning The internet of things (IoT) is a network of physical objects that are connected to the internet and, by extension, each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 14, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-14/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The road to connected cars is now open, but it needs to be secured The Internet of Things is slowly finding its way into different areas of our lives, connected automobiles being one of them. Connected cars have excited &amp;hellip; MEDIA ALERT - HSA Foundation, AMD Spearheading HSA Technologies Tutorial at SYS-CON Media (press release) I wanted to gather all of my Internet of Things (IOT) blogs into a single blog (that I could later use with my University of San Francisco (USF) Big Data &amp;hellip; Blockchain power trading platform to rival batteries A Perth startup will begin trials of consumer-to-consumer electricity trading this month using Blockchain technology a small but potentially seismic &amp;hellip; World Economic Forum Report on Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s Role in the Future of Financial newsBTC The recent World Economic Forum report showcases the importance of blockchain technology in the future of financial infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 13, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-13/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Fog Computing: Intelligence at the Edge To achieve the business benefits promised by the Internet of Things, three core problems must first be addressed. By Matt Newton , Director of &amp;hellip; NAC Foundation Supports Blockchain Position of US House Resolution 835 Creator of Aten Coin, NAC has announced that it is supporting Resolution 835 in a bid to further its goals of improving financial literacy, increasing the &amp;hellip; After Airgain (AIRG) Priced Its IPO, Should Investors Buy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 12, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-12/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
The Internet of Things is the Great Equalizer for Startups In the early stages of the IoT, many of today&amp;rsquo;s commonplace platforms were either nonexistent or extremely expensive. But now, companies with &amp;hellip; Dubai Opens Up an Accelerator for Blockchain Startups The accelerator will support applications and projects built around smart cities, smart meters and blockchain technology. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s government seeks to &amp;hellip; Blockchain and Insurance: Partners in Crime?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 11, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-11/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
IoT is now growing faster than smartphones Model trucks illustrate fleet communications and IoT technologies in an industrial internet of things booth display at Mobile World Congress 2016 in &amp;hellip; IBM to Launch One of the Largest Blockchain Implementations in the World It comes as no surprise then that IBM is also behind one of the largest implementations of Blockchain in the commercial sphere. IBM Global Financing &amp;hellip; Labour raises alarm over blockchain at DWP The controversy has blown up over blockchain or distributed ledger technology- the encryption system behind bitcoin that has provoked excitement &amp;hellip; SMEs set to benefit from new communication package &amp;hellip; hosted services, machine-to-machine security, managed communications and fixed line solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 10, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-10/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
KORE to Sponsor and Exhibit at Allscripts Client Experience 2016 Allscripts Client Experience 2016KORE, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest managed wireless network services provider specializing in Internet-of-Things (IoT) and &amp;hellip; Bsquare Receives 2016 IoT Evolution Product of the Year Award 9, 2016 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; Bsquare (NASDAQ: BSQR) announced today that its DataV Internet of Things (IoT) solution has received a 2016 IoT &amp;hellip; NetComm Wireless Ltd launches research facility after major contract win NetComm builds and sells software and hardware for fixed wireless broadband, wireless machine-to-machine and cable to the distribution point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 9, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 18:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-09/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Getting The Data Is The Easy Part As sensors collect data through a rapidly expanding network of the Internet of Things, it&amp;rsquo;s generating unprecedented amounts of data that could be &amp;hellip; Fuel price monitoring the new benchmark in fleet management innovation Using machine to machine technology (M2M) is one area that fleet managers, especially in local government with a diverse range of assets, are &amp;hellip; Australia Post Accelerator explores blockchains implementation in EconoTimes The incubation arm of Australia Post is also looking into is e-voting, as the pseudonymous nature of blockchain will ensure that people&amp;rsquo;s votes will &amp;hellip; Stratis Blockchain Solutions set to launch on Tuesday Blockchain development platform Stratis is all set for its launch on Tuesday, August 9, following its Initial coin Offering (ICO) which ended on July 26.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily IoT/Blockchain News from @surgethings - Aug 8, 2016</title>
      <link>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crypt0.net/daily/daily-iot-news-2016-08-08/</guid>
      <description>Daily IoT/Blockchain news from @surgethings.
Getting Up Close And Personal With Alexa Echo is Amazon&amp;rsquo;s attempt at putting themselves in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat when it comes to a command centre for the torrent of internet of things (IoT) devices &amp;hellip; Hyperscale networking vendor Big Switch Networks launches Aussie assault Douglas Murray, Big Switch Networks chief executive, says the advent of cloud computing, big data, machine to machine communications and the &amp;hellip; Five Tips When Using Streaming Analytics Software For the Internet of Things, real-time machine data can be used for predictive maintenance, manufacturing optimization, energy management, industrial &amp;hellip; Coding to nurture interest in stem Dr Raja Kumar Murugesan As it is, youths spend most of their time with technology which includes the Internet of Things on the latest gadgets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>